Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Inherited will...
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
They cannot be stopped.
Translation
DemonRin
Funimation
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
shin
shin
eve
in
shin
stuck
stuck
TIKKU
TIKKU
dr
ama
TIKKU
land!
land!
you,
you,
ka
ra
you,
land!
land!
Tony is a decoy?
Yeah. He'll be fine.
Let's hurry, Vivi.
Explain the situation to me.
{But Sanji-san, you were
shot earlier, weren't you?}But Sanji,
didn't you get shot back there?
Hm?
Me?
Hello?
We've caught him!
What should we do
with this strange man?!
Where are you? Tell me!
Th-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase named Rain Dinners!
All right, nicely done.
That was a star performance.
Now your boss will show up here.
Th-Thanks so much...
So, can I go now?
No, sir.
Yeah, guess not...
Look, Chopper.
{His friends are starting to crowd around again in the same place that we were just running wild.}His buddies are regrouping
where we were just running wild.
Who are you?
M-My name is Mr. Prince.
Huh? So then, you're the one
who did all this to my companions?
Whatever I can manage...
My name is Mr. Prince!
What is the meaning of this?
I-It was a man,
calling himself Mr. Prince...
Him?!
Bad news! The bridge collapsed!
And that's more
or less what happened.
Is Tony all right?
Yeah.
He has some tricks
up his sleeve, after all.
You bastard...
Where did you go, Mr. Prince?
I swear I'm going to
find you and kill you.
Careful, now... Heart pounding...
Ahhh!
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
The water! The water!
Once this cage is submerged,
it's all over for us!
Hey, you stupid gator!
Come and get me!
Are you insane, Nami?!
{I'm making that guy mad,
to get him to bite the cage apart!}I'm goading him so he'll
bite this cage to pieces!
I get it! Great idea!
Come and get me, you stupid banana!
You rotten banana!
No, that's wrong! I told you,
he's basically an alligator,
but with a banana on his head.
What?! Would you shut up?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
You rotten banana!
Listen to what I'm saying!
What?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
A monkey is an animal, but the
monkey dance is a dance, and
Don't touch that!
Learn something, will you?!
{You eat both alligators
and bananas, don't you?!}But can't you eat both
alligators and bananas?!
Here he comes!
It's no use!
What a tough cage!
Vivi! Please hurry!
Hey, you guys...
Huh?
How can you stay so composed?!
You think up something too!
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
That woman who was
at Crocodile's side...
The World Government put a price
on her head going back 20 years.
The amount was over
70 million, as I recall.
S-Seventy million?!
S-So what about it?
{That's the same price
that Crocodile has.}That's as high as Crocodile's...
The moment those two joined forces,
this became more than
just a simple coup.
If left alone,
they'll escalate this into something
that'll involve the entire world.
The entire world?
What do you mean?
That does seem a little far-fetched.
What're you guys talking about?
Huh?
{I don't need any excuse
like that to kick his ass!}I'm just here to kick his ass!
All those other reasons don't matter!
I see...
So, how are we getting out of here?
It's up to my thighs!
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
I can't handle this much longer...
This is bad! This is bad!
Tough it out! Didn't Vivi say so?!
Must be hard for you, huh, Vivi?
I'm sorry, I know you
don't have time for this.
Damn it!
{if only my swordsmanship were
better, this cage would be nothing!}If I were just a better swordsman,
this cage would be nothing!
{Try as hard as you can not to
make any noise at mealtime.}You should try your hardest
to dine a little more quietly.
Huh?
Anti-Manner Kick Course!
Hey there.
Been waiting long?
Ahhh! Prince!
Thank goodness.
Stop goofing around
and find the key already!
Nami!
D-Do you love me now?!
Yeah, yeah, I'm in love,
now hurry and open this up!
Okay!
His idiocy knows no bounds, huh?
Mellorine! Mellorine!
Vivi! Way to go!
Yeah!
Here they come, one after the next.
Go, Sanji! Pound them all!
Feel free to bunch up together
and come at me,
you damn bananas.
Anyone with manners as poor
as yours, who would attack a lady,
gets some table manners
beaten into them well and good.
Sanji! There isn't any time for that!
One-second strikes!
No, make that one-instant strikes!
Take out the third one
who just came in.
What? You can tell?
Are your ears just for show?
{Its growl is the same as the one
that swallowed the key, isn't it?}Its growl belongs to the one
that swallowed the key.
{Smart thinking, collapsing the bridge
and buying time like that.}Collapsing the bridge bought
them some time. Clever.
They have more crewmates here.
{Was that to catch us off guard,
and get to the room?}So they lured us away to get
to the room with their comrades?
Probably.
There it is!
The key to the cage!
What is that?!
That doesn't look like a key!
Wax-Wax Ball!
Release!
Ah!
What?!
Oh! W-Water! It's water!
It's a miracle!
Hey, it's him!
3! It's 3!
Mr. 3! What was he doing
in the belly of an alligator?!
I'm alive again!
I thought I was dead back there!
That vile Crocodile!
He may have tried to get rid of me,
but he didn't try hard enough!
The moment I was swallowed,
I squeezed out the last of my power
to create this Wax-Wax ball.
What's this?
Hand that key over to us!
Ahhh! It's you guys!
What? This key...?
Hold on...
A room, forcefully leaking water...
an iron cage... and this key...
I know what's going on, now.
You're Mr. 3, are you?
You startled me!
Are you Mr. 3?
Hand over the key, quietly.
Gleam!
Here comes a long throw!
What?!
I don't know who you are,
but you appear to be on their side!
If you want the key, go find it!
However, don't hold me
responsible if you can't find it!
You bastard...
What if this person is able to
pick out the alligator
that swallowed the key?
Hmph, it wouldn't do any good.
Even if they were lucky
enough to get that key,
the real key is right here. Let them
struggle as hard as they want.
You are bad.
Just a minute, Sanji!
Couldn't his Wax-Wax power
make a key to this cage?
Indeed.
Nicely done, candle man.
Let's get moving.
There's little time.
Yeah. I'm sure the first route
they took is toward Alubarna.
{But there are still so
many bananagators that way!}But it's nothing but
bananagators that way!
Aren't there any more?!
That wasn't enough!
Nothing to worry about...
{And after I had that much trouble
with one of them...!}I was unable to take out
even one of them!
{No, their strength is just abnormal,
so don't worry about it.}No, no! Those guys are abnormally
strong, so don't take it personally!
Dammit, I can't go all out,
soaked in water like this!
The walls are crumbling!
Idiot, that's overdoing it.
The passageway is crumbling, too!
Out! We're getting out of here!
{Those small fry...
They're going to pay!}These small-timers are going to pay!
{I'll kill them all, right now,
with my own hands!}I'll kill them all with my own hands,
right here, right now!
What...?
Catch you later,
you damn gator.
~Mr. Prince
m 254 771 l 476 827 528 779 873 894 1121 451 745 296 531 316
Hey, you still alive, Luffy?
Usopp, wake up!
Good grief, what are you doing?!
Swim, like you're supposed to!
{Sheesh, you guys with your abilities
sure bear some hard risks, huh?}Man, those abilities of yours
sure have their downsides, huh?
Whoa, Smoker!
Hey now, Zoro, what are you
bringing the enemy along for?!
Back off! I didn't want to.
He was this close to dying, after all.
Whatever. Let's just hurry on ahead.
We've lost quite a bit of time.
Vivi, can we still make it?
I don't know.
Nami...
{Do you still have that perfume
I bought you in Nanohana?}Do you still have
that perfume from Nanohana?
Huh? Yeah. Why?
Put some of it on.
Like this?
{It makes me fall in love
to the ends of the world!}Ah! I love you to the
ends of the world!
Come on, get going, seriously.
Roronoa!
Why did you save my life?
Hey, Zoro! Save him!
Huh?! He's our enemy!
Just leave him!
{If we leave him there,
he's gonna die, you know!}If we just leave him,
he'll die, you know!
He can't swim!
Yeah, well, I know that...
but he's...!
I was just following
the captain's orders.
I don't think you necessarily
have to thank me.
It was one of his whims.
Don't overthink it.
Then, you'd have no gripes with me
carrying out my duties here, right?
See? Didn't I tell you? That's what
you get for saving a marine.
They're here?
The Straw Hat Pirates?
Yeah! Captain Smoker
is with them now!
Let's go back him up!
All right, men!
Full speed to Alubarna!
Where is Crocodile?!
Ah, they came around.
Smokey! You want some of this?!
Ahh! It's Smoker!
Hey, Luffy, don't do it!
Let's scram!
Is this guy for real?
This way! Hurry!
Go.
But this is the only time
I'm letting you off.
Next time we meet,
consider yourselves dead.
There they are!
Don't let them escape!
Come on, let's go.
The marines are coming.
Which way is Alubarna?
That way! We head due east!
Hey, Luffy! Hurry!
What are you doing?!
Yeah...
They won't get away this time!
You know,
you're not so unlikable!
Get the hell outta here!
Don't let them get away!
I see them!
After them!
Captain, aren't you going after them?
No. I'm too tired.
You're too tired?
Hey...
Sir!
It's no use going after those guys.
Tell our men to stop.
Have them regroup here.
Contact headquarters too.
We'll request that they dispatch
all military vessels in the vicinity
{of the Kingdom of Arabasta
gather here, to this land.}to this country,
the Kingdom of Arabasta.
You're calling for reinforcements...?
But Captain,
I'm not sure our superiors
will be willing to move ships
against such a small pirate group.
{When did I ask
for the opinions of our superiors?}Do I look like a man who cares
what the top brass thinks?!
Uh, y-yes, sir! Right away!
Hey! Come back! Come back here!
Hurry!
Mm-hmm, this way. The scent
of Nami's perfume is getting stronger.
Hey, we're not actually
{just going to run all the way
to Alubarna like this, right?!}gonna run the entire way
to Alubarna, are we?!
That's right! Eyelashes!
Where has Eyelashes gone?!
Now that you mention it,
this town should have
a stable or something!
Let's get horses!
But the marines are in town.
Not to worry.
Look in front of you.
Hey, guys!
A crab?!
Chopper!
That's a moving crab!
Looks yummy!
Awesome! Awesome!
Awesome! That's awesome!
Hop on board!
We get to ride it?! Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Nice to meetcha!
Its face looks kind of iffy,
doesn't it?
And you've got yet another
amazing thing in tow, huh?
He's Eyelashes' friend.
Eyelashes was born in this town
and has lots of friends in the area.
He is kind of pervy, though.
Amazing! Moving crabs are
usually submerged under the sand,
so these crabs are like phantoms!
But he's pretty fast...
isn't he?
Guys, hang on tight!
Alright, let's go! We're off!
What?!
Stop, Chopper!
It's him! Why, you...!
Hey! Luffy!
That idiot!
Luffy!
You guys go on ahead!
I'll take care of things here!
Make sure you deliver Vivi
back to her home! Make sure!
Just make sure.
That idiot...
Hey!
Go, Chopper!
Keep steady toward Alubarna!
G-Got it.
We're off!
Hold on...!
Hey!
Hey, Zoro!
Are we leaving him behind?!
Hey, that's cold!
Luffy!
It's all right, Vivi!
He'll be fine!
I feel sorry for the other two.
After all, there isn't a single person
{that Luffy has gone after before,
who has come out all right.}who's come out unscathed once Luffy
has set his sights on them.
{Listen to me, Vivi. He will
keep Crocodile under control.}Listen to me, Vivi. He'll for sure
tame him... that Crocodile.
The moment that
the Rebel Army started running,
the time limit on this land was set.
Once the Royal Army
and the Rebel Army meet,
this land, the Kingdom
of Arabasta, will be gone.
If you are the one and only
hope for preventing that,
{then you have to survive,
no matter what. - OG}then you have to survive, at all costs.
{No matter what might happen
to any of us here, from this point on! - OG}It doesn't matter what might happen
to any of us from this point on!
B-But...
Vivi, this is a fight that you started.
{You're the one who ran
out of this land years ago,}Several years ago,
you departed Arabasta and
challenged this unknown
organization to battle.
However...
don't go thinking that
you're fighting alone anymore.
Ah! V-V-Vivi! Don't you wor... wor...
Don't worry! I'm g-gonna...
Luffy!
...Luffy!
Huh?
We'll be waiting for you
in Alubarna, okay?!
...okay?! ...okay?!
Yeah!
Princess Vivi got the slip on us, huh?
Either way, our agents are
scheduled to gather in Alubarna.
Contact them at once.
{You've taken your nonsense
a little too far, Straw Hat Luffy.}And now... You've taken this
nonsense too far, Straw Hat Luffy.
Well, what she does is try...
{to help everyone she sees,
despite how weak she might be.}to help everyone along her way,
no matter how weak she is.
{She can't bear to abandon anything,
so she's always in pain.}The thought of abandoning someone
just wrenches her heart.
She thinks that no one needs
to die in this rebellion.
Nobody needs to die?
There are many maudlin,
peace-loving fools like that.
{That's because they don't know
what a real fight is.}Those are people who have
never seen true battle.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yup.
{But as long as you're around, she's
going to go at you, until she dies.}But as long as you're here,
she'll come after you until she's dead.
That's why...
{going to put
you down, right here!}I'm gonna stop you right here!
That's worse than nonsense.
{You're the unsalvageable fool here.
This is a good example.}You're the biggest fool of them all,
kid. What an example you are.
You get close to someone,
and then die because of it.
I've forsaken tons of people like that.
In that case...
doesn't that make you the fool?
Find something funny?
You want to die too,
Nico Robin?
If you feel like it, go right ahead.
Besides, didn't you promise
not to call me by that name?
Where are you going?
I'm going on ahead to Alubarna.
I can't figure that woman out.
I'll give you three minutes.
I don't have time...
to mess with you
any longer than that.
You don't mind, do you?
No, that's fine.
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Oh?
Gum-Gum...
Stamp!
I should warn you, Straw Hat Luffy,
that no matter how hard you try,
there is no way
you'll ever beat me.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy.
You can continue hitting me
with these mosquito-bite attacks,
but you will never
Gum-Gum...
Bazooka!
Battle Axe!
Why, you... you... you...!
Did that smash you?!
You sand croc!
I told you, that won't work.
You bastard...!
No matter how hard
a rubber man like you might try,
there is no way...
you'll ever defe{-Zenef- I left this line as is because it needs a TL-QC's knowledge to be able to localize it better. As far as I know, "peat" doesn't really fit, so I'd be willing to change it to "defea" or something similar, with Luffy's response being "Defea"?}
{"Peat"? What was
that you were just trying to say?}"Defe"? What's that?
Can't understand you!
I think that is just about
enough fun and games,
Straw Hat Luffy.
I've been taking this seriously
the whole time!
{But he's got me. I can't
slug him at all like this.}But this is a problem.
There's just no hitting him.
He's all dry and sandy.
As a pirate,
I outclass you in every way!
Desert Spada!
O-Ow!
Good call on your part.
{If you'd taken that, it would have
gotten more than an "ow" from you.}Taking it head-on would have
elicited more than just an "ow."
What the...?!
That thing split the desert in two!
Devil fruit abilities must be trained and honed
until they are powerful enough
to rival any weapon.
{I'm not like you other fools, who are
only preoccupied with your abilities.}Do not take me for the fools who are
satisfied with their powers as is...
{You can regret defying me
as much as you want, now.}And now, it's time you
regret ever defying me.
Desert Girasole!
What?! What?! What?! What?!
The sand! {It's being sucked
into the ground!}It's sucking me
into the ground!
Never heard of quicksand?
It makes for a handy desert coffin,
with no need for a tombstone.
The sand is drawn down
into underground waterways.
I am able to detect where those are.
No one in the world can stand up
to me when fighting in the desert.
I'm not about...
to let myself be buried alive in sand!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
Bazooka!
If I can't hit you,
then how about I catch you?
Gum-Gum...
Finger Net!
{Can't you learn anything?
That won't work.}Are you just incapable of learning?
That won't work.
Gum-Gum...
Whip!
Are you planning to keep doing that?
Let go of me, you bastard!
Barjn!
M-My arm!
My arm...! My arm...!
It's turned into a mummy!
My arm has become a mummy!
Because of the sand.
The hydration in your arm
has been sucked out.
{I could go on wringing the water
out of your whole body like that, until you shrivel up and die.}{I could just keep absorbing every bit of water in your body until you shrivel up and die.}I could wring every drop of water out
of you until you're shriveled and dead.
That is how the desert works too.
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
I know! Water!
That was worthless.
Nothing worthless about it!
The dried-up old man
in Yuba spent all night
preparing this water for me!
Luffy-kun.
Take this with you.
The old guy told me...
Yuba wasn't going to
give in to the sand.
Gum-Gum...
Are you still planning
to do something?
Munch Munch!
{Don't go pulling
ridiculous crap like that!}What kind of nonsense
are you trying to pull?!
Die. You, along with
the indomitable land of Yuba.
Your three minutes are up.
I told you when we got started,
{I don't have time to hang around
with you any longer.}I just don't have the time
to entertain you any longer.
Sables!
The sand is nice and dry.
Rainbase
{It's a sandstorm! I can see
a sandstorm in the sky to the south!}Sandstorm!
I see a sandstorm to the south!
Take shelter!
Wait, the sandstorm isn't
coming this way! It's heading south!
Captain Smoker, over there!
Vivi, what's wrong?
There's a sandstorm
over toward Rainbase!
It's him.
Luffy...
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy.
The prevailing winds here always blow
from north to south.
{If this baby sandstorm of mine
were to catch one of them}Now if this baby sandstorm were to catch hold of the winds,
gaining in size and strength
as it headed south,
{where do you think
the larger sandstorm will hit?}just where do you think
this enlarged sandstorm will hit?
South, you say?
Yuba.
Why?!
Hey, you!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
Look. Little by little,
it's starting to head south.
That dried-up old man
has nothing to do with this!
Why, you...! Stop it, you!
Stop, you bastard! Stop!
Give it up, it won't work.
That sandstorm will pick up strength,
and obtain wind speeds
that even I can't stop.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Yuba is finished.
Stop it! Right now! Stop
Who do you think
you're ordering around?
There are any number
of rookies like you...
who are nothing but talk...
Straw Hat Luffy...
here in the Grand Line.