Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Funimation
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality-checking
alasta
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Formatting
Sewil
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove #41
Duval-sama.
What's taking Young Master Straw Hat
and the others so long?
Maybe they're busy with
the people chasing ‘em?
I heard the port's in a real uproar!
Then that's all the more
reason to stay sharp!
We don't want any idiots showing up
and taking off with this ship!
Guard it well until the
coating craftsman arrives!
Rosy Life Riders!
Yes Duva-some!
Grove #1
Auction House
You still haven't caught them?!
Admiral Kizaru is currently pursuing them
so it should only be a matter of time!
Please have patience!
You pathetic dimwitted dogs!
Not only did they do this
to my father and brother...
but they also let all of our slaves escape!
What do they take the blood
of this world's Creators for?!
When I get my hands on them...
I'm going to put them through
a living hell so horrible...
that they'll crawl on the ground
and beg for forgiveness!
Grove #13
Shakki's Rip-off Bar
I'm suddenly feeling uneasy.
I hope Luffy-chin and the others are okay...
What's with you Camie?!
Don't say worrisome stuff like that!
But...
They're strong.
There's nothing to worry about Camie...
I hope you're right...
They're up against a navy admiral.
Not even Monkey-chan's group
stands a chance strength-wise.
The seas ahead will be rough.
Giant waves they've never
seen before are coming.
They mustn't let these waves do them in.
There. Can you hear it?
Little by little the tide of
the times is beginning to change.
Adventure on the Island of Women
Meanwhile, Monkey D. Luffy
after being ejected
from Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
Damn it!
Zoro! Nami!
Usopp! Sanji! Chopper!
Robin! Franky! Brook!
Where did you send all my friends?!
Where did you guys disappear to?!
That bear-like Warlord
of the Sea is gonna pay!
How far am I gonna fly anyway?!
Perhaps, instead of disappearing, they were all sent flying like this too?
I'm dead if I fall into the ocean...
I'm hungry too...
But... I'm feeling sleepy...
I'm alive...
I don't think me being rubber
is why I'm still alive...
But what's this bear paw-looking thing?
I just hope the others
were saved the same way...
Anyway, I gotta get back!
Where is this place...
...and which way is Sabaody Archipelago?!
Oh yeah!
I have my Vivre Card!
Good thing we all got one!
Alright! I gotta go back!
I gotta get back there!
I'm sure I'll see everyone again!
That way, huh?
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now we can't beat these guys!
Just get out of here!
You can think things over after you're safe!
Go!
What's wrong with me?!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
Ouch!
Actually, that doesn't hurt.
but oh there's something in the way...
Still...
...the card is pointing this way...
Alright!
Giant Pistol!
N-No good...
I'm out of strength...
Sanji! Food!
Oh wait he's not here...
"Stomach rumble"
Thanks for the food!
This brings back memories...
Back when Grandpa would throw me
into the jungle when I was a kid!
I don't wanna remember that.
Aren't these Laughing Mushrooms?
Yeah! This is perfect for times like this!
Now I'm having fun!
Even though I'm all alone!
There are some weird ones over here too!
Now I'm feeling mad!
Laughing Mushrooms! Laughing Mushrooms!
Oh! There are weird mushrooms here too!
Crying Mushrooms!
Marguerite! Marguerite!
Over here!
What is it Sweetpea?
What do you make of this?
Of what?
What do you suppose this is?
Wh-What the...?! This is a person!
Is it someone from the village?
I don't know.
There are so many mushrooms
growing out of her body...
This is it.
Look! She ate this mushroom!
A Parasite Mushroom.
When eaten mushrooms
grow out of your body!
This is bad!
If we don't do something the mushrooms
will sap away her vitality and kill her!
So it's a race against time!
Aphelandra! Carry her to the village!
Okay!
To the village it is!
Let's hurry!
We have an urgent patient!
Hey! Down in front! I can't see!
What happened to her?!
She's covered in mushrooms!
Have you seen her in the village before?
No never...
Hey who is she?
The mushrooms are covering her face...
Where do you think she came from?
Is she even alive?
She ate a Parasite Mushroom.
What should we do Belladonna?
They come off when pulled
so pull them out. All of them.
They come off?
They really do!
But some of the roots are left behind!
I'll get rid of them afterward
so don't worry about the roots.
You've certainly brought
a strange one home Marguerite.
Ouch! Hot! Hot!
Hold on Belladonna! What are you doing?!
This is the only way to keep
them from growing back.
But isn't that a little excessive?
She passed out again!
Still, she was covered in injuries
before she was covered in mushrooms.
Really?
They seem like marks
from a tremendous battle.
We'll need to treat her wounds too.
I hate to ask Marguerite
but could you go wash her off in the river?
O-Okay! Sure!
It sounds like she's not from
this village after all Sweetpea.
Yeah...
Huh? Look here!
What's wrong?
There's still a mushroom
between her legs that we missed!
There's one left!
But doesn't this one seem
different from the others?
It's oddly shaped!
Alright!
It won't come off! How come?!
It's stretching!
Hey what's going on? What happened?
She says it stretches...
That's enough gawking all of you!
This isn't a freak show!
You're watching too you know!
Look! There seems to be a problem!
Still she's not very well-endowed.
She even seems sort of rugged.
It's no use.
What's this? What's this?
What's going on?
Oh Granny Nyon!
There's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off!
Now now. Wait. Just who is this?
Oh my!
Th-This person...
...is a m-m-man!
Th-This is a m-man?!
I've never seen one before!
Here sits the maiden island of Amazon Lily
"Kuja"
inhabited by the tribe of
female warriors known as the Kuja.
May you never dream of it or step foot on it
should you still value your life.
Maiden Island – Amazon Lily
This is the all-female land of Amazon Lily.
On occasion women will leave
the island and return with child
but oddly enough
they only give birth to girls.
"Kuja"
Inside a tall mountain surrounded
by thick jungle is a large hole
and inside it a fortress-like village
was built and a country created.
I found it!
Step right up! We have
Sea King meat on hand today!
It looks good!
It'll make your skin nice and smooth too!
How about some fresh-picked
fruit from the jungle?!
All the wage-earning and manual labor
is done by women too of course.
I brought it!
Thanks! Just set it right there!
Sure thing!
Raised from birth as warriors
they truly are burly and large-hearted
but they also have an air of
elegance about them as well.
There is no place here
for greedy foolish men at all.
"Fighting"
And more than anything the
women of this island are strong.
Here are today's odds!
1000 Gol on Poppy!
1500 on Pansy!
In this land the strong are beautiful.
Should a man ever approach this country
eradication is all that awaits him.
"Prison"
The man's awake!
Let me see! Let me see!
I want to see too!
He's moving around!
Look! He has no breasts at all!
What a weird rugged creature!
He looks so weak with his
shaggy hair and scrawny body!
He slept for quite a long time...
But I heard he ate meals while asleep!
Did you know that?
What do men usually eat anyway? Raw meat?
I get the feeling he'll eat anything...
What's going on?
--What's all the noise?
--Oh! He can talk!
Where am I?
What was I doing again?
Oh yeah!
Everyone was separated
at Sabaody Archipelago!
Everyone! Shh! He's saying something!
I remember eating mushrooms
but everything after--
My hat's gone!
There it is!
Give it back you jerk!
His arm stretched!
What kind of body does he have?!
That's a relief!
M-M-Men can stretch their arms!
How shocking! Notes! Notes!
This is most intriguing!
Say! What's your name?
I'm Luffy.
I'm naked!
You're slow!
I feel breezy!
Do you know where my clothes are?
Men are slow and want to conceal
their heads before their bodies!
Umm before you get dressed umm...!
What's inside that bag
sewn between your legs?
Bag?
Wait you don't know what these are?
What a weirdo! These are balls!
Balls?
What are balls?
They're the family jewels of course!
Gorgeous!
Family jewels!
Could you take your jewels out
and let us see them?
Hell no!
Are you trying to kill me?! You idiot!
Here are your clothes then!
Yours were all torn up
so I made new ones with the same design!
Oh?! That's great!
Thanks! I don't even know who you are!
What did you...?
I added sexy flower frills too!
Outdoor outfits are all about the frills!
Great job Marguerite!
He seems so happy he's shaking!
Don't be stupid!
I'm a man you know!
Prepare to attack!
What?!
What a vicious temper!
Is that your true nature?!
Shamelessly yelling without any care
for the fact that we saved his life...
What a savage temperament!
His words and actions haven't shown
a shred of elegance whatsoever!
His kind really is incompatible
with us after all!
Even so Kikyo!
He hasn't done much!
I'd feel sorry for killing him!
Wait! Hold on!
You saved my life?!
What happened?! Tell me!
These girls saved you after you ate
a lethal mushroom and collapsed.
Oh really?! Thank you!
Sorry for complaining about the clothes!
Just don't shoot me!
Your apologies and excuses mean nothing!
This is the woman empire of Amazon Lily!
Men are forbidden!
That has been the absolute
rule here for centuries!
Never in history has it been broken!
Woman empire?!
Now that you've regained consciousness
we have no sympathy for you!
Yeah! Now that I look closer
it's nothing but women!
What a weird country!
We'll put an end to that
disdainful way of talking as well!
Hey!
Aphelandra!
When the Snake Princess returns
she will absolutely disapprove
of this situation!
You'll also be charged with the crime
of bringing a man into the village!
Marguerite.
Sweetpea.
Aphelandra.
This is for your sake!
It is best that we cover up this incident!
Wait! Let me go!
I have to get to the place
my friends and I agreed on!
Shoot!
He broke through the roof!
Don't let him escape!
He's nimbler than he looks!
Aphelandra!
Right!
Sorry for saving you and then doing this!
He fell!
Now he's bouncing!
Hmm now what do I do?
Oh right! My Vivre Card!
I left the old guy's piece
of paper in my other pants!
There she is! That's her!
I can't talk here!
Sorry! There's something I wanna ask you!
Let go! Help!
Oh no! Marguerite's been abducted!
Rubber Balloon!
Hey. You alright?
Stay away!
You... turned fat just now didn't you?!
You must be crazy to jump from way up there!
I was ready to die!
It's a miracle we're still alive!
Really?
Stay away!
I've heard that you men have a virus!
Do all men suddenly grow fat?!
I don't have any kind of virus
and it'll be a pain to explain, so let's just say all men suddenly grow fat.
Anyway was there something
in my torn-up pants pockets?
Is this it?
This is it! This is it! What a relief!
I wouldn't know what to do without this!
Thanks for holding onto it!
L-Let go!
Oh what a relief!
There was something written
on it so I figured...
Here look!
How odd! It looks like it's moving!
A bunch of stuff happened
and all my friends went flying
through the sky in different directions.
But thanks to these pieces of paper
we can all get together again!
They're all tough you see!
Oh I've been thanking you non-stop!
Is there anything I can do for you?
Could you take out your family
jewels so I can see them then?!
I told you they don't come off!
Put the sword away!
Who are these "friends" of yours?!
Oh I'm a pirate!
Do you know what a pirate is?
You're a pirate?
This land's empress is a pirate too.
Really?
Then she has a women-only pirate group?
Are they strong?
That's a foolish question!
The most elite warriors of this land
ride aboard her pirate ship!
They're very strong!
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
She's strong noble and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
This land is closely protected
by her and her two sisters!
Oh no! The Snake Princess's ship is nearby!
This is bad!
We need to end the
incident with the man quickly!
Kikyo...
It looks like the man jumped
into the jungle after all!
Warriors! To the jungle!
Kill the man and rescue Marguerite!
The Snake Princess has returned!