Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Monsters of the Grand Line
Well? Now do you see?
I was only using you guys
from the very start.
You had some decent skill, and you were good suckers worth using.
So she fooled you completely!
This girl's like a cold-blooded witch;
she'll even overlook her own
parent's death for money!
Just chalk it up to bad luck that
you crossed her and give up.
I see.
Though, it's not like I ever
trusted her to begin with.
Even if she were a mass murderer,
I wouldn't be too surprised.
In that case, could you just
go away?! You're an eyesore!
What happened?! Why'd he
suddenly jump into the water?!
Is this some kind of prank?!
No, it's not like he slipped or anything.
Then he ran away!
No, his arms and legs are tied!
He can't swim like that!
It's suicide.
Leave him be.
Th-That idiot!
– He's back.
– Hey! What's going on, Nami?!
What do you think you're doing?!
No, what do you think you're doing?!
You're just a little girl who
can't even watch one guy die.
Stop trying to act cool!
Save me sooner next time, you idiot!
I thought I was gonna die!
Screw you!
Mess with me any more
and you will die!
I wonder.
You're covered in quite a few bandages.
I didn't have a change of clothes,
so I used these instead.
Hey, Nami.
What should we do with him?
Lock him up! I'll deal with him myself!
Arlong! Arlong!
What is it, brother?
I'm sorry! That guy had a long-nosed
friend with him, but he got away!
What the hell, Usopp?! You wound up getting spotted anyway?!
I think he might've escaped
into Cocoyashi Village.
Cocoyashi Village, huh?
Perfect. I have other
business there, too.
Hey! Arlong's coming!
What?! What for?! We just paid our tribute money to him!
It's probably about the weapons
of mine they found.
Return to your houses, everyone.
Gen!
They're here!
So you're the bastard who was
in possession of weapons.
Yes. That's right.
I've always enjoyed looking at weapons.
Are collections not allowed
under your rule, either?
No, I can't have that.
Weapons breed nothing but
evil thoughts and violence.
They're the primary cause
of disturbing the peace.
He's huge! That's Arlong?!
H-He's not human!
Right. Because he's a fishman.
Makes sense.
I control 20 towns and villages.
As their manager,
I can't afford to have rebellions.
I destroyed the great port town
of Gosa as an example
to the other communities!
The mistake of being unable
to pay tribute money
is an act of rebellion against us!
Hey! Tribute money?
Exactly as it sounds.
It's money that we offer to them.
We buy our lives every
month with money.
Adults and children.
If anyone in a village can't
pay the tribute money,
even if it's just one person,
the village gets wiped out
just like Gosa Town.
Then that huge town was destroyed
just because of one person?!
That's how Arlong governs.
They're specists that don't give a damn about killing humans.
Listen.
You lowly humans simply need
to mindlessly keep paying up!
I need vast sums of capital!
Your tribute money will eventually
become the cornerstone
of the Arlong Empire,
which will rule the East Blue!
A-Arlong Empire?!
They're planning to turn the entire
East Blue into a fishman empire?!
Just get out of here.
Before Arlong comes back.
Gen!
{The possession of weapons
is a clear sign of rebellion! - OG}The possession of weapons
is a clear act of rebellion!
To keep any more rebels
like you from showing up,
I'm going to kill you right now,
as an example to the other humans!
No way! He'll kill someone
just for having a weapon?!
He has no right!
H-H-Hey, you! Hey! Hey!
You have no right to do this, Arlong!
For eight years straight,
we've paid your tribute money!
Why would we want to
rebel now, of all times?!
Take your hands off Gen!
Yeah!
It's not like he
used any of the weapons!
Stop this! Let Gen go!
I'm saying that the possession of
weapons indicates the will to rebel.
Or what? Shall the entire
village be destroyed?
If just one of you lays a hand on us,
your village will meet its demise.
Either way is fine with me!
Get inside, everyone!
If we cause trouble now, the last eight years will be for nothing!
If you wanted to fight to
the death to defy his rule,
then you should've done so
eight years ago instead!
But we all swore to fight
the patient fight! To live!
– Gen!
– But...
What a valuable opinion!
You're a great speaker!
Yes! Being alive is enjoyable!
Even for puny insects like you!
Gen!
By their very nature,
some lifeforms are inferior to others!{arch: or "superior". OG is close but sounds like he's trying to argue against some statement, while he's really saying "all living things are born unequal" ... if that were to work in English.}
Damn you...!
Stop!
Don't... touch them!
But, Gen!
If you die, it's all over!
Don't stop fighting the patient fight!
Even if I die!
That's nice resolve!
Pay close attention, humans!
This is what happens to those who
have even a sliver of evil thoughts!
Exploding Star!
Wh-What was that?!
Look! Up there!
There's someone on the roof!
Who the hell are you?!
My name is Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
It's him!
Th-The world fears me and
calls me Demon King Usopp,
the man from the netherworld!
I'll give you one last
chance to run away!{arch: OG is close to being literal, but it's more "I'll let you off" / "I'll let you run away" than "forgive"}
I have 8,000...!
Arlong! That's him!
The guy who got away earlier!
Bring all the tens of thousands
of men you want.
I'll tear apart every last one!
He's not scared, and
the Exploding Star had no effect!
What has a human...
a mere, lowly human done to me?!
Arlong! Wait!
We'll lose another source
of income, like Gosa!
Human settlements are easy to
destroy, but our goal is to rule them!
If we lose some,
we can just get some more!
We are the supreme species!
Now he's destroying the village!
Is he...?!
Whoa! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
H-He's still alive! After 'im!
Crap!
Catch and kill him!
Hey! Let's get him back to Arlong Park!
If we don't, he'll destroy the village!
Yeah!
Do not let him get away!
Who does he take us for?!
{We'll be back another day.
Looks like you're spared for now!}We'll be back another day.
You got out alive for now!{arch: want to stress that their life was danger. Lit. it's "You narrowly escaped death"}
I'm sorry... I caused you all trouble.
What are you talking about?
You're not at fault here!
Yeah!
But who was that youngster?
Damn! I can't lose 'em!
Wh-Where is he?
Who here thinks the Unbelievable Usopp's
death would be a great waste of talent?
Me!
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Fool! What are you thinking?!
Oh, you guys think so, too? I agree!
Wh-What?
Lethal Egg Star!
– Rotten eggs!
– I can't breathe!
Everyone! It's good to see you again!
– Nami!
– It's Nacchan!
What's going on? You never
walk right through the village...
I heard a loud sound.
Arlong, huh?
Just seven million belly left to go.
You have as horrible
a reputation as ever.
That's fine. I am a pirate!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Money'll fix all this. Just a bit more, and I meet my bargain with Arlong.
Whatever it takes, I'm going
to earn 100 million belly
and buy this village!
She tells me to run, but I got nowhere else to go but here.
Plus, I promised Luffy I'd bring her back.
What's he up to now?
Things are starting to get messy.
Guess that's good enough.
Momoo! Time to eat! Momoo!
That's strange.
He should be starving by now.
Where could he have gone?
What's taking so long?!
When is Luffy gonna show up?!
Five more minutes and
I'm gonna die of boredom!
Ohh! Oh!
Oh! Incredible!
Not even Hatchan, great octopus
officer of the Arlong Pirates,
can pull you up!
You're a super grade fish!
Dunno who you are, but you're
the gutsiest fish in the East Blue!
What the...?! Oh!
It was me all along?
I'm indeed the gutsiest
fish in the East Blue.
Wait, does that seem strange?
Sure does.
Wh-Who are you?!
Me? I'm Hatchan! Call me Hachi!
You a fishman, too?
Of course, of course!
I'm a ravishing octopus fishman!
From the looks of it, you're a human?
Y-Yeah.
A marine? Or maybe a guest?
Guest?
I guess you could say I'm a guest.
Arlong's not here right now, is he?
Nope. Where'd he go?
Apparently, there's a long-nosed
outsider running all over the place.
Another one is already locked up here
{and went to Cocoyashi Village
to get this other guy. - OG}and Arlong went to Cocoyashi Village
to get this other guy.
Usopp, huh?
Guess I'll save him for now.
This Cocoyashi Village...
How do I get there?
Get in.
Hm?
You're a guest.
I'll take you there, swordsman!
What's that?
A sea monster!
It's a cow! It's huge!
A cow? They don't swim.
It's gotta be a hippo.
What's something like this
doing in the East Blue?!
This is a Grand Line creature!
Huh? What's this guy doing?
He's after the food!
What?!
Hurry and give it to him!
He'll flip the boat over!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Stay away from my food!
You did it! You're incredible,
Big Bro Luffy!
Looks like you made it mad!
Need another one, huh?!
You dumbass!
Don't beat up someone who's
hungry for no reason!
He's probably hurt or something
and can't catch his own food.
Right?
How sweet.
Here, eat up. No need to hold back.
Die, you damn thing!
What're you doing?!
What happened to that sweetness?!
The bastard just tried to eat me, too.
Here he comes!
He's gonna sink the boat!
– That jerk!
– Get back. I'll do it.
Collier Shoot!
Damn hippo!
All right! Back to eating!{arch: or maybe "Back to the food" (this here is lit. though), but just "Back to food" sounds too shortened even for Luffy}
That was good exercise.
These guys are crazy.
Here's Cocoyashi Village.
Arlong should be here.
Great. Thanks.
No problem! Bye, now!
Whoops! I just remembered,
I forgot to ask your name!
Huh? Me? What are you
asking my name again for?
It's Hatchan!
Come back again!
What a strange guy.
Wh-What the hell happened?!
What happened here,
my brothers?!
Roronoa...
What? What are you trying to say?!
Roronoa Zoro!
What?!
{The Pirate Hunter?!
Did he come to collect my head?! - OG}The Pirate Hunter?!
Did he come for my bounty?!
N-No, he didn't come. Th-That guy...
He was... Zoro!
What?!
{That haramaki guy we
caught was Roronoa. - OG}That belly band guy we
caught was Roronoa.
I caught him, Arlong!
Wh-What in the world?!
Took you long enough, Chew.
D-Don't tell me Zoro...
{Catching this scum isn't
enough to satisfy my hunger!}Catching this scum isn't nearly
enough to satisfy my hunger!
Y-Yeah, huh?!
So you should let me go!
I was just saying hello earlier!
Th-That's how we do it in my village!
But you are one of Zoro's men.
Though, it's only natural for famous
bounty hunters to come after me.
Don't kill me! I don't have
anything to do with Zoro!
Enough of your blatant lies.
You stood up to Arlong, too.
Doesn't look like you're
going to live either way.
H-Hey! As a matter of fact,
Zoro and I are really close!
So just try and lay a finger on me!
Zoro won't stand by quietly!
Oh? Which means if I kill you,
Zoro will come back?
N-No, you're wrong!
Killing me would be very bad!
If you keep me alive, Zoro'll show up!
But if you don't keep me alive,
Zoro won't come!
But how exactly did Zoro...
escape from our prison?
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
someone let him escape.
Arlong. Does this
sound plausible to you?
Perhaps Nami let Zoro infiltrate this place so he could take your head?
N-Now that you mention it,
Nami has been acting strange lately.
Yeah. She even helped Zoro
when he jumped into the water.
Don't tell me she was working
with Zoro from the very start.
She tricked us all?!
Betrayal is her specialty.
That's enough of that!
Don't go any further based
on a bunch of conjecture!
Nami!
Watch what you say!
Me, a traitor?
Eight years ago, I got this tattoo
as my oath of loyalty to this crew!
Sorry, sorry.
Nami. It's only natural
for you to be upset.
But rest easy.
I don't suspect you one bit.
We've known each other
for eight years now!
We were just a little on edge is all.
Right, Nami?
The ones we do need to get rid of
are Roronoa Zoro and his group!
H-Hey, Nami! S-Say something!
Nami!
Zoro just had to go and do that.
What's wrong, Nami?
You seem a little pale.
But, as for long-nose here...
not even you can save him now.
Not after he's defied Arlong.
How long...
How long are you going to suspect me?!
You're too smart, you see.
I'll have the amount Arlong
and I agreed to soon!
Why would I betray you now?!
Agreed amount?!
I know.
You agreed eight years ago to buy
Cocoyashi Village from Arlong
for 100 million belly.
But I just can't make sense of it.
You betrayed the villagers and your parent, and you only trust money,
so why do you care so much
about Cocoyashi Village?
Why such a puny little village?
Actually, I found this... in your room.
Th-That's my...
S-Say what?!
Usopp's been captured?!
Yeah! They took him to
Arlong Park a little while ago!
Brave as he was,
that youngster defied Arlong!
He's surely dead by now!
Damn.
Of all times to get caught, it had
to be after I killed some time there!
Usopp! Don't die on me!
Go! To Arlong Park!
Hang on, Nami!