Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
ItsKipz
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
ItsKipz
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Fuunimation
Raws
df68
You just never learn, do you?!
Let go! I'll pay later!
With my body!
Not you too!
You made another boy cry?!
He made me mad!
It's okay. Kids will be kids.
He said your tangerines suck,
Bell-mère-san!
– Say what?!
– Bell-mère!
Don't give in to anyone!
Even girls need to be tough.
It doesn't matter if
people don't praise you!
Don't hate the times you live in.
Don't forget how to smile, no matter what happens.
Bell-mère-san!
Live
Under my rule,
anyone without money dies!
Understand, you worms?!
What's this?
A sea chart?
No!
I drew that! It's important to me!
Give it back!
You drew it?
– Give it back!
– Nami! No!
Oh? This is quite impressive.
She's an invaluable asset!
Bring her with us!
Right!
No!
Let go! Let go! No!
Let Nami go! Let go!
Stop!
You got your money!
You promised not to
lay a hand on her!
Yeah. I ain't gonna hurt her.
I'm just gonna borrow her.
Gen! Help!
Keep your hands off the children!
Kuroobi.
Gen!
Gen! Gen!
I'll save you, Nami.
I won't let you pass!
No! It's okay!
You don't need to save me!
Please!
– This is getting tedious.
– I'll... save...
They sank all the village's ships.
Our idea of having Nojiko
and Nami escape to sea...
was pure fantasy.
Just as I feared,
the Navy won't listen to us.
This island will be under his control.
Bell-mère knew!
She fully knew how they work
from her experience as a marine!
She knew not a single person
could ever escape.
They took Nami with them.
What... am I supposed
to do now, Bell-mère?
We've found out where
the Arlong Pirates are!
It seems they intend to
settle down on this island!
It's time to decide!
Do we fight now and
die in defiance of their rule?!
Or do we place our hope in waiting
for help from the government,
while living under the constant fear of death?!
It's one or the other!
Only Navy Headquarters stands
a chance against them!
But HQ has its hands
full in the Grand Line.
Our hopes of them coming all the way out here are as good as zero!
But I can't let Nami go!
I'll fight!
Me too! I doubt I can live my life
knowing I abandoned a child!
We're all family here!
Even if I die alongside them,
I'm gonna save Nacchan!
Bell-mère gave her life up
to protect them!
Let's fight 'em again!
They'll blame us all anyway
as long as any one of us fights!
Nami!
– Nami!
– Nacchan!
You're all right?!
Nami! Nami!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Did they do anything to you?
Nami?
I'm... joining...
Huh?
I'm joining... the Arlong Pirates.
I'm going to join the Arlong Pirates...
to be a surveyor and draw sea charts!
What are you saying, Nami?
Are you in your right mind?
Did they do something
horrible to you? Did they?
No.
They threatened you,
– didn't they?!
– No!
Say it!
Let go of me!
Nami...
Nami!
Th-That's Arlong's tattoo.
You...
Nami...
Look at this!
They gave me all this money.
And they say they'll buy
me anything I want.
Nami!
Unforgivable! Shameful!
I absolutely can't forgive you if you join those pirates!
And them, of all people!
Do you even know what
kind of people they are?!
So what?!
If living an honorable life gets me killed like Bell-mère,
then I don't wanna live honorably!
I can't believe you.
Bell-mère...
Bell-mère died for us!
How can you just–
That's enough, Nojiko.
Leave, Nami!
Never step foot into this village again!
Nami!
How could she be so foolish?
Did she not see
Bell-mère as her parent?!
No, that's not true.
Nami loved Bell-mère.
Hey,
didn't Bell-mère say that we'd be happy someday, if we survive?
She said we'd be so happy.
Yeah.
After Arlong dragged me off,
five naval ships came to capture him,
but Arlong easily sank them.
I don't think the government will
send any more help to this island.
That's what made me realize
I have to do something.
I made an agreement with Arlong
to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
To buy the village?
For 100 million belly.
If I buy the village, we can be free.
No one else will have to die.
In exchange, I have to join his
crew and draw sea charts.
B-But, 100 million belly?
I'm not sure you can earn that
much working your entire life!
I will earn it!
No matter what it takes!
Everyone's working their hardest
to pay the tribute money,
so my only choice is to do it alone.
If I ask anyone for help,
more people will get hurt.
You know, it won't be easy.
I know.
Staying with the people who
killed Bell-mère will hurt.
I'll be fine. I'll put on a big smile,
even when I look at him!
I've decided not to cry anymore.
I've decided to fight on my own!
Nami was only ten. Can you imagine how hard of a choice it was
to fight and survive on her own?
For the only deal that could
save the village, she...
I'll make whoever makes my
beloved Nami suffer–
Wh-Why, Big Sister?
I told you! I came here
to tell you to stop!
If you make a big fuss
about her being your friend,
the pirates'll grow suspicious of Nami.
Her eight years of struggle
will be all for nothing!
Don't make her suffer
any more than she already has.
She has to fight alone,
so the most painful thing for her
is having people who
call her their friend!
– Get back here, you damn brat!
– How dare you steal our treasure!
Stealing from pirates?!
Yeah!
I'm using the huge number of pirates
in this era to my advantage!
It's like, "You get what you deserve!"
You're covered in cuts, though!
Yeah. I sorta screwed up.
But look at this! One million belly!
Forget about that!
We need to treat those cuts, quick!
I'm fine! It's nothing!
No one will ever find it here!
I'll save my money here, little by little,
and it'll be 100 million by the time it's full!
I have a long way to go.
A hundred million belly.
It's taken a long time,
but I just need seven million more.
I can earn that much now in one run!
Just one more journey,
and it'll all be over.
Everyone in Cocoyashi Village
and I will be free of Arlong.
And then...
And then, I think I can finally smile
from the bottom of my heart.
Bell-mère.
What does the Navy want with Nami?
You simply need to keep quiet and lead the way.
Why does that old guy have
a pinwheel on his head?
Guess I'll get started on
my final plunder run!
Gen? And the Navy?
Are you the thief known as Nami?
Our information has it you've hidden
treasure you stole from pirates.
The government hereby confiscates
all the property you have stolen!
What's the matter?
Did you not hear me?
The government hereby
takes possession
of everything you stole
from the pirates.
My, my. You're very passionate
about your duties, I see.
You're not brave enough
to stand up to pirates,
so you deal with cat burglars
instead to earn brownie points.
Talk about noble!
Here's a warning for you.
I'm an officer of the Arlong Pirates.
Mess with me,
and Arlong won't stand by quietly!
Silly girl. Do you think you're
dealing with me on equal footing?
Find the stolen goods!
Wait!
Stop!
Is this what the Navy
should be doing right now?!
The Arlong Pirates have killed people,
and even destroyed towns!
You know that!
He's ruling over this island and
trampling all over people's lives!
Is ignoring such a major problem
and snatching stolen goods from a thief
what the government stands for?!
Watch how you speak to me.
Continue your search!
People all over the island've been
waiting for your help for years now!
How dare you just pass
them by and come here!
Captain! This tangerine
orchard seems suspicious!
Dig it up!
Keep your filthy hands off of
Bell-mère's tangerine orchard!
I won't let you have my money!
That money's for...
Her money is meant
to save Cocoyashi Village!
What gives you the right to
take it away, marine?!
Oh? A lowly village representative,
challenging a naval captain?
Gen, how do you
know about that?
I've always known, Nami.
I couldn't believe
what you did back then,
so I confronted Nojiko later.
Everyone in the village
has known since then
that you stayed with the Arlong Pirates so you could save the village.
We only pretended we didn't know.
We thought our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong,
if you ever decided to.
You can't be serious.
Whatever are you talking about?
You're saying all
the villagers are thieves,
and we should arrest them?
He's saying that each and every
one of us is fighting to live!
But only because we can't rely
on any of you government people!
If you're not gonna save our village,
then get the hell out of here!
Dilly-dally, and Arlong'll go after your ship, too!
Mr. Arlong will?
I wouldn't be so sure.
You still haven't found it?!
We're looking for 100 million
belly here! Not a grain of rice!
Hey, you! How do you
know how much there is?!
Oh, the 100 million?
I just got the feeling there's that much.
Don't tell me he...
Don't tell me Arlong sent you here?!
Who knows?
We're simply dealing with theft
as any civil servant would.
What rotten scum!
I can't believe the Navy would
stoop to being pirate cronies!
Arlong!
I found it!
This is incredible!
I'm impressed a girl like you could gather this much!
It's all ragged and stained with blood.
No matter! Money is money!
Thirty percent of this is all mine!
Don't touch that.
Nami!
Don't touch that!
Nojiko!
Doctor! Doctor!
What is it, Gen?!
– Nojiko's been shot!
– By who?!
The Navy!
The Navy?
Nojiko!
I'm fine.
Arlong's been working with the Navy.
What?!
He's lied to Nami for
the last eight years.
He never intended to
honor their agreement!
– What?!
– Oh, no! Then...
That bastard!
He lied to our Nacchan!
Nacchan!
Nami.
Heya, Nami! What's up?
Need help with anything?
Are you still here?!
This has nothing to do with you!
Leave the damn island already!
Arlong!
I'd die before I break an
agreement concerning money.
It doesn't matter
how many years it takes.
I'll honor our agreement.
Arlong!
What's her problem?
Oh? What's wrong,
skilled surveyor of ours?
What's with the angry look?
The marines you have under
your control stole all my money!
What happened to dying before
breaking promises about money?!
Why?!
When did I break our promise?
Don't play dumb!
You teamed up with the Navy to–
When did I break our promise?
Let's hear it!
Damn you. Damn you! Damn you!
I see! So your money's been stolen?
How unfortunate.
But an agreement is an agreement.
If you can't bring 100 million belly to me,
I'm afraid I can't give
you the village back.
You scum!
It's only 100 million belly!
Just start saving up again!
Or are you gonna run out on me?
But if you do run away,
I'll kill everyone in Cocoyashi Village.
Nami,
we only pretended we didn't know.
We thought our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong,
if you ever decided to.
Oh? Finally running away, huh?
Shouldn't we chase after her?
Chase? What for?
She won't run away.
She could never abandon
the lives of the villagers.
You certainly do know
how to play dirty.
No way would I let
such an exceptional surveyor as Nami go so easily.
But I'm not a heartless devil.
Once she's done surveying
all of the world's seas,
I'll give her her freedom!
That'll take decades!
Not even a hundred
years'd be enough!
No more of this!
Take up your weapons!
Let's fight!
Gen! Everyone!
Please! Don't be hasty!
You can't die! It'll all be over!
You have to survive,
or everything will end!
Eight years ago, we swore
not to throw away our lives!
No matter how painful and insulting
it was to be ruled by them,
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
But this is their answer!
Now that our village's chance for
freedom is gone, we have no hope!
More than that,
we must make those fishmen pay
for toying with that girl's kindness!
Any objections?!
Of course not! Let's go!
We were always fully ready
to fight at any time!
I refuse to let them rule
over me any more!
Wait, everyone!
Nami!
Just a little more!
Just wait a little more!
I'll keep working hard!
I'll save up the money again!
It'll be easy this time!
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
There's no need to worry at all!
This is nothing compared
to back then!
I don't want anyone else to die!
Everyone! I'm fine! I'm just fine!
You can stop now.
Even you know there's no point now.
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time.
Joining them must've been
even more painful for you
than being cut through the heart.
You fought very well.
Gen.
Leave the village now.
Gen?!
Do it, Nami.
Wh-What?!
– Nacchan.
– Nami.
You're crafty, and you have your dream.
Nojiko! Everyone!
I won't let you go!
Stop it, everyone!
I don't want to see anyone
else get hurt by them!
You'll die, you know!
We know.
It's no use!
We've made up our minds!
Get out of our way, Nami!
Let's go, everyone!
Even if we can't win,
let's show 'em what we're made of!
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong! Arlong!
Arl–
Luffy?
What do you want?!
You don't even know anything!
You have no clue what's happened here for the past eight years!
Yeah. I don't know.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you to leave the damn island already!
Yeah. You did.
Leave! I don't need you!
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave!
Luffy,
help me!
Of course I will!
Don't touch my treasure!
Luffy!
Let's go.
Yeah!
Hey! Are you guys alright?!
Did Arlong do this to you?!
Move aside.
We have business with the fishmen.
Now that we know the truth
about Big Sis Nami,
we felt the only thing we
can do was to defeat Arlong.
So we challenged him.
But we lost by a hair.
Sorry, but we're not letting
you through this door,
seeing as you have
no hope for victory!
What?!
We're waiting here for a group of men, you see!
A group of men?
I'd bet my life on it.
They will come!
Here they come!
It's those guys?
Just who are they?
If they can't handle them,
then there's no hope
for not only this island,
but for the future of
the entire East Blue!
Those four men are here to change our fate.
Burn their faces into your minds!
Move aside.
Hey, do you think those two idiots
were part of Zoro's group?
Zoro's? They seemed too weak for that.
They're not even worth killing.
That's for sure!
What the hell?!
Which one of you is Arlong?!