Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
What the hell?!
Which one of you is Arlong?!
Arlong?
That'd be me.
I'm Luffy.
Luffy?
So, what are you?
A pirate!
Hold it, you bastard.
Where'dya think you're goin'?!
You need to run things
by us first, kiddo.
– Yeah!
– If you don't stop...
Move!
What does a pirate want with me?
Who the hell are you?
Luffy,
help me!
I won't let you make our navigator cry!
Why, you...
How dare you insult Arlong!
Butt out, small fries!
Yeesh. You just had to run
on ahead by yourself.
It's not like I'd lose on my own.
Idiot! When did I say
I was worried about you?!
I just don't want you
hogging all the prey!
Oh!
I-I don't mind if you
hog them all, though!
You sure got some guts.
That's him!
He's the unknown swordsman!
It's Roronoa Zoro.
Yeah? Yeah, I thought so!
He tricked me!
He completely took me for a ride...
No, wait. Didn't I give him a ride?
Look! It's that long-nosed guy!
D-Didn't Nami kill him?!
The bastard's alive. Which means...
It's just like I thought, then. {Dan: Too short, putting "It's just like I thought, then." instead of just "I knew it"}
The girl was a traitor all along!
Hey! Who are those guys?!
Hold it!
He sent Arlong flying!
Unbelievable!
No ordinary human could do that!
They're...
Do you still want to
try to break in now?
{If you go, you'll wind up putting
a damper on this fight.}Your presence would stall the fight.
You'll only get in their way!
B-But, why are they fighting?
What reason do they have to fight?!
Reason to fight?
Big Sis Nami was crying!
Do they need any more reason than that...
to put their lives on the line?
A pirate, huh? I see.
So that's what your guys' deal is.
You were after Nami
from the very start.
However,
what can you four lowbred
worms possibly do?!
Fool! You're not worth Arlong's time!
I've got something that'll be more than enough to handle you!
No!
It's coming!
What the... What the...
What's going on?!
Rise, Momoo!
A-A monster!
It's the Grand Line monster that
destroyed the town of Gosa!
It's here!
Th-That's...
The fearsome sea cow, Momoo!
Oh, it's him?
He's a friend of the fishmen?
Wait! Momoo!
Where are you going?!
Hey! Stop! Get back here! Momoo!
Momoo. What are you doing?
Though, if you wanna run away,
I won't stop you.
Understand, Momoo?
Here it comes!
– Alright!
– Follow Momoo!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'll do it! This is a waste of time!
What's he planning now?!
I don't have a very good
feeling about this.
His arms stretched!
He has a devil fruit power?!
– What?!
– Who cares!
Go!
Whoa! Run!
What? What's he doing?!
I dunno, but it doesn't look good!
Gum-Gum...
Pinwheel!
I didn't come here to
take on these guys!
The one I wanna beat up...
is you!
That's perfect, then.
I was just now thinking of killing you.
That was dangerous, you moron!
Are you trying to kill us, too?!
What incredible power!
I wouldn't have believed that any human {exists
who can}could throw that giant beast!
Is this fight some kind of dream?
How dare you hurt our brothers!
It would seem we need to fight, too.
Looks like we need to teach them
the differences between our races.
The main forces finally show up, huh?
Arlong, please just relax.
If you lose your temper,
you'll lay waste to Arlong Park.
We'll take care of these guys!
Alright, do as you wish.
Yikes!
Hey. Hey, guys.
There's something I...
That octopus is up to something.
Octopus is best boiled with a little salt and sliced up.
Add some olive oil and paprika, and
it's a perfect snack while drinking.
Hey, I'm kind of in trouble.
Hear me out.
See how you like having no vision!
Takohachi Black!
You idiot! Why didn't you dodge?!
I can't see!
Now to finish you off!
Hey, Luffy! Run!
Yeah, that's the problem.
I can't seem to move!
Huh?!
M-My feet are stuck!
You're the one who stuck
them in the ground!
Why would he do that?!
Takohachi Black on the Rocks!
What a pain.
Sanji! That was amazing!
Seems I've wound up following
one hell of an idiot of a captain.
Agreed.
He's... awesome!
But he's 100 times better than
some damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
Lady?
You're pretty crazy to bust in here
just for that one lousy girl.
Lousy girl?
Just try and insult
Nami one more time.
I'll {use a buttered frying pan to
turn you into meuniere, Fish Man!}panfry you in butter, monsieur fish fry!
You seem somewhat
skilled for a human.
Any sort of chivalry from a pirate
is bound to be half-hearted.
Go ahead and see if my chivalry
is half-hearted or not.
I spent half my life
raised by a tough-as-nails pirate.
It appears you don't know the true
power of the fishman race.
{Dan: This should probably me removed, unless you want to make it "heave-ho" or something}
They're still really stuck.
Still?! They're still stuck?!
Yep, they're still stuck.
I get the feeling just pulling
me won't get them unstuck.
Are you even trying?! Are you even
trying to get your legs out?!
Why're they playing around here in Arlong Park?
I'll kill them!
Hey, you! Get unstuck already!
Get back here!
Hey, octopus.
They're busy right now.
I'll take you on.
Roronoa Zoro! Yeah! I forgot!
How dare you trick me!
Yeah! And you cut down
tons of my brothers!
I'm not interested
in these old stories.
It doesn't matter what reasons
you have for wanting to kill me.
The situation's changed now!
You're not trying to destroy us.
We're trying to destroy you!
A-Alright, Zoro!
That octopus is all yours! Nice!
Luffy!
I'm back.
Why, you...
My bad!
Seems you really do
want me to kill you.
Wasn't that the guy
who saved Gen?
You're the people from
Cocoyashi Village!
Oh?
Judging from the fact you have
weapons, I take it this is a rebellion?
Then you're all–
Exploding Star!
Big Bro Usopp!
I'm your opponent!
If you wanna die that badly,
I'll finish you right now!
Just who is that lad?
He's brave one minute, then runs
away the next. He's a baffling man.
Get back here, schnoz!
Well, you got a big mouth!
Why are these people pirates?!
You're all pathetic. Move.
I'm sick of watching this.
Arlong! We asked you
not to go on a rampage!
I won't. I just thought up a fun game.
I'm gonna clobber you!
Do you really think you can beat us?
So what if we do?
We do, idiot! Let go!
Sounds like he has something to say.
What the... What the...
People with devil fruit
powers can't swim!
Though, even people without powers
would sink in this situation!
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Oww!
You fool.
Damn you!
How pointless.
Luffy!
You bastard!
I'm coming to save–
Idiot! Don't get worked up!
They want us to go in the water!
The fishmen would obviously have
the advantage in an underwater fight!
There's only one way to save Luffy!
Take these guys down tout de suite,
then go into the water?
Let's do it! There's no time!
Yeah!
Just how many seconds will
the rubber man hold out?
Oh, so that's the game?
I see.
You can have the fish.
You can dress the octopus.
This is bad.
I feel so weak.
What do we do?!
He can't help himself now!
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
They can't even breathe underwater.
Humans are utterly pitiful creatures!
Bring it on!
I'll cross swords with you, octofreak!
I'm game!
I'll take care of you in five seconds!
No, three seconds!
Don't be in such a rush.
No matter what happens, none of you have any hope of surviving!
I-I'm dead meat!
I'll defeat him in
five seconds, Luffy!
I'll come rescue you at once!
Takohachi Black!
My hair! You bastard!
I'm gonna...
forgive you.
It's just hair, so it'll grow back.
Huh?
Roronoa Zoro!
You can't cut me because
I have six hands.
Go ahead and cut me if you can!
You octofreak!
OctoTriple Razor Sharp Blade Grab!
Octo Triple Razor Sharp Blade Grab!
Ouch!
I don't have time to play with you!
He throws me off my rhythm.
{If you're not paying attention,
you'll shorten your life!}You won't live long,
if you're not paying attention!
Fish shouldn't take on a cook!
We're running out of time. There's no time!
Just drop dead already!
Takohachi Number Nine!
So what?! Come down already!
That octopus bastard!
He's meandering and dawdling!
But then, if he goes
into the sea now,
he'll be dragged to
the bottom of the sea.
But at this rate,
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
We have to do something about it!
Yeah!
Wait!
Ouch!
What're you going to do in
the sea with such serious injuries?
You can't do much like that.
If you're talking about that young rubber man, I'll go and rescue him.
Y-You will?
I'll go, too! I'll go as well!
Me, too!
No! If a lot of us go and take time
rescuing him, the fishmen will notice.
It will just cause these people trouble, if anything.
Gen!
It'll be pointless if we end up
interfering with their fight.
So I'll do it alone.
Sorry. Thank you!
I'll leave it to you.
Sorry, but please be quick.
Wait!
Gen, I'll go too.
Nojiko, you're injured!
Those guys're fighting
for my little sister!
Gen!
Okay. Come on!
Let's hurry!
Okay!
I'm sorry!
If only we were a little stronger...
Please save Big Bro!
You damn fish bastard!
Roronoa Zoro! Do you mind if I ask
you a question? You don't, right?
I heard you use three-sword style.
Why are you using only one sword?
You're already losing
fairly badly with one sword!
Sh-Shut up! I'm not taking this seriously!
Actually, there's a reason that
a human swordsman can't defeat me.
Wanna hear what it is?
You wanna hear it, right?
When you hear it, you'll be
surprised, scared, blown away!
Dammit! I can't be in pain right now!
My fever's getting worse, too!
I thought it would come down
while I was moving around, but...
Just as I thought, it's the wounds...
from your fight with Hawk Eye!
Big Bro!
What're you doing?
Are you trying to fake
an illness or something?
I won't fall for that. Roronoa Zoro!
Just check out my true form!
Look! This is my true form!
Here comes Hachi,
user of the six-sword style!
Hey! That's not when you're
supposed to fall! Don't mock me!
Ah! Big Bro!
So he was bearing the pain!
Yeah. His injuries would kill a normal person
or leave them bedridden for half a year!
What?!
I thought something was strange.
He looked as if nothing had happened
right after that fierce fight.
Is he an idiot or what?!
I thought I warned you
to pay attention.
I have a 40th degree
in Fishman Karate.
Wh-What? Someone went flying?!
B-Big Bro?!
Big Bro Cook!
Ahh...
He's been taken care of, Arlong.
What do we do with Roronoa Zoro?
Just ditch him in the sea.
What weaklings. How boring!
That's all?
Geez, they sure did
a lot of damage, though.
It's no big deal.
Arlong Park can't be destroyed
by this kind of damage.
Indeed.
How dare you, Roronoa Zoro!
You died from shock before I, the
great swordsman, could attack you?!
History would have remembered you,
had you fallen to my six-sword style.
Well, no matter how much you struggled,
or even if the sun were to rise in the west,
{you humans can't even give a
scratch to}no human could ever lay a hand on me, the wielder of six swords!
Stop it, Hachi. I know how you feel,
but if you really go on a
rampage, we'll be in trouble.
Are you trying to destroy Arlong Park?
Oh! Ahh...
N-No. Sorry.
I got too worked up.
Don't get carried away.
You're right. Sorry.
Six-sword style, huh?
What a joke!
Big Bro!
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll tell you one thing, octopus.
There's a man I must see again.
Until that happens,
{my life can't be taken away
even by the God of Death!}even the God of Death can't take my life!