Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Chivalry vs. Fishman Karate
Hm? Ahh!
He's still alive!
Big Bro! Big Bro Cook!
That fishman's punch was
a 40th-degree punch? Hmm...
Then those kicks I used to take all
the time from that damn geezer
must've been 400th-degree kicks.
What is it, Roronoa Zoro?
I'm not sure what's going on,
but you look like you're in pain.
You think you can defeat my
six-sword style in that condition?
{Everyone in the whole world
thinks the same way.}The whole world would agree that you have no chance.
I don't want to hear it.
Big Bro's in real danger!
{He's probably got a fever
from his wounds}His wounds probably triggered a fever.
I expect he's barely conscious.
If those wounds open up,
he's definitely going to die!
{But it's no time to think
about things like that!}Now's not the time
to worry about that!
Yeah! He's the only {one who can
break through this situation!}man alive who could find a way out of this!
I'll show you three-sword style.
Yosaku! Johnny!
Let me use your swords!
Of course!
Big Bro, catch!
Dammit! I feel like
I'm about to pass out.
I wonder how long
I can keep standing.
Big Bro! We threw our swords!
You said you wanted to
use them! Catch them!
Ha! I'll show you {the wall that you
humans with two arms can't surpass!}what two-armed humans can never overcome!
Six-Sword Style:
Big Bro! Watch out!
Tentacle Whirligig!
Big Bro!
Three-Sword Style:
Floating Wolfblade!
He dodged it!
He handled the {Six-Sword random
hits! He's really amazing!}six-sword onslaught! He's incredible!
What concentration!
What willpower!
{Ahh... How dare you have
the impudence to do such a thing!}Ahh... Your impudence
is so impudent!
I'm livid, you son of an angler!
I'm gonna kill you!
{If you just think about it,
you should know!}It's so obvious,
when you think about it!
{I can hold six swords so there's
no way you can defeat me}I have six swords;
you only have three!
{when you can hold only three
swords! Isn't that right?!}There's no way you could possibly beat me! Right?!
It's so obvious?
Sounds like a grave miscalculation.
{What do you bear
on your shoulders?}What burden do you bear?
{What do you desire once
you've obtained power?}What is your aim in attaining power?
He's taken in a lot of water.
We need to bring him up soon,
or it'll be too late.
Dammit! I guess I can't
break it in the sea.
It's just too buoyant.
Gen, hurry up.
It's no good. I can't smash the rock.
An oxygen {cylinder would be helpful
but we don't have time to go get it.}tank would help,
but we don't have time to get one.
{And we can't carry him up
along with the rock,}We can't surface both him and the rock, either.
That's it!
{Whether it's three swords...
or six swords...}Three swords... six swords...
The amount doesn't matter!
{Your sword and my sword
carry different weight!}The heft of our blades is different!
You're talking about their weight?
I see. So your swords are heavy.
{But my swords weigh at
least 300 kilos per sword, though they may not look like it.}You'd be surprised, but each of my swords weighs at least 300 kg.
{They weigh a lot more than you
humans' swords, you bastard!}They're a lot more massive than your puny human swords, you bastard!
{There's no point in
discussing with an idiot.}You can't argue with stupid.
Six-Sword Style:
Octopus Trap Stance!
New Year's...
Open...
Body Slam!
That's dirty! He hit him
right in his wounds!
That'll show you!
Big Bro!
He's gonna die!
{I won't let you land
while you're still alive!}I'll kill you before you hit the ground!
Six-Sword Style Esoterica:
Waltz of the Six Swords!
You'll be {mincemeat if you
touch it even for a second!}ground to shreds the moment you touch my blades!
Ground Zoro coming up!
Big Bro!
Ow!
That bastard! {He rolled on my
swords adjusting to the spin!}He perfectly timed his roll in sync with my swords.
{On top of that, he gave me
a free hand cutting service!}What's worse, he threw in a free exsanguination treatment!
{How dare he make fun of me!
I'm not a circus acrobat!}I'm not to be trifled with!
I'm no clown!
{I'm completely angry now!
I won't let him get away!}I couldn't be more pissed off!
I'll never forgive this insult!
He's as good as dead!
Big Bro looks like he's in a lot of pain.
His wounds might've
opened with that attack.
{Ahh... If I could, I'd wanna
take his place for him...}I'd take his place if I could.
{Even if it's an injury that knocks
ordinary people out, I must not fall.}I must not fall, even to wounds that would normally be debilitating.
Six-Sword Style:
Octopus Trap Stance!
It's all over!
{Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!}I must not die, even to wounds that would normally be life-threatening.
New Year's...
{In order to defeat the
extraordinarily strong Hawk Eye,}To defeat the extraordinary Hawk Eye,
I can't just be ordinary!
Dragon Twister!
Hachi!
{How could I be... defeated by...
the Three-Sword Style?}How could I...
three-sword style... how did it...?
Octofreak,
you've now learned the difference...
{between the weight
in our swords, right?}between the heft of our blades.
Are you happy now?
Sorry, but {I don't care
about that octofreak.}that octofreak doesn't matter now.
I have to hurry and rescue Luffy.
Big Bro! Watch out!
How dare you beat Hachi!
You...
You sure did send me flying!
Oh? I didn't know there was someone
in the East Blue who
could survive my fist.
There're probably many...
especially at a certain restaurant.
You disrespect me.
B-Big Bro! That's reckless!
Hey, stop it!
You'll die if you go into the sea
with wounds like that!
Shut up! Luffy's already been down there too long.{I absolutely know there's smth missing here. Gaijin: Yep, I added it in the next line.}
We don't have time to wait
for you to finish with him.
Yeah, I know.
{There's no time to waste any more.
I know that much.}I got it; there's no more time to waste.
{I'm trying to stop you when
I'm fully aware of that!}I fully grasp the situation.
That's why I'm stopping you.
You need to shut up, moron!
You can't complain
if I do this, right?!
Fascinating!
He wants to fight against me,
a fishman, in the water?
He's a colossal idiot!
That hothead!
Fighting in the water
is exactly what they want!
{If I remember correctly,
he's from Cocoyashi Village...}Oh? That guy's from Cocoyashi Village!
{His neck!
Luffy's neck is stretched!}Is that his neck? They stretched Luffy's neck!
Sorry, I'm not strong enough
to drag your whole body.
{Spit out water with your neck
stretched. Please at least breathe!}With your head out here, cough up what water you can and just breathe!
Breathe already!
I hope it's not too late!
{I'd better hurry up before
I can't hold my breath any more.}If I don't hurry,
I'll run out of air!
I see. He can't break the rock,
but if Luffy's {neck is stretched above
the water, he can at least breathe.}head is above water,
at least he can breathe.
That means, if I can break that rock with a kick,
I can leave the rest to that old guy.
{Realize... that you all
are mere humans!}It's time for a lesson!
You're nothing but humans.
Hmph! You're from Cocoyashi Village.
You're wasting your time.
Dammit! He found me!
What's the point of stretching
his life like that?!
I'll sink you as well!
No way I'll let you!
You damn human!
Are you seriously trying
to fight me in the water?!
You're an inferior race that has
to worry about holding your breath!
Okay, I'll fight.
Fishman Karate: Devil Ray Grappler!
What's that? {The power of
your kick dropped in half.}Your kick is half as powerful here.
That's the limit for humans.
But being in water doesn't cripple Fishman Karate{'s power
doesn't drop even in the water!}!
{Rather, depending on the technique,
the power doubles.}In fact, some techniques become twice as powerful!
Fishman Karate:
Blistering...
Bowel Buster!
Fishman Karate:
Flaming Axe Kick!
Back Foot Jawbreaker!
Lethal...
Upper Deck Palm Bomb!
Air! Air! Air! Air! Oxygen! Air!
I let out too much air!
I can't breathe!
Where're you going?
Dammit! Let me through.
I need air! Let me breathe!
Your resilience is astonishing.
I can't believe you're human.
Let me breathe...
{This is the outcome
of your cheap chivalry.}This is the consequence of your worthless chivalry.
{You won't be able to escape
from me and will die.}You'll die here,
unable to escape from me.
{That policeman and
the rubber man will also die.}That villager and the rubber guy are finished, too.
We'll slaughter Zoro, that long-nose
man, and the village rebels.
With all that's happened, Nami
won't get away with betraying us!
Do you get it?
With your superficial chivalry,
you can't protect Nami or anyone else!
You may be fairly tough,
{that's just silly talk
by a helpless human.}but your drivel ultimately betrays your weakness.
You humans can't handle {a sudden
change in water pressure, right?}sudden changes in water pressure, right?
In other words, if you rapidly
dive into the abyss,
{your organs will burst
out of your body.}your body will burst from the insides.
Pulverizing Pressure Plunge!
I'm not gonna let him
get away with this!
I can't protect anyone?!
He still won't die?
{Then, I'll give you that
attack as you wish!}If you wanna go again, I'll give it to ya!
{They use pulmonary
respiration on land but}They breathe through their lungs on land,
{switch to branchial
respiration in water.}but they switch to their gills in water.
That means he's just
a talking fish right now.
Will you survive it a second time?
A fish'll die if air is
shot into its gills.
{If you're also a fish,
you'll feel the same pain!}If you're a fish, then this oughta hurt just as much!
Hm?
Hey–
Don't worry. He's okay.
Really?!
Yeah, sort of.
Sort of?
I'll explain it later.
Anyhow, come out of the water,
you damn fish! Let's settle this!
You still don't get it, do you?
Whether it's in the water or
on the ground, it's all the same.
I'm furious!
{I'll make you experience the
essence of Fishman Karate!}I'll give you a taste of the soul of Fishman Karate!
{The earlier attack I used to send you
flying was the Hundred Tile Fist!}The attack that sent you flying earlier was the Hundred Tile Fist!
But my ultimate attack
is the Thousand Tile Fist!
Your probability
of surviving...
is zero!
Collier!
My chivalry is naive?
Épaule!
I can't protect anyone, you said?
Côtelette! Selle! Poitrine!
Gigot!
You son of a...
Damn fish!
Ultimate Fist: Thousand Tiles!
Mouton Shot!
I guess...
he doesn't want dessert?
Kuroobi...
Hachi...
They're small fish, after all.
{It's a million and fifty thousand years
too early for them to go against a cook.}It's one million, fifty thousand years
too early for fish to oppose a cook.
We win this game.
How dare you bastards beat my
dear brothers one after another?
Aren't you getting a little
too carried away?!
Hey, what'd you mean by
Luffy being sort of okay?
It means that he won't
die for the time being.
But to revive him, I have to go
into the sea one more time...
though it doesn't seem like
that guy's gonna let me.
Amazing! They're really amazing!
They beat two of the Arlong Pirates' officers!
{This is it. I can no
longer hold my breath!}That's all I can do.
I can't hold my breath any longer.
Gen, take my place.
I'll go in this time.
He coughed up quite a bit of water.
What's going on over there?
Don't worry. Everyone's still alive.
In fact,
I can't really believe it,
but this fight has stirred...
the hope that I've been holding back!
Man... Causing me all this trouble!
What an amazing ability to run away!
But that was too easy.
He died instantly with
a shot of my Water Gun.
Hmph! I guess I should head back.
The others should be done by now.
I'm saved! It worked!
I'm so glad I made
the Ketchup Star for times like this.
He thinks his Water Gun or whatever
actually hit me. Go home, nerd!
Seriously, what a scary race they are.
They turned the houses
in town upside down.
Well, I feel sorry for Nami,
and I really want to help her, but...
Hm?
I guess it was just my imagination.
I think I'll pass on dying.
B... But actually, although
I'm covered in fake blood,
I want something that shows
a trace of deadly combat.
Oh, yeah. If I show up with my body all covered in dirt,
it may look that way.
I'd say something like, "Ahh, sorry. I lost."
Hmm. I wonder if,
"Well, I let that bastard slip away,
but I was this close," is better.
That may not be all that convincing.
You're one of us now, aren't you?
"Well, don't cry, Nami.
We only did what was right."
I'd rather die than lose.{Flashback to Baratie 4 @15:23 - the line is expanded here to include the word "lose"}
"Well, we all fought very well."
He's 100 times better than some
damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
"Well, it certainly was a battle to the death."
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
"Well, my injuries aren't that bad."
Big Sis Nami was crying!
Do they need any more reason than
that to put their lives on the line?
Nami was only 10. Can you imagine
how hard of a choice that was?
Let's fight!
"Well, the way...
I fought... was really..."
How...
How disgraceful!
How could I be so disgraceful?!
Hold it, you damn fish!
Oh? You're still alive?
Of course! {No way that staggering
shots by a half-fish would hit me!}Like some gangly half-fish could hit me!
The moment I left my village,
I gave up on things...
like peace and safety.
{Because they live risking their lives
everyday, they laugh so happily!}They risk their lives every day,
so their laughter expresses real joy!
That's why I decided
to set out to the sea.
I wanted to laugh from the
bottom of my heart, too!
If I don't fight with all my might here,
I won't have the right to be
on board the same ship as them.
{I won't have the right to laugh from
the bottom of my heart with them!}I won't be able to join them in unrestrained laughter!
Are you an idiot?
You should've just kept playing dead.
Even your brain is inferior.
I'm done.
Yeah, you are!
You're done for alright!
I'm done!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp's Rubber Band of Doom!
Ahhh! Dammit!
I fell for that stupid trick!
Why that dirty...!
Lethal Lead Star!
Alcohol?
{How dare you do all these impudent
things, you feeble species!}I've had enough of your cocky nonsense, you insolent worm!
{No matter where you hide, I'll blow
you away using this rice field water!}Wherever you hide, I'll blow you away with this water!
{Impudent or whatever...
It doesn't matter.}I don't care if he says I'm cocky or insolent.
{At any rate, as a man,
I can't run away from this fight.}If I want to be a man,
I can't run from this fight.
If I lose, I'm dead.
I'm actually a pirate!
Water Cannon!
Wow! What power!
Why do I have to fight
an idiot like that?
He's completely exposed!
I'm gonna riddle you with holes!
Water Machine Gun!
Ahh! H-How did he figure
out where I was?!
Dammit! Dammit! Just watch me,
Usopp Pirates! Kaya!
I set off to the sea
and became a pirate!
I'll fight! {In order to become a real,
brave sea warrior, not a fake one!}I'll become a brave warrior of the sea for real! No more lies!
I'm done fooling around and pretending to be a pirate!
What'd you say's done?
This fight! You know,
alcohol catches fire!
Lethal Fire Star!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Water! Water!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
This isn't good!
Water, water, water! Water!
Usopp Hammer!
D-Damn you...
Ugh! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp's Rubber Band of Doom!
Usopp Hammer!
I win! I beat a fishman!
It serves you right!
I can do it, too, if I try!
Did you see that?!
Don't underestimate me,
you bastards!