Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
How can someone like you, with no
damn pride, be a pirate captain?
Happiness
What in the world can you do?
I can defeat you!
That's right, you damn idiot!
If he dies, I'm gonna kill him!
I've got your back!
That's it, Gum-Gum!
Get him, Big Bro Luffy!
You've got this!
You're on the same level!
{Go ahead and babble,
you inferior species!}Go to hell, worm!
Ugh! He's got new teeth!
I'm a shark. New teeth
grow {}in one after another.
And they're sturdier
than the previous ones.
Each and every time!
Whoa!
As many times as I want!
{This is a distinctive quality
that heaven gave us.}The heavens have bestowed this trait to us.
That's amazing!
Are you starting to realize what
a superior race the fishmen are?
Tooth {}& Gum!
Huh?
Stop!
Big Bro Luffy!
A-Arlong...
that hurt.
Wh-Wha...! B-Brother!
Phew.
You rubber punk!
How dare you use my
brother as a shield!
What're you talking about?
You're the one who attacked.
Phew... That sure was scary.
Don't move,
you rubber bastard!
Oh yeah!
I've got a fun idea.
A fun idea?
What in the world will he...?
Does he have some
trick up his sleeve?
Tooth {}& Gum!
There we go!
Idiot,
it's useless for you to keep
destroying my teeth.
You still don't get it?!
B-Big Bro Luffy,
{You surely don't mean
your interesting idea is...}surely you didn't mean
that this is your fun idea.
Look! I've got fangs, too!
S-So he didn't have
a trick up his sleeve?
How long are you going to
keep fooling around?!
The shark bit me!
That's because you're playing around!
I'm not trying to mess around.
Tooth {}& Gum!
Arlong bit him!
How do you like that?
A tooth for a tooth!
You can use my teeth all you want.
You're still stuck with that weak jaw.
Listen up.
A shark's teeth are only
as good as his jaws,
{with a strong jaw that
can bite off the meat!}which tear through flesh!
{Ahh! Big Bro's arm's
gonna get bitten off!}Ahh! Big Bro's gonna lose his arm!
Luffy!
Is his arm okay?
If he backed off even a step,
he would've lost that arm!
I doubt he thought too much about what the fangs'd do to him, though.{Timer's Request: If you can merge this line with line above and make it short, plz do so.}
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Luffy! The sea!
The sea?
There's a shark!
That's Arlong!
What? Did he dive down?
This is serious!
He's twice as powerful in the water.
No one can stop me once
{my
speed accelerates in the water.}I gather speed underwater.
{This is precisely an ability
that is given only to fishmen.}This ability is precisely the kind
bestowed only to fishmen.
Did he run away?
Shark Gone...
Darts!
What was that?!
A torpedo?!
Something flew out of the sea!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Wow, you handled that well.
{But the more you dodge it,
the longer your hell continues.}But the more you dodge,
the more hell you'll get.
Shark Gone Darts!
Wh-What the hell are those
damn shark's bones made of?!
His nose shattered the ground!
Shark Gone Darts!
Hey Luffy, {}you gotta hide!
Arlong went into the sea again!
Big Bro! Please hurry and hide!
He'll target you again!
Get out of there!
N-No.
Don't be stupid! Are you trying
to be a target?! Take cover!
I don't want to! I'll catch him
and break his nose!
Come at me, shark!
You got some nerve.
Or have you realized that running
away is not gonna save you?
Can't you see that you've
gotta hide, Luffy?!
You barely dodged his attacks,
but they all grazed you!
That move will instantly kill
you if you take its full force!
Gum-Gum...
Shield!
What's that stance?
{Surely he isn't going to
stop the attack like that?}He wouldn't try to stop
the attack like that, right?
I have twice the distance
to accelerate this time!
I'll punch through your heart!
Shark {}Gone Darts!
It's a direct hit!
Wait, did he get hit?!
No! He flung himself away!
You're done! That attack
won't work anymore.
Shark {}Gone Darts!
You bastard!
That was just a lucky guess!
This is the final blow!
You won't hit me!
Gum-Gum...
Net!
Fishing! I'm fishing!
And...
Spear!
Whoa!
Hm? Is he dead?
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
{They look the same as the eyes that
sea kings show when they snap.}He looks just like
the sea kings when they attack.
Luffy's last attack must've pissed him off!
{I've never seen Arlong's
eyes like that...}I've never seen Arlong with a look like that.
Inferior human!
What do you think
you're doing to me?!
I'm a fishman!
Boy, was that a shocker!
It didn't hurt,
but he's definitely pissed.
What the heck is that?
Kiribachi!
That's a monster saw!
– Big Bro Luffy!
– Hang in there, Luffy!
Run! Watch out!
The attack is relentless.
He's cornered!
He escaped into the building!
It's the left window on the top floor.
That room is...
There's nowhere left to run.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
What's this room?
It's full of papers.
They're no ordinary papers.
This room is where I make that
girl draw sea charts. It's...
...the survey room!
Nami's room.
These are the sea charts
that Nami drew.
{How many people in this world
can draw such accurate charts?}Across the globe, few could draw charts as accurate as these!
The girl has a gift.
There's nothing as sad and senseless
{as letting a natural-born
talent go to waste.}as letting natural-born talent go to waste.
{Staying here and drawing sea charts
is the greatest happiness for her!}She'll find true happiness
in staying here and drawing charts!
This pen is stained with blood.
Nami's charts are absolutely vital
if I'm to attain world supremacy!
She's going to continue drawing
sea charts! All for my ambition!
{And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...}Once we've learned everything about the world's seas from those charts,
we fishmen will be invincible,
and my empire will span the globe!
This island and the East Blue
are the springboards for that end!
How could you possibly use
her as effectively as that?!
What the...?! Kiribachi...
isn't budging!
What?!
"Use"?!
What's goin' on inside?!
Dammit! What happened,
Big Bro Luffy?!
I can't tell what's going
on up there at all.
Luffy.
What do you take her for?!
She's an inferior creature,
but a smart girl.
If you compare all other humans to sewer rats,
then she's a sassy little cat.
After all, she is adorable.
I'm going to keep on feeding her
and buying {}her the clothes she likes.
She'll have everything
she needs to live.
All she needs to do is keep
drawing charts for me.
She will forever be my tool...
no, {}a part of my crew.
What's that?!
A desk...?
Wh-Whew, it's just a desk.
Man, that scared me. I thought
it was Big Bro Luffy for sure.
Hold on, partner!
Are you sayin' you don't have
faith in Big Bro Luffy's strength?!
Wha...?!
You were scared too, Johnny!
D-Don't be stupid!
I was, uh, you know...
{O-of course I thought it
was that damn Arlong!}I-I naturally thought
it was that damn Arlong!
Huh?! {That sounds kinda
fake if you ask me!}It sounds like you're trying to pull one over on me!
Say what, you jerk?! Of course,
Big Bro Luffy'd never lose!
Luffy?
What do you think you're doing?!
{What in the...?!
There's an awful lot of stuff flying!}What the hell is going on?!
All that random crap is flying about!
Alright! As of today,
this is your room!
Your desk, your pens...
Everything you'll need is here!
Stop that!
The charts!
M-My charts!
You damn brat!
Don't think you can trick me,
drawin' fake charts like that!
Do you have the time to be
drawing crap like this in secret?
Try to fool me again, and I'll drag people from the village one by one
and make you watch as I wring their necks!
They'll meet the same fate as her!
Damn you! I spent eight years
making her draw those!
I invested eight years in those
charts! In my ambition!
Bell-mère-san...
Nojiko...!
This is a pretty intense fight!
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Definitely!
Thank you!
You've gone too far,
you rubber freak!
"Fishmen are great" and...
"sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
I don't know much
about any of that stuff...
but I finally figured out how to save her!
This room is why she
can't leave this place!
{If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!}She doesn't want to be here,
so I'll just destroy it all!
Gum-Gum...
Don't get cocky!
Scum like you could never
bring down Arlong Park!
Shark Gone Cog!
Battle Axe!
L-Look at what that impact
has done to Arlong Park!
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
This is dangerous!
Everyone, get back!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
But Luffy's still inside!
Big Sis!
Luffy! What about Luffy?!
Luffy!
Luffy.
Oww!
What's all this damn noise?
Luffy.
Arlong Park... collapsed!
Big Bro.
What the hell happened inside?
Who won?!
Given all this debris,
don't tell me it was...
Luffy...
Luffy!
Big Bro!
Is he okay?!
Nami!
You're one of us!
I know!