Video Editing
Meggo
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Zenef
Ravenfire
arch1t3cht
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Zenef
Ravenfire
arch1t3cht
His final words lured all sorts
of adventurers to the sea.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
arch1t3cht
My treasure?
It's yours... if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
JT-421
Translation
Gaijin
Everything is right where I left it!
Raws
Df68
Now pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
jyuu
shin
ba
n
nan
te
jyuu
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Storm
What's the big idea?!
If we invite the pirates aboard,
they'll take over the entire restaurant!
That's only if they have
the will to fight.
Isn't that right,
you Grand Line washout?
N-No way.
Don Krieg failed on the Grand Line?
Even the most powerful man
in the East Blue
couldn't make it
with a fleet of 50 pirate ships?!
The Grand Line?
You're Blaze Leg Zeff.
You're alive.
You were a cook and a captain...
A pirate unlike any other.
I'm alive. So what?
It's none of your concern.
As you can see,
I spend my days as a chef now.
It sounds better
when you say it like that.
As I see it, you're not just
passing time as a cook.
I doubt you could survive
as anything but a cook.
Blaze Leg Zeff
was known as a master of kicks
who never used his hands in a fight.
His mighty legs were said
to shatter bedrock
and even leave their mark in steel.
"Blaze Leg" came from your boots
looking like a searing fire,
stained in the blood of those
you kicked into submission.
But it looks like you've lost
one of your esteemed legs.
Seems the rumors were true.
A stroke of bad luck doomed you
to an accident at sea.
I suppose losing a leg would mean
you lost the ability to fight.
I don't give a damn about fighting.
I may have lost a leg, but I can cook
so long as I have these two hands.
You need to get
to the damn point already.
Blaze Leg Zeff,
you once sailed the Grand Line
and returned unscathed.
You must have the ship's log
from that year-long voyage.
Hand it over!
Wow, Boss Man!
You sailed the Grand Line too?!
A lifetime ago.
The ship's log?
Sure, I've got it.
But there's no way in hell
I'm giving it to you.
That ship's log is the pride
of all those who sailed with me.
The likes of you couldn't handle it.
Then I'll just have to take it!
I admit the Grand Line
got the better of me.
But even in defeat,
the indomitable Don Krieg
is plenty capable of crossing
even the most treacherous seas.
I had the men. I had the ambition.
The only thing I lacked
was information.
I just didn't know what to expect.
I will have that ship's log.
With it, I will reassemble
my pirate fleet, seize the One Piece,
and rise to the top
of this Great Pirate Era!
Wait just a minute.
I'm going to be the pirate king!
Cabin Boy?!
Hey, back down, Cabin Boy!
You're no match for him!
I can't back down. Not about this.
Did you say something, kid?
We can pretend
I didn't hear you say that.
No need to pretend.
I'm only saying what'll happen.
This ain't a game, boy.
You're right.
I will conquer the Grand Line.
You're taking it too lightly, punk!
Putting aside our lack of intel,
we lasted only seven days
with 5,000 of us on that devilish sea!
A child like you
doesn't stand a chance!
S-Seven days?
The Krieg Pirates lasted
only seven days?!
What the hell happened to them?!
I'm sorry, but I hate it
when people joke around like this.
If you persist with your claim,
I'll just crush you right here and now.
If you can.
Perfect.
As you wish.
I'll be sending you to the afterlife.
You gonna fight, Luffy?
Need some help?
I-I'd also let you
fight him yourself, though.
Zoro? Usopp?
I didn't know you were here!
I'm fine.
Just watch from there.
O-Okay.
Are those your men?
That's a pretty small crew
you got there!
What are you talking about?!
We have two more!
Hey, don't go counting me in!
I'll deal with you later.
I'll go feed my men first.
Anyone who wants to live
needs to clear out before I get back.
I'm only after your log and this ship.
If you still want
to throw your life away,
I can spare the time
to bury you at sea!
Make your choice.
I'm so sorry, Sanji-san.
I had no idea he'd go this far.
You don't need to apologize, grunt.
Every cook here
did what they thought was right.
That's all there is to it.
Chef Zeff!
You're not seriously taking
Sanji's side in this, are you?
That's right!
It's his fault this happened!
He's trying to destroy
your precious restaurant!
Shut up, pea-brains!
Have you ever been so hungry
that you thought you'd die?!
Do you know the terror
of running out of food and water
on this vast ocean?!
Can you comprehend such suffering?!
Huh? Wh-What do you mean,
Chef Zeff?!
What sets Sanji apart
from the rest of you
is that he knows exactly what I mean.
What's that about?
What does Sanji know?
If all you're going to do
is bitch and moan,
crawl out the back door and get lost!
I'll stay and fight!
I'm too pissed off
to let myself get whupped like that!
Me too!
This is where I work!
I got nowhere else to go.
What are you doing?!
You saw what the don's capable of!
Hey, Gin.
Let me tell you something.
My duty as a cook is to feed
those who are hungry.
That said...
when those looters turn on me
with full bellies.
I'll beat the hell outta them,
even if they're in your crew.
That goes for you too.
Just try to take this restaurant,
and I'll kill you without a second thought.
Understood?
Sanji, I can't believe you'd kill him
after keeping him alive.
Shut up, you crappy cook!
Look at that!
He's pretty cool, huh?!
Whatever. I don't care about him.
We gotta get outta here!
Settle down!
Did you see Krieg?
He's in bad shape.
Gin, you said you don't know anything
about the Grand Line, didn't you?
You've been there, right?!
It's true;
the Grand Line is a mystery to me.
What we saw on our seventh day
on the Grand Line
might have been a dream,
or it might have been real.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
It was unbelievable!
How could a lone man...
destroy a fleet of 50 ships?!
What?!
It happened out of nowhere.
Before we even realized he was there,
the ships began to sink,
one after another.
If we hadn't been lucky enough
to encounter that storm,
our flagship would have met
the same fate.
I don't know how many
of our ships survived.
It's just too horrible
to believe it was real.
I want to forget what happened!
I want to forget that man
how he could seemingly kill
with just a glance
with that hawk-like glare!
Could it be?!
There's no mistaking it.
That must be the man
known as Hawk Eye.
Just telling us that his eyes
were like those of a hawk
wouldn't be proof in itself.
But the fact that he could do
something so horrendous
is plenty of evidence that it's him.
The hawk-eyed man!
Huh? Do you know him, Zoro?
Yeah.
It's who I've been looking for.
That guy must have really had
a grudge against your crew.
I'd never seen him before!
Maybe you woke him
from a nap or something.
Don't be ridiculous!
Who the hell would
smash a fleet over that?!
Don't get so worked up.
I'm just saying...
that sort of thing is possible
in the Grand Line.
What kind of place is that?!
It means anything could happen.
Hey Luffy, we shouldn't
go somewhere like that!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy?
Whoa, that's so freakin' cool!
I knew it had to be crazy there!
At least acknowledge
how dangerous it is!
Well, that settles it.
My only goal at this point
is the Grand Line.
That man... The Grand Line's
where I'm going to find him!
Are you nuts?
You're the type
to charge in and die first.
You're right,
but saying I'm nuts is going too far.
I threw my life away when I decided
to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Only one person can call me nuts,
and that person is me!
Yeah, the same goes for me too!
Yeah, me too! I'm a man of the sea!
You're lying.
How ridiculous.
Hey, hey.
Do you numbskulls have any idea
what's going on here?!
Outside this restaurant
is a massive galleon
from Pirate Commodore
Don Krieg's fleet!
You can build your castles in the sky
when the battle is over!
We're saved!
I'm so glad we're gonna live!
It's like I'm dreaming!
We're free from that nightmare!
We made it back alive
from the Pirate Graveyard!
Heh, that's right.
We can once again turn
our sights on the Grand Line.
Huh? What's with those looks?
W-We're going back there?!
Anybody else have any objections?
First,
we'll abandon this irreparable wreck
and take over the restaurant.
It's staffed by a gang
of thuggish cooks.
They've got nothing on us.
Attack!
They're coming!
I can hear them yelling!
Hold them off!
This ship is our restaurant!
Make way, you scum!
What was that?!
What happened?!
Don Krieg!
Our flagship was...
sliced in half!
Sliced in half?! Did I hear that right?!
Our massive galleon?!
How could...
something so preposterous happen?!
Weigh anchor!
It'll bring the whole ship down!
Yes, sir!
Not good!
Nami, Yosaku, and Johnny
are on the ship out front!
Dammit!
We're probably already too late!
Big Bro!
Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you guys okay?
Where's the ship?! It's gone!
What happened to Nami?!
Well... I'm sorry, Big Bro!
She's already gone!
See ya!
Tell Luffy and his crew...
Big Sis Nami...
See you again if our paths cross!"
She took all the treasure and ran!
What the hell?!
Hm?
That man...
What'd you say?!
Nami took the Going Merry and ran?!
What the hell is she doing?!