Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Meggo
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
obtained everything the world has to offer.
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
PhosCity
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
PhosCity
What he said in his final moments
drove countless souls to the seas.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Gab
Typesetting
PhosCity
Gab
You want my treasure? Go ahead.
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit
Gab
Gordingus
Poppy
Westfal
Zenef
AphantasticRabbit
Gab
Gordingus
Poppy
Westfal
Zenef
Translation
Chloelyy
Funimation
PamkinPinguin
rangicus
Chloelyy
Funimation
PamkinPinguin
rangicus
Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
Raws
df68
People set their sights on the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams.
The world has truly entered
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
shin
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
The Fourth
My hat! My straw hat!
It's right there.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Here it is.
Rise and shine.
Oh? Are those guys still...?
They left...
thanks to you.
Me?
Gin said, "I'll see you again
on the Grand Line."
Gin said that...
to you?
He said it to you!
{Speaking of which,
since I drove them away, - OG}Speaking of which,
since I drove them off,
{today is my last day
to do chores, right? - OG}today is my last day
doing chores, right?
Congrats.
Which means that you'll...
...not be going with you!
I won't become a pirate.
I'll keep working here as a cook
until I get that old fart
to acknowledge my skills.
I get it. I give up.
Your hand hasn't given up yet!
I can't leave here when every
last one of them is unreliable.
But... I am hoping
to head out someday...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Hey...
have you heard of the All Blue?!
Nope.
You've seriously never heard of it?!
That sea itself is a miracle!
In that sea...
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
{Fish from all those four seas
live in that sea! - OG}Fish from all four corners
of the world swim there!
To us cooks, it's a dreamlike paradise!
{That's what the Grand Line is like!
So, have you heard... - OG}{That's what the Grand Line is like!
So, you've never...? - Z/PP}I mean, that's the Grand Line
for you. So, you've never...?
He still lights up
when he talks about it...
What a goofball.{Z- feels more endearing than normal, so I wanted something softer. Maybe there are other suggestions out there to help craft this line.}
Time to eat, guys!
Thank goodness...
Employee Dining Room
2nd Floor, Baratie
We can finally eat!
Food! Food! Food!
Hey, where are we supposed to sit?
Where's our food?
Seats are all taken.
Sit on the floor and eat.
No seats?
How is that even possible?!
This is a restaurant!
Well, whatever...
They're acting kinda weird...
What's new?
Hey! Who prepared
the soup this morning?!
Hey, that was all me!
Pretty good, right?!
I took extra care in making it today!
I can't eat a vile soup like this!
This is just slop!
Hey... is human food not
to your liking, you damn tanuki?
It's an art to make
something this bad.
It makes me sick to my stomach!
Sorry, but I'd stake my
reputation on this soup.
{There's something wrong
with your taste buds! - OG}{There's just something wrong
with your taste buds! - Z}You should go and get
your taste buds checked.
Ugh! This is disgusting!
I can't eat it!
Right, guys?!
It's inedible!
This soup is revolting!
I can't eat soup like this!
This is terrible! Someone,
give me some water!
{What do you think you're doing,
you bastards?! - OG}Who are you bastards trying to fool?!
You're a sham of a sous-chef,
just so you know.
{Your time has come and gone. - Z- another that needs serious TL since calling someone an old-timer is usually referring to their age.}You've gotten stale!
{We're sick and tired of you
settling matters with violence! - OG}{The way you settle matters
with violence has gotten old. - Z}We're tired of you solving
every problem with your feet.
If the food's bad,
we'll tell you it's bad!
Say what...?!
We're seafaring cooks.
We don't waste even a drop of soup.
{ Owner!
Owner! - OG} Chef Zeff!
Chef Zeff!
Old fart...!
{What is this damn nasty soup?
It's like sludge! - OG}{Z- sludge doesn't feel right since that implies a thicker substance... but it could be justified as an insult to Sanji's very clear broth.}What is this vile scum of a soup?!
If we serve something like this,
we'll go out of business!
Knock it off, you old fart!
{Just how is this soup
different from yours?! Tell me! - OG}Just how is my soup different
from yours?! Tell me!
You think this soup
compares to mine?!
Don't flatter yourself!
Chef Zeff punched him...
Instead of kicking him?
{It'll be a billion years before you can give me a lecture on cooking, little eggplant! - OG}It's a billion years too early for you
to lecture me on cooking, little eggplant!
{I'm a man who has cooked
on seas around the world. - OG}I'm a man who has cooked
on seas across the world.
Dammit!
This soup is pretty tasty, you know...
We know that.
Huh?
{Sanji's cooking skills
are recognized by everyone here. - OG}Everyone here knows
what a fantastic cook Sanji is.
It's not bad at all.
Yeah, this soup is exquisitely made.
Boy, that was scary...
He seriously snapped.
He sure did.
But that idiot won't listen
unless we go this far...
Say, kid...
You were saying that you wanted
a cook for your ship, right?
{This isn't a favor that I'd like
to ask of you or anything, - OG}I'm not asking you a favor or anything,
but would you take that
little eggplant with you...
to the Grand Line?
The Grand Line...
is his dream.
{Man, Owner, you really made us
put on quite a show. - OG}Chef Zeff, you made us
put on a hell of a show.
{I was worried that he might figure
it out because of your bad acting. - OG}I thought for sure he'd figure it out
because of your bad acting.
You were the bad actor here.{Chloe - This TL is slightly inaccurate: it's not really a 'too' sort of line at all and Patty is more so just saying roughly "It was you putting up the horrible performance" in a very lighthearted, joking and teasing manner.}
I'll have another bowl!
Me, too!
I can hear everything,
you damn idiots...
So what do you say, kid?
No.
What?!
I thought you wanted
a cook for your ship.
Or are you saying that
he's not good enough for you?
{He's good enough, alright.
I do want him to come with me. - OG}It's not that he isn't good enough.
I really do want him to come with me.
{But he says that he wants
to continue working here as a cook. - OG}But he says that he wants to
keep working here as a cook.
{Even if you guys ask me
to take him with me, I can't. - OG}Even if you guys ask me
to take him, I can't.
So you're saying that you can't agree
to it until he tells you so himself, huh?
Exactly. More, please!
Well... fair enough.
{But who knows if that twisted
damn brat can just say he'll go... - OG}But who knows if that screwed-up
brat can just say that he'll go...
{But who knows if that twisted
damn brat can just say he'll go... - OG}But who knows if that screwed-up
brat can just say that he'll go...
{There's no way he can, since
he's an idiot through and through... - OG}I wouldn't hold your breath
for a stubborn idiot like that.
More, please!
Dammit...!
Sanji!
What is he? A fishman?
{He came all the way from
the Fishman Island to eat our dishes? - OG}He came from Fishman Island
to try our cuisine?
Idiot! It's a human and a panda shark!
What's going on?
Oh! It's Yosaku!
Ah... Big Bro Luffy!
{Why are you alone?
Where're the others? - OG}You're all by yourself?
Where's everyone else?
Did you find Nami?
We didn't actually catch up to her...
{but from the direction Big Sis Nami was heading, we figured out roughly where she was going. - OG}but based on Big Sis Nami's heading,
we could guess her destination.
We can bring her back, then.
The thing is...
{If what we're thinking is right,
her destination is a crazy place... - OG}if we're right about this, then she's
headed straight for trouble.
In any case, we need
your help, Big Bro Luffy.
Please come with me!
{Okay! I don't really get it, but got it.
I'll come with you. - OG}Alright! I don't really get it,
but okay. Let's go!
Wait!
We both have foolish dreams.
{In order to achieve my goal,
the All Blue... - OG}To achieve my goal
to find the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah.
I'll come along on your journey
to become King of the Pirates!
Huh?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!
Alright!
Congratulations, Big Bro Luffy!
Yeah!
Yay! Yay!
We got a cook! We'll have good food!
That's what's happening, everyone.
Good food! Good food!
Sorry for causing you
all sorts of trouble.
You're pissin' me off...
{I wanted to kick you out
from here myself. - OG}I wanted to kick you
out of here myself.
{And then you just
casually decide like that? - Z}And then you casually
decide just like that?
{Sorry for making you resort
to bad acting. - OG}Sorry for making you show off
your crappy acting skills.
You knew?!
I could hear you in there...
You're all so stupid.
We're what...?!
{That is to say, you're willing to go
that far to kick me out, huh, - OG}So that means you're willing to go
that far to kick me out,
huh, you old fart?!
Why do you always talk like
such a disrespectful turd?!
That's right, little eggplant!
I couldn't care less for kids, anyway!
{Not a single day passed where I didn't regret letting a useless one live, you damn brat. - OG}Not a single day went by where I didn't
regret letting such a useless brat live.
That makes this easier, you old fart!
{Enjoy the rest of your life
to the utmost. - OG}Savor the rest of
your life to the fullest!
{This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it? - OG}Is it okay for us to use
such a nice ship?
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
You still need more?!
Yeah. Give me more meat.
Just how many days
will you be at sea?
Don't know...
Whoa!
Old fart, is this the Sea Restaurant?
m 271 292 l 273 287 276 283 287 278 1145 23 1157 20 1164 19 1162 756 1159 759 267 943
{Baratie Employee Guidelines1. Serving customers! That is "love"!And "love" means "restaurant"!2. Motto! Motto! It's my service motto!3. Service is about pleasant greetings!4. The customer is king!}fillerfilBaratie Employee Guidelines
fillerf1. Serving customers equals love,
fillerfiland love equals restaurant!
file2. Motto! Motto!
fillerfilIt's my service motto!
ll3. A pleasant greeting equals service!
4. The customer is king!
m 271 292 l 273 287 276 283 287 278 1145 23 1157 20 1164 19 1162 756 1159 759 267 943
For example, Sanji...
Yeah?
Be they master criminals
or escaped convicts,
{if these damn bastards
badly want to eat and find their way to this restaurant, - OG}if these damn bastards are starving
and find their way to this restaurant,
{there may be a point
in our continuing to fight - OG}that would give us reason
enough to keep fighting,
wouldn't you say?
Yeah!
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Ouch...
Honestly...
{You peeled the skin too thick,
little eggplant! - OG}Thinner peels, little eggplant!
That really hurt!
{When someone's cooking seriously,
you should just watch quietly! - OG}When someone's focused on
their cooking, just shut up and watch!
{What?! Don't get smart,
you little eggplant! - OG}What?! Don't get smart
with me, you little eggplant!
I'm not a little eggplant!
You old fart!
Try this.
Did you make it by yourself?
Yeah.
How is it?
{Cripes, this is damn nasty,
you little eggplant! - OG}Disgusting!
you little eggplant! - OG}This is inedible, you little eggplant!
You old fart!
Big Bro Cook sure is taking his time...
Yeah...
This is a long time coming!
Get ready, Sanji!
{There's no way
you guys can defeat him. - OG}You guys will never kick his ass.
Let's go.
Shouldn't you say goodbye?
It's fine.
Sanji!
Keep your feet dry.
Chef Zeff!
{Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me over all these years! - OG}Thank you for every damn thing
you've done for me all these years!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for as long as I live!
You asshole!
I'll miss you, dammit!
I'm gonna miss you!
I'll miss you!
You're making me cry, dammit!{Z - just saying "I feel sad" doesn't feel right in the context of manly men seeing each other off. They'll try their best to hide the emotions even if they're coming through.}
You're all idiots!
Men should part without a word.
Let's go! Set sail!
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
{As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself,}If your conviction is such
that you no longer fear death...
you'll surely find...
the All Blue.
Guys, customers are
gonna show up soon!
Get to work already!