Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Gigglebot
Ninja
Timing
PhosCity
DraSleek
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Inherited will...
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
They cannot be stopped.
Translation
DemonRin
Funimation
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
shin
shin
eve
in
shin
stuck
stuck
TIKKU
TIKKU
dr
ama
TIKKU
land!
land!
you,
you,
ka
ra
you,
land!
land!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Tin Plate Wapol
Guys! Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
To the village of warriors!
Yeah! Okay!
Gi-Gi-Giants! Gia-Giants!
Elbaf-baf! Elbaf-baf!
Everyone's huge
'cause they're giants!
They're huge! They're huge!
They're huge!
They sure are lively today...
{I'm suddenly exhausted after
everything that's happened. - OG}Suddenly, I'm pretty worn out
after all that's happened...
{Vivi. Could you watch
this compass for me? - OG}Vivi... could you keep an eye
on the needle for me?
Sure.
Now you can finally...
return to Arabasta.
{Well, assuming we can make
it there safely, of course... - OG}That is, assuming we can
avoid trouble along the way.
Yes. It's time I returned!
After all, I am...
...the only one who can
save the kingdom, Princess!
{The kingyour fatherno longer
has sway with the people now. - OG}The kingyour fatherno longer
holds sway over his people.
{Our only hope of stopping
this uprising now - OG}Our only hope to stem
the tide of rebellion is for the country
{is for you to tell the people
the truth directly! - OG}to hear the truth directly from you.
So, no matter the cost,
you must not die!
{You must live on, even if
it means losing those near to you - OG}If it means you survive,
then sacrifice those closest to you
or betray them to your enemies!
It will be agony!
{Princess Vivi!
Are you prepared not to die? - OG}Princess Vivi! Are you
resolved to stay alive?
I will stay alive
and return to Arabasta.
No need to push
yourself so hard, Vivi.
You have me!
{Today's relaxing sweets.
How about some petit fours? - OG}Today's sweets will put you
right at ease. Petit fours?
{For drinks, you have
your choice of coffee or tea. - OG}And to drink, would you
like coffee or tea?
Sanji!
Yours is in the kitchen!
Alright!
I got there first!
2,603...
2,604...
2,605...
2,606...!
If only I'd been able
to cut through that wax...
we would've escaped so much sooner.
I'm weak...
I need to get stronger...
{I need to be able to cut up
stuff like that from any stance! - OG}{and obtain the power
to cut even steel! - OG}and get to where I can
cut through stuff like that with ease!
Sandy Island
Kingdom of Arabasta
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
The Swanda is ready to set sail!
Okay, okay! Dial it down a notch!
Honestly! What does any of this
have to do with me?!
{Mr. 3 is nothing but bulky garbage!
You guys go toss him out! - OG}Mr. 3 is a waste of space!
You guys go finish him off!
W-We can't!
{We wouldn't stand a chance,
even if we ganged up on him! - OG}Even all of us together
wouldn't stand a chance!
P-Please! It's the boss' orders!
Un, deux, trois...
"Bon Kurei"
What's "four" again?
Zero baby is so high maintenance...
Vivi... Sorry. I think I'm gonna...
go lie down.
No problem, Nami!
I'll keep an eye on our heading.
You should get some rest.
Are you all right?!
Everyone, come here! It's urgent!
Huh? What's up, Vivi?
Nami has a terrible fever!
Say what?! Nami has a what?!
Is Nami gonna die? Is she, Vivi?
It's most likely the climate.
{One of the obstacles all sailors
who enter the Grand Line run into - OG}Illness caused by abnormal weather
is a well-known obstacle
for those new to the Grand Line.
There are countless stories
of the toughest, most infamous pirates
suddenly dying from it.
If left untreated,
even the slightest chill can be fatal.
Nami!
{Is there anyone on this ship with
any medical knowledge at all? - OG}Does someone on the ship have
any kind of medical training?
{But eating meat makes
sickness go away! Right, Sanji? - OG}{Eating meat makes you feel better!
Right, Sanji? - OG}Well, she'll feel better once
she eats some meat! Right, Sanji?
{I can make some basic food
meant for sick people, - OG}Y'know, I can think of a few meals
meant to nurse sick people.
{but that's entirely in
"nursing" territory. There's no guarantee
it'd make her better... - OG}But nursing isn't my expertise,
so there's no telling if it would help.
{Besides, I normally put
100 times more care... - OG}Even so, I put 100 times more care
into Nami and Vivi's meals
than I do yours.
To balance their diet, I only serve them
fresh meat and vegetables.
And I give all the rotting stuff...
to you guys.
Hey, now!
It tastes great, though!
My point is, as long as
I'm this ship's cook,
{there'll be no problems whatsoever
in terms of getting a balanced diet. - OG}I will always guarantee
you get a balanced diet.
{But there are different kinds
of meals for sick people. - OG}But sick people
require specific meals.
What does she need,
and for which symptoms?
I can't make that call.
Then feed her everything!
{She's sick because she doesn't
have the energy for that! - OG}Going overboard like that
is bound to make her sicker!
{40 degrees?!
Her fever's gone up again! - OG}I-It's at 40 degrees?!
Her fever's gone up!
{There'll be doctors when we
get to Arabasta, right?!}There are doctors in Arabasta, right?!
How long till we arrive, Vivi?
A week maybe,
but it might be too late by then.
Is being sick that bad?
Dunno. Never been sick.
Who in the world are you guys?!
Of course it's bad!
Fevers of 40 degrees
don't happen every day!
Her life may very well be at stake.
Nami's gonna die?!
Don't die, Nami!
Settle down! Be quiet!
Let's find a doctor to help Nami!
Okay! Just calm down!
{You're going to make
her illness even worse! - OG}You'll make her worse!
No...
Nami?
Oh! She's all better!
Get real!
In my desk drawer...
there's a newspaper.
No change in course...
N-No!
This can't be!
Hey. What is it?
Is it about Arabasta, Vivi?
{300,000 royal soldiers
- defected to the Resistance... - OG}My kingdom just saw 300,000 of
the Royal Army defect to the Rebellion.
It all started as a cold war
{with 600,000 royal soldiers and
400,000 Resistance soldiers... - OG}with the 600,000 Royal Army soldiers
deterring the 400,000 rebels.
But this changes everything!
{The uprising in Arabasta is finally
going to get serious now... - OG}The tensions in Arabasta are
only going to intensify from here on.
That paper's from three days ago.
{I'm sorry...
We can't change our speed, - OG}I'm sorry...
We can only go so fast.
{so I didn't want to worry you
by showing you that...}I thought if you saw this
you'd only worry...
Understand, Luffy?
Things look pretty bad!
{Whew, that got through to
you more than I expected... - OG}Whew, you got the gist of it.
But you still need to see a doctor!
I'm fine... That thermometer
must be broken.
Nobody gets
a temperature of 40 degrees...
{It's probably just
sunstroke or something... - OG}It's most likely sunstroke.
{We don't need a doctor.
I'll get better on my own... - OG}{No time for doctors,
so I'll get better on my own. - OG}I don't need a doctor.
I'll get better on my own.
For now, let's head
straight for Arabasta as planned!
Thanks for worrying about me.
Oh! She's better now?
{You idiot/jackass.
She's just acting tough. - OG}Don't be stupid. It's just a front.
{At this rate, so much blood will
be shed throughout the kingdom. - OG}At this rate, blood will flow
through the kingdom's streets.
It'll be an all-out war.
If I don't prevent that,
the Kingdom of Arabasta will be finished.
Crocodile will take over!
{No! It isn't enough
to simply get back alive! - OG}It's not enough...
to simply get back alive!
I must expedite my return!
{If I don't make it in time, a million citizens will
kill themselves pointlessly! - OG}A moment wasted means a million citizens
will senselessly kill each other!
There's a million people?!
What an immense burden
you're carrying, Vivi.
{Urgh! What were you
watching all this time?! - OG}C'mon! Were you even
paying attention up here?!
{Whad'ya talking about?
The ship's been going straight. - OG}Whad'ya mean?
The ship's going straight.
Yeah, straight at a right angle!
You need to watch the needle!
{I don't need to.
I was watching that big cloud there. - OG}That wasn't necessary.
I was watching that big cloud there.
Clouds move and change shape!
Oh, man, my head's killing me...
So then leave this to me
and go to bed!
I'm here because
I can't leave this to you!
The air's different.
{The air? It's been nice weather
this whole time. - OG}The air? The weather's been
nice this whole time.
Forget it! Just get the others!
{Hey! Get out here, you guys!
Got work to do! - OG}Hey! Get out here, you guys!
We've got work to do!
What?
{Huh? Hard to feel motivated
when you're the one giving the orders. - OG}Huh? Hard to feel motivated
when it's you giving the orders.
Just shut up and move!
{Hoist the sails and catch
the port side wind! - OG}Hoist the sails
and catch the wind aport!
Everything okay, Nami?
The waves are quiet,
and the weather's nice.
The wind...
The wind?
{An immense wind...
is coming directly this way... - OG}The wind is picking up
and heading directly toward us.
I think th
What?
Hot!
You're burning up! Yeah,
stay inside until we find a doctor!
Mind your own business!
This is my normal temperature!
Quit being dumb and man the ropes!
{Nami-san, I know you're saying
that for Vivi-chan, but if you push too hard... - OG}Nami, I get that this is
for Vivi's sake, but if you overdo it...
I told you, I'm fine!
{Hey, Nami.
- I think you really should... - OG}C'mon, Nami! You really ought to
Just hurry it up and turn the ship!
But...
what could it be?
{It seems a little different
than a storm... - OG}This is a bit different from a storm.
I need to hurry... back to Arabasta.
Everyone, I need a favor!
{I know it's not my place to ask
this as a passenger on your ship, - OG}As a passenger on your ship,
I know I have no right to ask this,
{but my homeland is
in a terrible state now, - OG}but my homeland is
on the brink of disaster.{I love your wording but she doesn't actually say "War" so I think this is a good middle ground}
So we need to expedite our trip!
We can't waste even a single minute!
{So I want this ship to head for
Arabasta at its fastest speed! - OG}You must take me to Arabasta
at this ship's top speed!
Of course!
That's what we promised!
{So let's find an island
with a doctor on it right away! - OG}{That said, let's find an island
with a doctor right away! - OG}So let's find an island
with a doctor right away!
{Let's cure Nami-san as quickly as
possible and then go to Arabasta! - OG}The sooner we cure Nami,
the sooner we get to Arabasta!
That's this ship's top speed, right?!
Yeah! We can't go
any faster than that!
Are you sure?
{As their princess, you should be
worried about those million citizens. - OG}Shouldn't a princess be more worried
about her one million citizens?
{That's right! So we need to hurry
and cure Nami-san's illness! - OG}You're right! All the more reason
to hurry and cure Nami!
Well said, Vivi!
I've fallen for you all over again!
You've got spirit.
Thanks...
Don't overexert yourself, Nami!
{Sorry, Vivi... I think...
I am kind of... in trouble... - OG}Sorry, Vivi. Y'know...
I might be... in trouble.
Nami! Hang in there!
What the heck is that?!
It's a cyclone!
It's huge!
W-Wait! That's the direction
{That's the direction our ship
was just headed in! - OG}That's the direction our ship
was just going!
{It would've been a direct hit
had we kept going straight! - OG}We would've hit it head-on
had we kept our original heading!
Yikes! We just barely missed it!
Incredible!
Grand Line cyclones are said
to be impossible to predict!
Yet, she...
{She doesn't predict weather
based on standard theory... - OG}She doesn't predict weather
based on prevailing theory.
It's almost as if she's detecting
the weather with her body!
This navigator is one of a kind!
Alright! Let's hurry, then!
Let's go find us a doctor!
Yeah!
The Next Day
{What do we do, Vivi-chan?!
Nami-san's fever won't go down! - OG}What do we do, Vivi?!
Nami's fever won't break!
Sanji! Karoo!
I asked you to stop freaking out!
See any doctors?!
You actually expect him to, moron?
{Hey, guys. Do you think
people can stand on the ocean? - OG}Hey, guys. Ever heard of people
who could stand on the ocean?
Can people stand on the ocean?
{C'mon, Zoro.
What kind of question is that? - OG}C'mon, Zoro.
Is this some kind of riddle?
Then... what's that?
What's what?
Huh?
Hi. It sure is chilly today.
Yeah! It is chilly today!
Y-Yeah! Chilly, chilly!
Today's very chilly!
Really?
Increase buoyancy!
Yes, sir!
What's that?! A watermelon?!
Why are we shaking?!
{Hold steady the rudder! If anything
happens to Nami-san, I'll gut you all! - OG}Steady the rudder! If anything
happens to Nami, I'll gut you all!
This thing can't actually be... a ship?!
Crap! A p-pirate ship!
S-So cool!
Just when we're in a hurry...
{Did our jumbo underwater raid ship,
the Bliking, surprise you?! - OG}Surprised?! It's our jumbo
submersible raid ship, the Bliking!
Vivi! Take over!
Okay!
Hey! What's going on?!
So? What's going on?
The ship's under attack.
Well, I had figured as much
from the looks of things.
{Are you really pirates?
You're strange. - OG}Are you really pirates?
This can't be right.
Is it just the four of you?
"Tin Plate" Wapol
Bliking Pirates
I find it hard to believe...
that a pirate group would only have four people.
{What is that guy?!
He even ate the knife! - OG}What is that guy?!
He even ate the knife!
Just watching hurts!
{Well, no matter.
I'll start by asking this... - OG}Well, no matter.
First, a question for you.
We want to go
to the Kingdom of Drum.
Do you happen to have
an eternal pose or a log pose?
Nope. Never even heard of the place.
Hey, if that's everything,
then get outta here!
We're in a hurry!
We don't have time to mess with you!
Don't rush life like that.
So you don't have either one, oh well.
{For now, I'll take your
treasure and this ship. - OG}{Since I'm here, I'll take your
treasure and this ship. - OG}In that case, I'll take
your treasure and your ship.
What?!
But first, I'm feeling a bit hungry!
What is this guy?!
Get your mouth off our ship!
Hold it right there!
The great Wapol is currently eating!
Shut up!
Damn that bastard! Fire!
Should've done that from the start...
Oh? We can have at 'em?
No, wait! We can discuss this!
Look what they started.
They're fools rushing to their deaths!
Gunfire?!
Karoo! Watch Nami!
I'll be right back!
Don't bite off
more than you can chew!
Rception!
All bark and no bite.
W-Wapol, sir! These guys are...!
Are you still eating it?!
Say, this ship doesn't taste half bad.
Hey, you!
Fool! You're no match
for the great Wapol!
{Time to get eaten by the power
of the Munch Munch Fruit! - OG}His Munch-Munch Fruit power
will eat you whole!
Luffy!
Wh-What is this?!
Oh, Vivi, is everything
okay with Nami?
Huh?
This guy's hard to chew on!
Why, you!
Go flying!
Wapol...?{Z- still trying to keep it a secret that he's the former king of drum, so localizing this -sama will be tough.}
{Hey, this is bad!
Wapol-sama was sent flying! - OG}Hey, this is really bad!
He sent the great Wapol flying!
{This is terrible!
Wapol-sama is unable to swim! - OG}This is a disaster!
The great Wapol isn't able to swim!
{He will surely perish and drown in the sea if we don't rescue him before he sinks! - OG}He will surely drown and perish in the sea
if he sinks before we can retrieve him!
This isn't over, you!
We'll make you pay for this!
Remember us!
You're gonna pay!
Please, remember us! Please!
J-Just now, what was all that?
So, I guess his name is Wapol?
Doesn't matter. Don't sweat it.
He's a moron.
Let's just forget about him.
Where have I seen him before?
{Won' her fever go down
if we dump water on her? - OG}Will her fever go down
if we dump water on her?
You dumbass!
This isn't good. The sun's
about to set for today, Vivi.
Yes... You're right.
Let's drop anchor somewhere.
{We can't navigate at night
without Nami-san's instructions. - OG}We can't sail at night
without Nami's navigation.
True.
Brr, it's cold...
Almost a full moon, huh?
Brr! Oh, crap, I fell asleep!
You're up early, Usopp!
I can't just sit around doing nothing!
We gotta get out of this jam
as quickly as possible!
Yeah. Good point.
{Say, doesn't this area seem
kind of calm and cold? - OG}Say, isn't this area
unusually calm and cold?
Yeah, sudden, strange calms...
{I guess that's another thing that
happens in the erratic Grand Line. - OG}I guess that's another
erratic quirk of the Grand Line.
That's not necessarily the case.
{It's probably proof
that an island is nearby. - OG}This is likely proof of a nearby island.
Sanji, can you carefully
scan the horizon?
Vivi?
A winter island is nearby.
I'm certain of it.
Winter island?
Ow!
{Climatically there are four basic
types of islands in the Grand Line. - OG}Climate-wise, the Grand Line
has four basic island types:
{Summer islands, spring islands,
autumn islands, and winter islands... - OG}Summer isles, spring isles,
autumn isles, and winter isles.
{And each one generally
has four seasons of its own. - OG}In addition, each one generally
has four seasons of its own.
Summery Summer            Wintery Winter
Summer Island Spring Island Autumn Island Winter Island
On the Grand Line, you contend
with no fewer than sixteen seasons.
{you must conquer from summer island
summer to winter island winter. - OG}There are summer island summers
and even winter island winters.
Of course, there are many exceptions
and unknown climates.
I get it.
{The Grand Line has lots of
different islands one after the other, - OG}The Grand Line consists
of strings of various islands,
{and that's why the seas between
them have such unstable weather. - OOG}and weather is adversely affected
on the seas between them.
That's right.
{Which is why stable
weather means an island is nearby. - OG}So when the weather stabilizes,
you're near an island.
You're right! There it is!
We found an island!
An island?!
Oh! An island! We found an island!
{Hey, Nami! Good for you!
There's an island! You can get better! - OG}Hey, Nami! Great news!
It's an island! You'll get better!
There's an island! An island! Island!
Island! Island! Island! Island!
Just go look already. I'll watch her.
Island! Island!
An island!
White! So white! Has to be snow!
A snow island, huh?!
{Hey, Luffy! Just so you know,
we're not here to have an adventure! - OG}Hey, Luffy! Just remember,
this isn't the time for adventure!
It's a quick stop to find a doctor.
{We're leaving once
we get Nami-san looked at! - OG}Once Nami's looked at, we're gone!
Hey! Hey, Luffy!
Snow is so nice and white!
It's no use. He's not listening.
H-H-Hold on! Is this a good idea?!
{If there's snow,
couldn't there be snow monsters too?! - OG}If there's snow, won't there
also be snow monsters?!
{Besides, we're not even sure
if people live there or not! - OG}And we don't know
if people live there! Oh, no!
My chronic can't-get-on-this-island disease!
Snow! I love snow! It's white!
Guess I'll prep us for landfall.
All this snow! It's pure happiness!
This is really something.
What's with those mountains?
Say, Luffy. Aren't you cold,
dressed like that?
It's minus 10 degrees right now!
That's when bears
get ready to hibernate!
Huh? Oh.
So cold!
Took you long enough!
It's a waterfall of melted snow.
We may be able to dock here.
So, who's going doctor hunting?
Actually, you see any people?
I'm going!
So am I!
Okay! Have fun!
That's far enough, pirates!
Hey. I found people.
But... they don't seem too friendly.
Attention, pirates!
Turn around and leave
this place immediately!
We came to find a doctor!
There's a sick person on board!
{We won't fall for that trick,
you filthy pirates! - OG}That's a dirty trick,
you pirate bastards!
{This is our island!
We won't let any pirates land here! - OG}On our island, any and all
pirates are barred entry!
Raise anchor and leave,
or we'll blow your ship to smithereens!
{They really hate our guts.
And we've just met, too... - OG}They really hate our guts.
And we've only just met.
Less talking!
They're shooting!
You did not just do that!
{ Stop, Sanji-san!
Bastard! - OG} No, Sanji!
Bastard!
Vivi!