Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Gigglebot
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Typesetting
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Inherited will...
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
Subtitle Editing
EvoWarrior5
Randy Troy
Ravenfire
Silence
Zenef
EvoWarrior5
Randy Troy
Ravenfire
Silence
Zenef
They cannot be stopped.
Translation
arch1t3cht
Funimation
Rangicus
arch1t3cht
Funimation
Rangicus
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
shin
shin
eve
in
shin
stuck
stuck
TIKKU
TIKKU
dr
ama
TIKKU
land!
land!
you,
you,
ka
ra
you,
land!
land!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Dalton!
Did you find him?!
Here he is! We found Dalton!
What?! They found him?!
Thank goodness!
Dalton!
Who is that, anyway?!
This is terrible...
There's no heartbeat.
In order for you to get
a healthy smile back,
{I prepared an exceptionally
nutritious dish... - OG}I prepared an exceptionally
nutritious dish.
Thank you, Sanji.
{though you're still painfully beautiful even after what your body's been through... - OG}{You're still painfully beautiful
even after what your body endured. - Evo}Despite what your body endured,
you're still so gorgeous that it hurts.
{Good lord! When did you use
my kitchen without asking? - OG}Good grief. Who said you could use
my kitchen without asking?
Madam, that roast over there is yours.
{It's high in protein
and is good for rejuvena- - OG}It's high in protein and will rejuvena
I'm not a "madam."
{I'm a sparkling single...
and still youthful. - OG}{I'm a sparkling single,
and still youthful. - Evo}I may be single, but I'm
still beaming with beauty.
You're only 139 years old, right?
Doctorine! Help me!
Wait! Hey! Wait!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
What are you doing?
This guy's gonna join us
and become our friend!
Oh, really?!
I didn't agree to anything like that!
You did.
I didn't!
You did!
Be quiet, both of you!
Wait!
Friend, huh?
{How deep a
meaning that word has to him... - OG}{How deep a
meaning that word has to him. - Evo}What a strong significance
that word holds for him.
You have no idea...
{There was one man whom he opened
up to when he was alone... - OG}{There was only one man to whom
[/q2]he opened his heart when he was alone. - Evo}{When he was alone, only one man
was able to open his heart. - Ravenfire}When he was all alone, only one man
was able to open his heart.
His name was Dr. Hiriluk.
{He was a quack who gave Chopper
a name and called him son. - OG}{He was a quack who gave Chopper
his name and treated him as a son. - Evo}He was a quack who gave Chopper
his name and cared for him as a son.
Quack Doctor
Hold it!
Is he there?!
No! We can't find him!
Hiriluk, that darn quack!
{We'll catch him no matter what!
Those're Wapol-[/i1]sama[/i0]'s orders! - OG}{We'll catch him at all costs!
That's King Wapol's orders! - Evo}We'll catch him at all costs!
Those are King Wapol's orders!
Yes, sir!
Dammit...
You can't go on like this.
Let's call a doctor.
{No. There aren't any doctors
in this country... - OG}It's pointless. There aren't
any doctors in this country...
except for the Issie 20
who belong exclusively to Wapol.
{We'll beg Wapol and call
the Issie 20. I'll go. - OG}{We'll beg Wapol
to let the Issie 20 help. I will go. - Evo}{Then we'll beg Wapol
to let the Issie 20 help! I will go. - Evo/Sil}{Then we'll beg Wapol
to let the Issie 20 help! I'll go. - Evo/Sil/Zenef}Then we'll beg Wapol to let
the Issie 20 come here! I'll go.
There's no need for that.
Dr. Hiriluk, Quack Doctor
I'll examine him.
Hiriluk! N-No thank you!
Please don't!
A bunch of people you treated
ended up getting worse!
Don't be nervous.
{I just developed a wonderful
all-purpose drug yesterday. - OG}I just developed a wonderful
cure-all yesterday.
You're in luck.{Ravenfire; note: this seems like a saying so I'd opt to make all of these lines match. It sounds exactly the same. This is repeated at 7:12}
{Hm? It's not what you think.
This is a tranquilizer gun. - OG}Hm? It's not what you think.
That's just a tranquilizer gun.
{I use it when the
patient's pain is severe. - OG}It's for patients in extreme pain.
I-I'll go and get the guards!
{Please leave!
If you want money, I'll pay! - OG}Please leave! If it's
money you want, I'll pay!
I don't take money from sick people.
I just want to help you.
Don't! Stop it! I've got a family!
{Croak! Croak, croak!
Croak, croak, croak! - OG}Croak! Ribbit! Croak! Ribbit!
Croak! Croak!
{Hm? This is strange.
Did I use a wrong ingredient? - OG}Hm? This is strange.
Did I use the wrong ingredient?
{I thought frog extract would work...
Guess it was a failure. Oh man... - OG}{I thought frog extract would work.
Guess it was a failure. Oh man... - Evo}I thought frog extract would work.
Damn... Guess it was a failure.
{S-Sorry... I didn't
mean for this to happen... - OG}S-Sorry... I didn't mean
for this to happen.
Hiriluk! Are you in there?!
Hold it!
Hmm?
Dr. Kureha (133 Years Old)
Are ya happy, young man?
{The doctor hunt has come
to the final stage. - OG}The doctor hunt is almost over.
I hear that you and I are
the only doctors left in this country.
Wapol is desperately trying
to catch us.
{Even if that wasn't the case, you're
already an outcast in this country... - OG}{[/q2]Even if he wasn't,
you're now an outcast in this country... - Ravenfire/Evo}Even if he wasn't,
you're an outcast around here...
seeing as you're nothing but a quack.
I won't get caught
by some doctor hunt.
{I'll save this country using
medical science one day. - OG}{I'll save this country using
my medical inventions one day. - Evo}One day, I'll save this country
using medical science.
{Oh? Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"? - OG}Oh? Didn't you mean to say
"destroy this country"?
There are people on the bridge!
I'll see you around, quack.
{I don't wanna see you again,
you thieving doctor. - OG}I'd like to avoid that, thief.
I'll never get caught!
I'll save as many
sick people as possible!
Hm?
You've been shot?
We need to stop the bleeding
right away or you'll die!
Don't worry. I'll save you!
It's a yeti! Shoot it dead!
{I just made an ointment that even
works on broken bones 3 days ago. - OG}{I made an ointment that can heal
even broken bones three days ago. - Evo}{[/q2]Just three days ago, I made an ointment
that can even heal broken bones. - Sil/arch}{[/q2]I made a new ointment just three days ago
that helps with broken bones. - Zenef}I made a new ointment just three days ago
that heals broken bones.
You're in luck.
Don't let it get away!
Take it down!
Shoot it!
What are you?
You don't look like a human.
{Oh, yeah. You're that yeti
that people have been talking about... - OG}Oh, right, you're that yeti
everyone's been talking about.
Yeah! We hit it!
It wasn't enough! Finish it!
H... How dare you...
Who do you...
think I am?!
Hey! Wait!
I'm not going to shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
I'm a doctor!
That was Chopper and Hiriluk's
first encounter.
{So what happened... to the
reindeer taken in by Hiriluk? - OG}{So what happened
to the reindeer taken in by Hiriluk? - Evo}So what happened
after Hiriluk took in the reindeer?
What?! You can talk?!
Why didn't you say anything
for three days?
I thought you'd hate me if I talked.
{When I talked to humans the
other day, they shot me... - OG}When I talked to humans
the other day, they shot me...
because it's strange
for a reindeer to speak.
So what if you can speak?
{I can speak, too...
a lot better than you can. - OG}I can speak, too.
A lot better than you can.
Run, Chopper!
What?
Dammit! It failed again!
Hey, are you okay, Chopper?!
{Hmm? Well, you aren't okay
to start with, I guess... - OG}Hmm? Well, you weren't okay
to start with, I guess.
Why are you calling me Chopper?
You're Tony Tony Chopper.
{After all, you're a reindeer and have fine antlers that could chop down trees. - OG}{After all, you're a reindeer and have
[/q2]fine antlers that could chop down trees. - Evo}After all, you're a reindeer whose
first-rate antlers can chop down trees.
That's a cool name, isn't it?
That's what I'll call you.
Chopper...
Listen, Chopper. You must observe
patients carefully while treating them.
Doing so will save people's lives.
{Let's go! Patients are waiting
for me today once again. - OG}{Let's go! It's another day,
but patients are still depending on me. - Ravenfire}{Let's go! It may be another day,
but patients still need me. - Ravenfire/PJ}Let's go! With every passing day,
patients are depending on me!
Get out of here, quack!
I thought lizard eyeballs would work!
Never come back!
Go away!
Run! It's the guards!
Chopper! We'll use the decoy plan!
The what?!
Take care!
Huh?
You almost got me killed!
{Oh yeah?! You failed to die once already!
You clumsy blue nose! - OG}{Well, you barely escaped death
once already! You clumsy blue nose! - Evo}Well, you almost died once anyway,
you blue-nosed oaf!
Leave my blue nose out of this!
Doctor...
Hm?
{This is... the first time
I've fought with someone... - OG}This is... the first time
I've fought with someone.
{Makes sense... To fight,
you have to have an opponent. - OG}That makes sense. To fight,
you need to have an opponent.
Then... is it your first time
for this as well?
Hm?
{I'll give it to you. It's a gift...
as a memento of our making up. - OG}{I'll give you this present.
See it as a memento of us making up. - Evo}I offer you this gift
to commemorate our making up.
A gift...? Making up...?
{We both go through hardships
as outcasts, don't we? - OG}{We're both outcasts on the run,
so life is hard for us. - Evo}{Life is hard when you're
an outcast like us. - Zenef}Life is hard for outcasts
like us, isn't it?
But don't hold a grudge
against humans.{But don't hold a grudge
against all humans. - Evo}
This country is sick right now.
{Both the citizens and the king
suffer from a sickness of the heart. - OG}{The hearts of the people
and the king have fallen ill. - Evo}The king and his people suffer
from a sickness of the heart.
{People would probably say
that you can't treat a sick country, - OG}{Some would probably say
that you can't treat a sick country, - Ravenfire}Some would probably say
that you can't heal a sick country,
but that's not true.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!{Once my creation is complete,
this country will be saved! - Ravenfire}
{There used to be a master-thief
in a country in the far west. - OG}{There used to be an infamous thief
in a country in the far west. - Evo}There used to be a master thief
in a country far to the west.
He had a serious heart disease.
{He went to see every possible skilled
doctor and got treated by them, - OG}He sought treatment from every
skilled doctor he could find
but none could fix him.
{After being told he'd die, he passed by a mountain while frustrated and unsettled. - OG}{He learned he would die, and it nearly drove him mad, but then he passed by a mountain. - Evo}Being told he would die unsettled him,
but then he passed by a mountain.
There... he saw a sight
that he had never seen in his life.
Cherry blossoms!
He saw vivid cherry blossoms
all over the mountain!
{And then, he went to see another
doctor and was shocked... - OG}{After that, he went to see
another doctor and he was shocked - Evo}After that, he went to see
another doctor and was shocked
because the doctor said,
"You have a clean bill of health."
What?
{He was cured! It was indeed
a miracle! Don't you think? - OG}{He was cured! You're thinking it
must have been some miracle, right? - Evo}He was all better! You're thinking
it must've been some miracle, right?
But it was definitely medical science!
{By being emotionally moved, some sort of change happened in this man's body! - OG}A powerful emotion somehow
triggered a change in the man's body!
{In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured. - OG}That means there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
{That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases! - OG}{That's why I raised this skull and
crossbones towards all the diseases! - Evo}That's why I raised this skull
and crossbones against all diseases!
A skull...
{This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible! - OG}This here... is a symbol of conviction
that defies the impossible!
I'll save this country as a doctor!{Evo: this is repetitive with the line from earlier but he seems to say the exact same thing both times so probably best to leave this the same too.}
{By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do! - OG}By raising this flag,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Hey! Reindeer!
Join us and become our friend!
Hm? Whoa! That looks so good!
It's cool to be a pirate!
Doctor, what are pirates?
Pirates?
Pirates are remarkable people
who roam the seas.
{They have large, well-trained
bodies and eyes like an eagle. - OG}They have large, muscular
bodies and eagle eyes.
{Their voices are like
a thunder splitting the sky! - OG}{Their voices boom,
like thunder splitting the sky! - Evo}Their voices are like thunder
splitting the sky!
Are you... really a pirate?!
Hm?
Yeah, I am...
Like I've been saying, join us!
It's fun to be a pirate! Pirates sing, too.
What? Th-They sing?
Yeah. And they dance, too!
You call that being a pirate?!
{That's right!
And they go on lots of adventures! - OG}Yep! And there are lots of adventures.
Adventures? So pirates
go on adventures then?
Of course! Pirates risk their lives
to go on adventures!
You can meet lots of amazing people!
Pirates are incredible!
There are countless people
like that out at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
{If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are. - OG}If you do, you'll realize
just how small your own problems are.
{This island that you were born on
is like this compared to the world. - OG}Compared to the rest of the world,
your home island is this small!
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
Your future lies beyond that sea!
The good times passed
in the twinkling of an eye.
But eventually...
the time to bid farewell...
comes for everyone.
It took a whole year,
One Year Later
but your treatment has finished.
Your injuries are
completely healed, Chopper.
Yes! Thank you, Doctor!
Well then... take care.
What?
{Now, leave! Live as you please!
I'm busy with my research! - OG}Now, go! Live as you please!
I'm busy with my research!
I no longer have any moral obligation
to take care of you!
{Doctor! I'll never cause you
any trouble! Please let me in! - OG}{[/q2]Doctor! I'll never cause you any trouble!
Please let me back in! - Evo}Doctor! I'll never cause any trouble again,
so please let me back in!
{I'll massage your shoulders everyday!
I'll make you tea and clean the house! - OG}{I'll massage your shoulders every day!
I'll make you tea and clean the house! - Evo}I'll give you daily shoulder massages!
I'll brew tea and clean the house!
Please! Let me stay!
I don't have any friends!
I have no place to go!
Doctor! Doctor!
Chopper!
{Look at this, Doctor.
I'm injured. Hey, Doctor! - OG}Look, Doctor, I'm injured.
Hey, Doctor!
Look!
Why... Doctor?
Go! Go out to sea! Go anywhere!
But don't ever come back here!
Forgive me, Chopper!
I'm... going to die soon.
Yeah, you will.
{Tell me!
How many more days do I have? - Evo}Tell me. How much longer do I have?
Oh? If you're asking me
to examine you, I refuse.
You don't have the money
to pay my fee.
Tell me!
{You can't kill a person
with a tranquilizer gun! - OG}How do you plan to kill me
with a tranquilizer gun?
{I'll tell you. You'll die at 5 pm
on the 10th day from today. - OG}{Fine, I'll tell you. You'll die
at five o'clock in ten days from now. - Evo, is she really this specific in the original?}Fine, I'll tell you. You'll die
ten days from now at five o'clock.
You won't have to suffer any more.
Ten days... That'll be enough.
I only need two days...
In two days, I will complete
my thirty-year-long research project.
I will... make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
{Cherry blossoms? So the research
you've continued for 30 years - OG}Cherry blossoms? So that research
you've continued for thirty years
was about making
cherry blossoms bloom?
The miracle cherry blossoms that saved you,
a master thief, long ago?{[/q2]The miracle cherry blossoms that saved you,
the infamous thief, long ago? - Evo}
That's right!
What?
{You're a fool. This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold year around. - OG}{Ridiculous. This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold year-round. - Zenef/Sil}Foolish man. This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold year-round.
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
They will!
{I was a hopeless
thug and dying, but I lived on and was able to
have a profound change of heart. - OG}{I was a hopeless thug
on the brink of death, but I lived on and was able to
have a profound change of heart. - Evo}{[/q2]I was just a thug hanging on by a thread to life,
but my heart changed as I continued to live. !- Zenef}I was just a thug hanging on to life by a thread,
but my heart changed as I kept on living.
Every human in this world
can be saved!
{I'd like to prove it here in Drum,
the land where I was born! - OG}I'd like to prove it here on Drum,
the land where I was born!
{Listen. What you're trying to do
isn't medical science or any science. - OG}Listen. What you're attempting
isn't medicine or anything like it.
{Even if the cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing to human bodies. - OG}{Even [/i1]if[/i0] cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing to human bodies. - Sil/Ravenfire}Even if cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing for human bodies.
Hiriluk!
{Chopper! We're alike. So I will
at least teach you before I die... - OG}Chopper... we're alike.
So before I die, I'd like to teach you...
{that there's nothing
impossible in this world... - OG}{that nothing is impossible
in this world... - Evo}that nothing in this world is impossible.
{and that you can accomplish
anything and everything! - Zenef}You can accomplish
anything and everything!
{But the story of these two
doesn't have a happy ending... - OG}But the story of these two
doesn't have a happy ending.
Why?!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
That smell...
Huh?
Wapol!
{When he found out that
Hiriluk had only 10 days to live, - OG}When he found out that Hiriluk
had only ten days to live,
Chopper was very upset.
Well, that was only natural.
But he took action in his own way...
I'm... going to die soon.
I will... make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
{This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible! - OG}This here... is a symbol of conviction
that defies the impossible!
{A lot of guards have been
absent recently. What's going on? - OG}What's going on?
Many guards have been absent lately.
Well... they're out picking mushrooms
at the request of the Issie 20.
Mushrooms?
They said there's some mushroom
that can cure anything...
Mushroom?
Ah!
Hm?
Bonehead! They'll see us!
Doctor, about what they said...
I'm not going to shoot you!
But don't ever come back here!
I treated you terribly.
Wait until you can see
my cherry blossoms.
They'll be my final accomplishment.
Well... here we go again!
Dammit! I don't have much time left!
{Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull! - OG}{[/q2]Nothing is impossible for a man
who raises a skull and crossbones flag! - Ravenfire/Rangicus}Nothing's impossible when a man
raises a skull and crossbones flag!
That's what I told you, right?!
I will fight!
Just like pirates do!
I found it! The amiudake.
That's the one!
But...
How do I get across?
One Week Later
Dammit!
Doctor...
{I'm sorry... I lost...
one of your precious books... - OG}I'm sorry... I lost...
one of your precious books.
What... happened to you?
Mushroom...
Medicine...
That's an amiudake!
You... got it for me?
Please live... Please live, Doctor.
{I wanna be a doctor.
Please teach me how to be a doctor. - OG}I wanna be a doctor.
Please teach me how to become one.
I'll fight, too... just like pirates do!
{Do you think a reindeer
can become one, too? - OG}Can a reindeer become one too?
You can! You can! You can!
You can be a great doctor...
Doct... I can't breathe.
...because you have such a kind heart.
You bonehead!
Chess! Kuromarimo!
Is the doctor hunt going well?!
King Wapol
Drum
Yes sir.
Chess
Drum Councilor
Kuromarimo
Drum Bailiff
{Most of the doctors
have already been exiled.[/an8] - OG}We've exiled most of the doctors already.
Most?
{There are two that
we haven't captured yet. - OG}However, two have eluded capture.
Dalton
Drum Royal Guard Captain
That Dr. Kureha and...
...the quack, Hiriluk.
What'd you say?!
Oh, yeah! I've come up
with a good idea!
Hm?
{Send an official notice to the citizens.
The Issie 20 have all... fallen ill... - OG}Send an official notice to the citizens.
The Issie 20 have all... fallen ill.
{Does the amiudake mushroom soup...
taste good? - OG}How is the amiudake soup?
Is it good?
{Ahhh!
Darn, this tastes terrible! - Evo}Ahh! Damn, this tastes terrible!
What?!
{This isn't something
that any living thing can eat! - OG}No living thing could stomach this!
Oh no...
{Don't be so down.
Good medicine doesn't taste good. - OG}Don't be so down. Medicine isn't
supposed to taste good.
That means it's working.
Thank you, Chopper.
Huh?!
Wha...?
Huh?
What's that?
I did it...
What?
I finally did it... This is it!
{This reaction... I've waited
for it for 30 years... - OG}{This reaction... I've waited
for this for thirty years. - Evo}This reaction...
I've waited thirty years for this.
{I did it, Chopper!
My research succeeded! - OG}I did it, Chopper!
I've completed my research!
I wasn't wrong! I wasn't! I wasn't!
{I can now make cherry blossoms
bloom on this winter island! - OG}Now I can make cherry blossoms
bloom on this winter island!
Listen. I'm going out,
but you stay put and rest here.
Okay.
See you later!
Doctor was happy...
I was able... to cure
someone's sickness!
Huh?
{You'll be able to become
a good doctor. - OG}You'll make a fine doctor!
I'm living proof of that.
{Do you know... that the entire
country is a madhouse right now? - OG}{Did you hear the news that's put
this country in a state of crisis? - Evo}Did you know that the entire country
has a screw loose?
Yeah, I know.
{About the Issie 20 falling ill,
right? Ridiculous! - OG}{About the Issie 20
falling ill, right? Ridiculous! - Evo}It's over the Issie 20
falling ill, right? Ridiculous!
So... what brought you here today?
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
Don't bother, I refuse.
I haven't asked anything yet!
What's this dust?
That is the fruit of thirty years.
{That's the medical science
that I've finally completed! - OG}{That's the medical science
I've completed at last! - Evo}{That's the medicine
I've finally completed - Ravenfire}It's a medicine I've finally completed
{It's an all-purpose medicine that can cure the country's sickness of the heart. - OG}{An all-purpose medicine
to cure the country's sick heart. - Evo}{an all-purpose medicine
to cure this country's sick heart. - Evo/Sil}a cure-all that can mend
this country's sick heart.
{You've lived 30 fruitless years.
Good work. - OG}What a waste of thirty years.
Well, good for you.
So, why are you showing it to me?
{There isn't enough dust.
I don't have much time left, either. - OG}{There isn't enough dust.
I don't have any time left. - Evo}There isn't enough dust,
and I'm out of time.
{I want you to make cherry
blossoms bloom in my place. - OG}I want you to make
the cherry blossoms bloom.
{Ridiculous! Why do I have to - Evo, changed timing to make them talk over each other.}That's absurd! Why do I have to
And one more thing!
Please teach medicine to Chopper.
He wants to become a doctor.
That's enough!
He's a reindeer and a monster,
Why would I...?
but I know he'll make a fine doctor!
He's a good kid with a kind heart.
{He risked his life
to make medicine for me! - OG}He risked his life
to make a remedy for me!
Please! Help him become a doctor!
You have some nerve!
You want me to take care of your
stupid research and strange pet?!
You should know I'm not someone
{who'll sympathize with a man
just 'cuz he's about to croak! - Evo}who'll sympathize with a man
just because he's about to croak!
Get out of here!
Yeah... I know... We've
known each other a long time.
I'm counting on you.
{It's not like you, Hiriluk...
throwing in the towel already... - OG}It's not like you, Hiriluk...
throwing in the towel already.
I'm out of time.
That idiot! He wouldn't!
What do you mean?!
The Issie 20 fell ill!
Who'll treat our people now?!
At least give us access to medicine!
There's nothing we can do!
Ropeway Station Four
Even doctors get sick!
Out of my way!
Ahh! Hiriluk?!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
That bastard is crazy!
Prepare the ropeway.
Take me to the castle.
Where's Hiriluk?!
You don't have to run away!
I know about you!
I'm asking you where the quack went!
{D-Doctor got better
so he went to the town... - OG}D-Doctor got better,
so he went to town...
Got better? There's no
getting better for him.
{He can't be cured with
the current medical science. - OG}{He can't be cured with
current medicines. - Evo}Modern medicine can't help him.
That's not true! Look at this!
He's fine now because he ate this!
That's... an amiudake!
{This is an all-purpose medicine!
So he's fine now! - OG}This is a cure-all!
So he's fine now!
{Doctor said that he felt
full of energy, too! - OG}Doctor said that he felt better, too!
He's going to teach me
how to be a doct
What was that for?!
You stupid reindeer!
That mushroom is...
a deadly poison!
Once you eat it,
you'll be dead within half a day!
What?
That's why that idiot...
That can't be true.
I looked it up in a book...
although I lost that book...
That mushroom can beat diseases!
{That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases! - OG}{That's why I raised this skull and
crossbones towards all the diseases! - Evo}That's why I raised this skull
and crossbones against all diseases!
{That's right! There was a skull right next to the amiudake mushroom picture! - OG}That's right! There was a skull
next to the amiudake picture!
Doctor also said he got better!
There's no way he'll die! You're a liar!
Paddle faster! Hurry up!
There isn't a second to waste!
What you did touched him deeply.
But the skull in the book
indicates poison.
That's a lie!
It's not a lie! Remember this:
{There's no medicine that can work
for all diseases in this world. - OG}No one medicine in this world
can possibly cure every disease.
That's why doctors exist!
That's not true!
Listen. You can't save people
just by being kind!
{If you want to save them,
then learn medical knowledge and skills! - OG}If you want to save them,
learn medical knowledge and skills!
Without these skills,
you can't save anyone!
You idiot.
{Wapol-[/i1]sama[/i0]! Hiriluk is
heading to this castle! - OG}King Wapol! Hiriluk is
heading to this castle!
So he took the bait!
What a hippo!
Is he serious? Why? What for?
{He'll no longer come back
to this house. - OG}He's not returning to this house.
{Looks like he decided the
castle is his graveyard... - OG}He's gone to make
the castle his graveyard.
Take me to the patients!
I came to save the Issie 20!
What?
What a hippo! You still don't get it?!
It was a trap! As you can see,
the Issie 20 are just fine!
Your only purpose here
is to die, Dr. Hiriluk.
Why did he come here?
Guards, ready...
That's all it was?
Good... So none of them are sick?
{I was convinced...
that this was a national crisis... - OG}I was convinced that
this was a national crisis.
But it was merely a trick...
{Humph! If it was really a national crisis, I wouldn't want someone like you! - OG}{Humph! If it really was a crisis,
I wouldn't want someone like you! - Evo}Hmph! If it really was a crisis,
I wouldn't want someone like you!
But I digress. Execute him!
Don't bother. You can't kill me.
Huh?
Hey... when do you think
a person dies?
{When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart? - OG}{When a pistol's bullet
pierces his heart? - arch}When a pistol's bullet
pierces their heart?
{No... When he's attacked
by an incurable disease? - OG}No.
{When he's stricken
by an incurable disease? - OG}{When he's stricken
with an incurable disease? - Ravenfire}When they're stricken
with an incurable disease?
{No... When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup? - OG}No.
{When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup? - OG}{When he eats
a poisonous mushroom soup? - Evo}When they eat
a poisonous mushroom soup?
No!
{A man dies...
when people forget him... - OG}A person dies...
when they are forgotten.
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
{The citizens' sickness of the heart
will be cured as well. - OG}The people's sickness of the heart
will be cured as well.
Why are you crying... Dalton?
I'm wondering... if this country
will be cured as well.
{Yeah, if there's someone
to pass it on to... - OG}{Yeah. If there's someone
to pass it on to. - Evo}Of course. If someone is willing
to carry it forward.
{Hey, hey, Dalton!
What're you crying for? - Evo}Now, now, Dalton!
What are you crying for?
{Soon a monster will come here.
He's my son. Don't hurt him. - OG}Soon a monster will arrive.
He's my son. Don't hurt him.
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom can't kill me.
What a marvelous life it's been!
Goodbye, quack...
Thank you, Chopper!
He blew himself up! What a hippo!
Ahh!
What's that?!
It's a monster!
Shoot it!
Ahh!
Wait!
Leave. Get out of here!
How can you possibly defeat them...
when you can't even beat me?!
{For laughing at
Hiriluk's death, I apologize! - OG}{I apologize on behalf of him
for laughing at Hiriluk's death! - Evo}{I apologize on behalf of all those
who laughed at Hiriluk's death! - Zenef}I apologize on behalf of all those
who laughed at Hiriluk's death,
{Without enough power,
you'll just die in vain... - OG}{Without enough power,
you'll just die in vain. - Evo}but you'll needlessly join him
if you fight them in this state.
{Don't sacrifice yourselves
any longer for this country... - OG}{Let's not cause any more sacrifices
for this country. - Evo}This country has seen
enough sacrifices for one day.
Please...
Huh?
You let him flee, Dalton.
Shut up! You still don't get it?
The only man who tried to save
this sick country has just died.
When everyone
gave up and despaired,
{a kind doctor who tried
to save this country died! - OG}a kind doctor died
trying to save this country!
So what if someone like that dies?
{I saw the path that this country
should take. It should die out. - OG}{I see now that this country is
on a road only to destruction. - Evo}I see now where the kingdom is headed,
so it's best if it dies too.
{As long as we stay here,
it can't be rebuilt because.... - OG}With us at the helm, it can't be rebuilt.
Even if medical care progresses...
{even if the research
on medicine continues... - OG}even if medical research continues...
{there's no medicine
that can cure fools! - OG}no amount of medicine
can cure a fool!
{I let you have your say...
You made me really angry! - OG}I let you speak your mind...
and it's made me extremely angry!
Please... please teach me
to be a doctor!
{Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine! - OG}Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the cure-all!
{I'll become a doctor who can cure
anything! I'll cure even a country! - OG}I'll become a doctor who can
cure anything. I'll even cure a country!
Because... Because...
there's no disease that can't be cured!
You can call me... Doctorine.
I won't... die here.
I will carry on his will.
{So for the 6 years since then...
Tony-[/i1]kun[/i0]has been studying under you... - OG}So for the last six years...
Tony has been studying under you.
Yeah... I taught him
everything I know.
Doctorine! Doctorine!
Doctorine! There's a problem!
Wapol is back!
Is that so...
Ah! That bastard!
It's that big mouth!
Look! Everything is just how I left it!
{This is my castle.
We're restoring the Kingdom of Drum! - OG}Let's get back to my castle
and restore the Kingdom of Drum!
{Just a moment, Wapol-[/i1]sama[/i0]!
On top of the castle... - OG}Just a moment, King Wapol!
On top of the castle...
Huh?
What's that strange flag?
{What happened
to the Kingdom of Drum's flag?! - OG}What happened to Drum's royal flag?!
I burned that thing.
So you show yourself, Dr. Kureha,
the last survivor of the doctor hunt!
This castle is no longer yours!
This isn't a place
for rotten brats like you!
Leave this country!
The Kingdom of Drum has already died out!
What'd you say?!
Wait!
I'm gonna beat the crap outta him!