Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Those are our Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go, always, be the best
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Battle
Doflamingo!
You weaklings are working together...
Looks like you're gonna get those handcuffs off soon, aren't you, Law?
Why the hell are you here?!
I came to save you.
How could you fall into such a stupid trap? That crap about a shortcut!
Straw Hat!
Bullet String!
Moocy!
Give him up! Straw Hatter!
Moocy...
You have no sense of crisis...
Stay... with me... Moocy...
So cheesy!
Anyone could kill you guys like this.
There are some idiots who are saying they'll kill me, rampaging out there...
It's amazing how you found people who side with you under these circumstances.
I've been giving you due respect for that special quality of yours since the War of the Best.
But...
You're actually this dumb!
Why did you choose him, Law?
You used to be a more promising man.
Even when you were a kid, you were more ruthless...
And more cunning!
Am I right?!
Who made you... into such a coward?
Shut up!
I'm not willing to become like you!
I've been... saved!
By my brother Corazon, you mean?
If you haven't become a coward...
Why do you want to die in vain...
...alongside this dumbshit?
Stop! Don't hurt Straw Hat-san!
Get your hands off of him!
What the hell is this?!
What's wrong with his body?!
It's his clone as I thought.
Clone?
That's a string puppet.
You guys...
Straw Hat-san!
Glad that you're safe!
In any case, pull out Straw Hat-san!
You saved me... Thank you!
No, no, no, no...
Now, is that his lower body?! What's going on with that?!
All in all, we brought down the big game, didn't we?!
Idiot! I told you before. That's a fake!
He took the trouble to send the string puppet to tease us?
Oh yeah! Actually, that Kelly Funk guy from earlier...
That bastard was fooling us!
What a simple-minded fool...
He fell into our trap completely.
We learned that and
when we tried to stop him...
We gotta do something! Abdullah, can you get up?
That infamous assassin Kelly got taken out in a split second...
If it's true, it's like we were really saved by that jerk!
He's mocking us!
What's going on out there?! How are Cabbage and the others?!
We're totally falling behind...
I bet everybody else reached the second level by now!
Damn! I thought we could take a shorter route to the Sunflower Field!
We gotta go back! Hurry up!
Royal Palace Plateau - Level 1
What the...?!
Rubber...
Royal Palace Plateau - Level 2
Ah! There's not a single dropout on the first level!
It's impossible!
Our subordinates can't match them-in!
Straw Hat and his group aren't here yet.
Let's take them out one by one.
Elephant Gun!
What's that?!
Oh no!
There'll be another one!
They don't even know what it is! How could they be freaked out by it!
Guys! Don't lose sight of the enemies!
In the Well
First Step
He really made a shortcut!
Guys! Take care of Moocy, okay?!
Yes!
I like this confusion!
Chinjao and the others are heading to the third level!
Stop them!
This big hole...
What the... hell is going on...
What's this?!
It's Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
Trafalgar Law!
Let's get going! Straw Hatter!
Yeah!
Wait for me, Mingo!
Are you serious?!
No...
I am serious!
You can't fly people with beetles!
Former Royal Plateau
Let's run through the town!
Yeah, yeah! I like her idea!
Now, let me give you instructions.
Aren't you even listening to us, small one?!
Tontatta Airlines
Yellow Cubs
This is Tontatta Airlines' Jumping Service!
Big Humans are too heavy so they can't bear you!
See, we told you!
We don't have that much time,
so just take off!
What?!
We told you we can't fly like this!
Leo, don't push them too far!
Hey, are you alright?!
Damn! Little People! I'll pay you back for this!
Am I... flying?!
They can't fly you but they can slow you down when you fall!
I'm falling! I'm falling! I'm falling!
Relax!
How can I relax?! I'm gonna crash into something!
Head for a rooftop!
A rooftop?!
That's right! And land on it smoothly!
Now! Kick off!
I'm flying!
Kicking off rooftops helps you to rise!
I see!
I'm getting the knack of it!
Good! You're doing great!
I feel like I'm a balloon!
Watch out for attacks from below.
Level 4
The Sunflower field
Head for the Sunflower Field on the fourth level, everybody!
Roger that!
Got it!
In front of the SMILE factory
Fraland!
We have an idea to unlock the door to the Factory!
What?! Really?!
Yes! So please keep Senor busy like that!
I got it!
Count on me!
On Top of Pica's Statue
You asshole! You just stepped on my sword!
So what?
In Town
Sabo vs. Fujitora
What a fight!
The Palace
Hey hey, Doffy!
Did you send String-Joker off somewhere?
I wanted to deliver something but I guess he doesn't need it.
You guys...
Do you remember the day we met Law for the first time?
He was nuts!
Even his eyes were crazy...
Yeah, yeah!
He looked like me when I was a kid.
I sensed he would become my right-hand man in 10 years or so.
It's a shame that I will have to kill him with my own hands.
We have an intruder!
Don't touch him!
He has explosives strapped to his body!
Hey! Who the hell is this kid?!
Who let him in?!
Let me join your pirate group.
I wanna destroy everything that I see!
Towns, houses, people...
I wanna destroy them all!
I...
...grew up in the White Town - Flevance.
It's not so long...
...before I die.
Mingo!
Dressrosa
Within the Birdcage
I'm feeling sentimental now...
The Royal Palace
What did you come here for?
Pirate Bellamy the Hyena
Bounty: 195 million Belly
Did you kill Straw Hat, Bellamy?
Why did you send Dellinger to kill me?!
Was it really your order?!
Oh boy... What rubbish...
Isn't there any...
...hope left for me?
Don't make me say it straight, Bellamy.
Your purpose was different from mine.
From long ago.
You always wanted to become a pirate.
But not me.
Anything was fine with me.
Anything?
As long as I could...
...destroy this world!
Royal Palace Plateau - Level 2
Colosseum Army vs. the Donquixote Family
Get out of my way, kid!
I'm in a rush!
Hey, what do I look like?
Hey, tell me, Suleiman!
You used to be a war executioner, right?!
I love... executing people!
Kicks!
Oh no... That's too bad.
It's over already.
Here come the Executives of the Family!
Alright! I'm gonna get to the third level first!
What are these bulging stones?
That place is dangerous.
Mine... pop!
Grandpa! I'm coming!
Da-in!
Floaty, floaty...
Ten-Ton Vise!
You see it, idiots?!
That's how powerful our Family's Executives are!
He did it!
They can't go any farther!
I got you!
Armsmorphosis!
Revolver Leg!
The Town in the South - Sevio
I got him!
Bring the rope now!
And treat him! He's been shot!
The rest of you, put out the fire!
Okay!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... Thank you!
I almost killed my family!
It was me who set the town on fire! I'm sorry!
I sliced up my own friend!
Me, too! Dammit!
It's not your fault.
Everything happened because of Doflamingo's meddling!
We gotta bring an end to this game somehow...
Hey!
We found out where King Riku is!
He's with the Five-star God Usopp!
Alright... Let's do it!
But we only capture them!
Okay?
Yeah, if we don't do it, this game will last until we die!
First, take King Riku and God Usopp as hostages.
And lure other criminals using those hostages!
Tell the people all over the country!
Head for Old King's Plateau!
Yeah!
SMILE Factory
Interior
Did you knock over this SAD tank?!
Pick it up!
Are you okay?!
Please stop! There was a sudden earthquake
and the tank got knocked over!
He's right!
What caused that earthquake?!
Shut up! You guys don't need to worry about it!
But!
Don't you guys wanna cure Princess Mancherie's illness?!
I bet you do!
Of course, we wanna cure it!
How is she doing?!
Huh?
Um...
I'm afraid the princess isn't getting better at all!
At all!
What?!
Please! Let us see the princess!
Oh, damn! What a pain!
Shut up and work!
Is that...
You fools, just stop grumbling and keep making SMILEs!
From inside, Unlock...
What are you guys doing?!
I said work, idiots!
From inside, Unlock...
Quit zoning out! Can't you hear me?!
...The door!
Those words...
It's the Pink Bees!
Bian!
Inhel! Wicca!
They noticed us! Bian!
Roger that!
Pink Bees, the next message!
We got fooled!!!
What? "We got fooled"?
What do they mean?
Hey, you guys! Can't you hear us?!
We got fooled?
Is it about the princess' illness?
Doflamingo has been fooling us?
Fight!!!
I guess you need another beating to understand things.
I don't know what's going on
but one thing I know is...
Friends don't lie!
Shut up!
Sanshita!
Royal Palace Plateau- Level 2
Straw Hat!
Cabbage!
Do you wanna get in my way, again?!
No...
Get on.
What?
I mean I'll give you a ride because I have no other choice!
You sure?!
You wanna get to Doflamingo ASAP, don't you?
Alright!
I'm ready! Go!
Have you ever once in your life been humble?!
Whatever, just go!
Don't tell me what to do!
Let's go, Farul!
Listen, if we get caught by the Executives, we get stuck here.
I'm gonna cut the wall and make a path so you kick the other enemies' asses!
Got it!
And we're gonna go straight to the third level...
Hey! That's one too many!
Who are you?!
Oh, Soldier!
When did you get on?!
Just now!
I followed the path that Luffyland made!
You followed too far!
Great! I was looking for you!
Even if you're his friend, we're overloaded! Get off!
We're gonna meet up with Rebecca!
Rebecca is in this enemy territory?!
Why didn't you stop her?!
Listen to me!
We'll rendezvous at the Sunflower Field on the fourth level.
She's on the criminal list, too!
Don't worry! She's with my friends!
Listen! My dear horse Farul can only run beautifully with two people or less!
The bull's back had more space...
By the way, pops,
why did you take off before I knew it?
Whatever the situation is...
What I have to do is...
...bring down Doflamingo
and take back the country!
But there's one more thing!
There's one man in the Family's Top Executives that I wanna kill with my own bare hands at any cost!
Old dude, you're not willing to die, are you?
No way! I won't be defeated with this human body!
Alright, then!
Nothing's alright! Get off!
Huh?! You get off!
That's nonsense! You're the worst!
You really are part of the Worst Generation!
Watch out, fool!
Look where you're going! Hey!
Like I said, don't tell me what to do!
What?!
Is that...
Go ahead, Straw Hat!
We're gonna keep them busy!
What-in?! They're suddenly...
They were disorganised before, fighting each other!
What?! Why are you doing this, guys?!
I am Dagama, the military technician!
This is war!
Even if we all run wild blindly, no one can reach the top!
I don't trust Dagama but I agreed to his plan to keep the Executives here and let Straw Hat go ahead!
Leave this mess here to us and go!
Make sure to take him there, Cavendish!
Hey, hey! I'm not public transportation!
We gotta win this war!
Way to go!
Looks like that guy is taking command.
He's annoying!
Daruma!
What the... Hey, let go off me!
You jerk!
Get to the top! Straw Hat!
Shoot, shoot!
Keep them off at any price!
Blade of Beauty! Saint-Exupéry!
Blade of Beauty: Stardust Prince
Rubber Jet Gatling!
Editing: Galaxy 9000
Timing: Datenshi
QC: Mr Luffy,
Sewil
Soundtracking: Halee
TC/Infoboxes: Datenshi