Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bonds that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Tsuki
Yibis (Opening)
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Soundtracking
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
Video editing
Sewil
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Raw provider
Crunchyroll
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose! I'll find One Piece. I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Bellamy's Changed Motivations and B Block's Start!
Now, the next competitor to enter is...
...a latecomer from B block!
It only took him a year to become infamous and enter the New World!
An incomparably brutal and crazy rookie!
He roasted a whole pirate crew on a skewer and shared the video!
He's also responsible for bombing innocent civilians!
He ranked No. 1 in the "most annoying pirate who should just go away"-poll!
Captain of the Barto Club Pirate Crew
Bartolomeo the Cannibal
Bounty: 150,000,000 Belly
The pirate...
Bartolomeo!
Every last one of you...
Can go to hell!
Go home!
You can go to hell!
What are you doing, you bastard?!
Don't tell me it's...
It's a bomb!
It's packed and I can't get out!
Move aside, old man! You're too slow!
You're in my way, too!
It's "ladies first"! Let me out!
Forget the others, just help me! I'll give you my money!
A ball...
How shameless.
They hate you so much, brat.
I don't even want those shitheads to like me.
But B block isn't done yet!
There's one more!
He's nothing like that Crazy-lomeo!
He admires Doflamingo, the king of our country.
and declared his loyalty to him by presenting him with a pillar made entirely of gold from a distant land!
Oh, don't tell me it's...
Since then, he's been destroying various towns in many countries where they disrespected us...
...by calling us a barbaric kingdom of pirates, and bringing them to terms!
He is the "Bullet of Dressrosa"!
He's been given a great chance by the royal family!
Back of the Colosseum
The medical room is that way!
We don't have enough stretchers.
Walk by yourself if you can!
They got beaten badly by the champion.
Hey.
I'm not blind.
No matter how you disguise yourself,
I can't help recognizing the face of the guy...
...who put a blot on my record!
You!
You...
...gave the diamond-head gramps hell.
Maro.
It's Bellamy.
Right, Bellamy!
Why are you here?!
No reason.
Former Captain of the Bellamy Pirate Crew
I'm not a resident of Jaya.
Bounty: 195,000,000 Belly
Bellamy the Hyena
(Spring Fruit User)
I can be wherever I want.
On top of that,
Doflamingo has been my pirate hero since I was a kid.
I have no interest in the Flame Fruit...
but I have my own reason to win this thing!
Well, then I'll have to just fight you again!
But this won't turn out like the last time.
Straw Hat.
I've been to Sky Island.
I lost my crew and it turned my view of the world upside down.
You mean Skypiea?!
You didn't do anything to the people there, did you?!
Who knows?
Anyway, I'm not holding a grudge against you anymore.
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's ship to ride through
the "wild wave" that's coming.
I won't mock you anymore.
If he wins this competition,
his tenacity will be recognized
and it has been decided that he will be promoted to
an executive position within the Donquixote Family
He is a real contender for winning this competition!
The pirate!
Bellamy the Hyena!
Bellamy!
Even if this is his home, his popularity is remarkable.
Alright, the battle royal of Block B is about to begin!
A competitor will be eliminated if he is killed in the ring!
Or if he is thrown out of the ring!
There will be only one winner!
And here's the starting...
Fighting King
Elizabello II
Martial Artist
Blue Gilly
Military Captain
Tank Lepanto
Criminal
Abdullah
Pirate
Bartolomeo
Gladiator
Ricky
Pirate
Bellamy
Tactician
Dagama
Fishman Warrior
Hack
Criminal
Jeet
Bell!
Now, who should I start with?
What the hell? It's like an army!
That's not fair! They're teaming up!
You can't call something like that a battle royal!
I'd like to see you try to call us cowards after you die!
There will be only one winner! All we need is the result!
Looks like we have some competitors who have teamed up and are fighting together!
Is that allowed?
It's not very sportsmanlike, but I don't remember it being against the rules.
The man behind such a trick must be...
...Dagama, a tactician of the Prodence Kingdom.
We the Prodence Kingdom will take home the Flame Fruit.
Our king - Elizabello II was born to be a weapon of destruction!
A punch that is thrown from his naturally gifted physique is terribly powerful.
He blew a hole in an enemy country's fort with a single blow, shaking the earth!
King of Prodence
The Fighting King
Elizabello II
However, his power has one drawback.
It takes an hour to increase his concentration and warm up to throw a punch.
He can only use it once per battle!
They say his "King Punch" could even take out one of the Four Emperors if it hit them.
His victory depends on his timing!
King-sama, how is the preparation going?
It's gonna take a while. Guard me.
As you wish!
I need you guys to earn your salt!
Protect the king and cut down the number of the competitors in the ring!
Yeah!
Is it okay, Lepanto?
For the captain of Dressrosa's army to help a tactician from another country?
Commander of the
Dressrosa Self-Defense Forces
Bellamy, money runs this world!
Tank Lepanto
I'd rather make big money than chase a big dream!
That makes my ears burn.
Oh shit! I'm gonna fall!
Three competitors were eliminated by being thrown out of the ring!
And of course, in the water outside of the ring...
The Colosseum's famous creature!
Get them!
A school of Little Fighting Fish!
Doesn't matter if you're in or out of the ring! It's Hell!
No one can survive uninjured!
That's the Corrida Colosseum!
You can't hit me like that!
Spring...
Death Knock!
Abdullah!
Take this!
You're showing your back to me!
You cowards!
Abdullah & Jeet
"Cowards"?
I like the sound of that!
Hey you stupid Fish-Man!
Why are you participating in a human competition, monster?!
Hey, fish!
Poor man.
Huh?!
You are a puppet who can't speak with words of its own.
Let us converse with our fists!
That's a good idea!
Oh? It's not moving!
4000 Tile Punch!
Like our species' hope and my friend, Jinbe, teaches... we can establish friendly relations with our fists!
Fishman Karate Master
Fishman Jujutsu User
100th Degree Hack
Hence, I will continue fighting!
Ow, ow, ow... Damn that bastard!
What the hell are you doing?! He's just a lanky, unarmed man!
I-It doesn't matter whether he's unarmed or lanky!
From the Longleg Tribe
Jiaokungdo Martial Artist
Blue Gilly
His legs are like iron whips!
Jeez, you guys...
Come closer. It's boring when you're so far away.
He's just a guy from the Longleg Tribe!
Why don't you try attacking his legs, then?!
It's impossible! We can't get close to him!
That form!
I can't figure out where his kick is gonna come from!
Hey!
Huh?
I haven't seen that gladiator around here.
That's the guy!
He's pretty strong. Do you know him?
I've been fighting here as a gladiator for a long time
but I've never seen him before!
Gladiators of this Colosseum are trained to fight with a sword and a shield!
But he uses just a sword! Like a samurai from the Wano Country!
Let's test his skill!
Okay!
Too slow!
(Former) Gladiator
Ricky
Did you just see what the gladiator with a skull on his cape did?
Yeah.
He's strong but I don't remember ever seeing him here before.
Well, I was gonna say...
I think I've seen him before.
A man who fought like that without a shield.
What was his name again?
Look at him!
What?!
What are you doing?! Do you wanna get killed?!
Why isn't anybody attacking him?!
I wish somebody would kick your ass already!
Participants' Viewing Area
He's fooling around again.
That guy is one of those annoying newcomers just like Straw Hat Luffy.
He's another one I want to take out in this competition.
What are you doing, Cabbage?!
I'm checking the wanted posters of the Worst Generation.
But I really need new ones.
I can barely see their pictures with these knife cuts.
Why don't you just let it go already?
No way!
I'll kill them!
There is a big prize for this competition.
I was hoping at least Apoo or Kid would come...
...I don't know yet if any of them are here or not.
They can hide their face like Burgess did earlier.
If any of them are here should I wait for them to move on to the next round or...
Oh, is this the place to watch the battle?
This is a really nice view of the match.
By the way,
how is Garp-san doing?
Straw Hat Luffy-kun!
What?
You know Grandpa?
What?!
I almost got killed by Garp-san once.
And I've made up my mind to carry my grudge even against his children and grandchildren.
W-What!?