Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
The Shocking Truth of Tiger!
The End of the Sun Pirates
We finally got an Eternal Pose pointing toward Koala's homeland.
Nyuu- Koala, you can return to your homeland!
Uh... Um...
You sure have changed.  I barely recognized you.
You've become a lot more feminine.
I'm not used to...
What?  We finally got you some proper clothes,
but you don't like them?
We even gave you a haircut.
I'm sure your mother will like it better like this.
I...
I have to clean.
Nyuu- you've gotta get rid of
your habit of working whenever you're distressed!
This isn't Mariejoa, you know!
Let her do what she wants.
Nyuu?
Let her take her time.  Recovering from a trauma isn't that easy.
Really?
Sounds like you understand it well, Brother Aladdin.
Former slaves understand each other.
But you still want to kill her, don't you?  Right now?
She's a human, just like those who enslaved you!
Stop it, Arlong.
Show us your true nature!
What did your mother teach you?
Your parents look down on fishmen, right?
That's how the human society is, right?!
They think that humans are
the greatest species in the world!
The children hear this from their parents
and take it to heart!
Unless someone uses force to stop it,
this cycle will never end!
You've all seen them many times during our three year voyage, haven't you?
Those conceited, scornful looks that humans give us!
Who knows what I'd have done
if the Boss hadn't been around.
Only a small percentage of the humans scorn us.
The rest looked different to me.
Brother Jinbe...
From what I could see, they were all terrified of us.
Is it because we're pirates?
Why are you so afraid?
Because...
we don't know anything about you.
You fear the unknown?
We are biased because we only come into contact
with certain kinds of humans.
We still do not know anything about them.
If we knew each other better, would things change?
Nyuu- look at this, Koala!
Try to guess which hand I've got this in!
So, where is it?
Uh... This one.
Wrong!
Koala, come down.  We've reached your homeland.
Where is your village?
Huh?
I'll walk you to the entrance.
Sure!
Don't go, Koala!
Let's go on more adventures together!
You're such a good girl, even if you are human!
Don't cry, you guys!
I'll tell everyone in my village...
that there are many kind-hearted fishmen!
Thank you, everyone!
Good bye!
Take care of yourself!
When she grows up,
that kid will be just like all the other humans.
What's that supposed to mean, you bastard?!
Jinbe.
Arlong, you...
Brother Jinbe,
you've changed a lot in these past three years.
What?
Think about it.
What difference does it make if one person from that village preaches that fishmen are good people?
It'll be just like Otohime's preaching.
Her words will go in one ear and out the other.
I am Rear Admiral Strawberry, from Navy HQ.
We received a tipoff from a certain island that you would come here.
The adults in the village you just visited were informed that there might be a small commotion out here.
They accepted it...
so that we would let that girl stay
even though she belongs to the Celestial Dragons.
Captain of the Sun Pirates, Fisher Tiger!
You are guilty of two crimes.
I'm sure that you know what they are.
Raiding and desertion.
Were those gunshots?
They came from where the Boss went!
Something might have happened to the Boss.
Hey, look at the sea!
It's the Navy!  We've been surrounded -chuu!
Why is the Navy here?
We've been set up!
That kid was bait, planted by the Navy!
This means that Brother Ti and the rest of us
have fallen into their trap!
Open your eyes!  This is what humans are like!
Damn Navy!
Boss!  Boss Ti is in danger!
Arlong!
Hmm?
I'll let you handle this!  We'll go and help the Boss!
Sure, Brother Jinbe!
You'd better bring Big Brother back safe,
or I won't go easy on you!
Of course I will!  Let's go!
Yeah!
Arlong-san, it's hopeless!  The ship won't hold!
Abandon ship!
We're going to steal one of the Navy boats!
What's with his endurance?!
Why won't he go down
even after getting shot so many times?!
Unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
I will never forgive you for this, humans!
Fire.
Do you hear something, Mommy?
No.
Boss...
Boss!
Rear Admiral!  The Sun Pirates are here!
So that's him?  The infamous...
Jinbe?
Guys... forgive me.
Boss!
So you're the one responsible?!
This is for the sake of justice.
For the eradication of the Sun Pirates!
Damned Navy!
I'll take your head as well!
Go ahead, if you can!
We managed to rescue the Boss,
and finally escaped on a ship that Arlong had seized.
However...
Boss!
You refuse to accept a blood transfusion?!  Boss, what are you saying?!
You've lost too much blood!
If you don't get a transfusion soon, you'll...
You have a rare blood type!
No one in the crew is a match!
But... the blood reserves on this Navy ship...
are human... blood, right?!
That's right!  We have the same kind of blood as the humans!
We can use human blood!  You can still be saved!
So let's hurry and start the...
Don't!
I don't want to survive
with that kind of blood in my veins!
It's filthy blood!
The blood that has continued to scorn us fishmen!
Boss...
I will not be indebted to them!
I will not accept pity from them!
I will not succumb to the humans!
Big Brother!  What happened
between you and the humans?!
I didn't want... to tell you.
On my... last journey...
Your journey was quite long this time.
Yeah.  A lot of things happened.
You... What did you see on your latest voyage?
Humans.
Shortly after I departed...
I was imprisoned!
I spent several years in Mariejoa.
I was...
a slave!
What?!
Boss...
What I saw there was the madness of humankind.
I managed to escape with my life intact...
but I couldn't just ignore
all the other slaves I had seen.
Listen closely.
I've lived my life as I pleased...
and as a result...
I've severely hindered Queen Otohime's efforts.
But she... is right.
Anyone can see that peace would be for the best!
But... the only ones who can truly change our island...
are those like Koala.
The next generation, who don't know anything.
So, I beg of you!
Don't tell the people on our island anything!
Not about the tragedy that befell us,
nor about our anger toward the humans.
But, Big Broth-
Arlong!
There are...
plenty of kind-hearted humans... in this world.
We all know that.
And yet those of us who die only leave hatred in the world... Isn't that absurd?!
Even if I know it in my head...
there's a demon inside my heart...
that stops me!
My body rejects that blood!
I...
can no longer love the humans!
Boss!  Please don't say that!  Live!
Please!  You can still survive!
Boss!  No matter what you say,
in the eyes of all the slaves you freed,
you are their savior!
You're the hero of the fishmen, who accomplished so much!
I'm glad you think so.
You still have a long way to go.
What?!
Your moves are too soft.
With such a weak punch, you can't protect anyone.
Protect?!
Brother!
If nobody else wants to challenge me, then I will be the boss of the Fishman District from this day on!
I am Tiger!
Now that I am your leader, you may rest assured!
Your lives are my life!
I will protect my underlings!
Boss!
I will never forgive this!
Prepare yourself!
You're that fishman-
You're really noisy.
So you're Arlong?
Why did you come back?
So recklessly...
coming back to this place.
I came to slaughter the humans who shot Big Brother Ti!
I'm going to go to the island that sold us out too!
So this is your retaliation?
That's right!  Fisher Tiger died!
You inferior scumbags killed him!
Oh, really?  So he's dead?
Either way, you'll be coming with me.
Fisher Tiger's death outraged Arlong,
so he bared his fangs toward the humans he resented...
and was captured.
If the transfusion hadn't been refused, he could have survived!
If we'd had access to fishman blood, Fisher Tiger wouldn't have died!
You humans drove him to his death!
"After being refused a blood transfusion by humans,
Fisher Tiger, captain of the Sun Pirates, died."
It's not too far from the truth.
It was the humans' fault that he died, after all.
Arlong lied to the Navy.
The truth was much more cruel.
Resenting the humans that betrayed him,
the hero Tiger refused to have their blood in his veins.
Not to mention his past as a slave.
If the world found out about that, it would damage the Boss's honor.
Arlong would never reveal that.
Nyuu- Captain Jinbe!
Enemy ship sighted!
Even if the Boss is gone, we cannot turn back now!
Prepare for battle!  But remember, don't kill anyone!
Yeah!
I became known as Sea Knight Jinbe,
captain of the Sun Pirates.
I devoted myself to never-ending battle.
"I am writing this to you...
because I feel you deserve to know the whole truth."
"Captain of the Sun Pirates, Jinbe."
I've made up my mind.
So Tiger was forced to choose the path he took -jamon.
Now I understand the scream I heard from his heart that day.
I will be alright.  I will not lose!
We must live beneath the sun!
The day when we and the humans understand each other will definitely come!
Sign this form!  Declare your wish to emigrate, here!
I can't!  It's impossible, Otohime-sama!
Tiger-san saved all the slaves,
he didn't discriminate by race...
but then the humans simply abandoned him!
Just how are we supposed to understand one another?!
Not a single signature today, either.
Mother!
My children!
Mother, are you alright?
Are you alright?  Are you alright?
She's completely worn out.
Ah, my oasis of peace.
I am alright!
Mother.
Mother!
Let us make a promise...
for your future.
Day after day, Queen Otohime ran herself ragged.
Rescuing the victims of shipwrecks.
Hang in there!
Pirates again?
Help us.
Of course we will!
Let us carry them to the island!
Teaching the children of the island about the surface world.
This is a forest, the place I told you about yesterday where lots of trees grow together.
Forest?  The Sea Forest?
Collecting signatures.
Wait!
It will only take a second!
However...
Queen Otohime.
Oh!  It's you!
You're all people who have signed the form, right?
Today, we've got a favor to ask.
How many signatures have you gathered?
I have spent five years collecting these.
There are ten signatures on each sheet...
and I have about a hundred of them.
So one thousand supporters.
Fishman Island has five million people
so I was hoping for more, but...
Uh, we have a selfish request to make.
We want to withdraw our signatures,
which works out at about fifty of your sheets.
Haven't you heard?
Pirates came to the island the other day.
They plundered the town and fled the island.
Otohime-sama...
Otohime-sama!
Oh, children.  Have you come to hear more stories about the surface world?
Well... This paper I signed the other day.
Mom said to.
Mom said to!
What is it?
I did as you asked because you're the queen, but...
The humans are the problem.
We've had enough...
of your speeches, too.
I'm tired of them.
Welcome home, Mother!
I gave it my all today as well!
I'm home, my little angels!
I went a little overboard,
so can you leave me alone just for today?
Liars!  Every single one of you!
O-Otohime-sama!
You're broadcasting to the whole country!
Shaddup... ya damn Ministah of da Left!
You... Have you been drinking?!
Shaddup.  Ah ain't... Ah ain't drunk!
Yes, you are!
What's that?
Queen Otohime's voice?
Listen up, y'all!
We... We can live anywhere in the ocean.
In this vast, vast ocean.
On the dark, dark ocean floor.
Why do we all live in this one place?
Otohime-sama...
Isn't it because there's a tiny bit of light and air here?
On the surface, the whole world is bathed in sunlight!
There is a vast sky above.
Why do children sneak out to look at Sabaody Park?
Out there in the world...
there are so many wonderful places!
We should be able to go to all of those places.
Aren't we just making up empty excuses,
and convincing ourselves that we should give up?!
Be brave...
and strive for the thing we all want the most!
Your Majesty.
If the humans are an obstacle standing in our way...
then let's overcome that obstacle together!
If we do, then maybe
the children living on Fishman Island today...
can change their future.
At least a little bit!
Have your wounds healed?
I ran into some serious trouble.
I never thought you'd get beaten this badly.
Arlong, who was imprisoned
in Impel Down the other day, was nothing.
The truly fierce one is Jinbe.
You don't see that kind of strength every day.
It's far too dangerous to let him roam free.
Unclear Justice
Become one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?  Me?!
Your bounty's 250 million beli!
The Government must have realized that you'll become a huge threat to them if they don't do this!
So they're beginning to learn their lesson!
Just turn down their offer
and become even more notorious,
Captain Jinbe -chuu!
No, I plan to accept their offer.
Huh?!
I heard about the offer to join the Warlords.
If I join the Seven Warlords,
the Government will pardon my crew.
Aladdin and others who want to quit being pirates
will be able to live in this country in peace.
More importantly, if I accept this title, maybe fishmen can get a bit closer to joining the World Government.
For the sake of Her Majesty,
after I've caused her so much trouble.
Yes, and I'm grateful.
Though she's in a pretty bad way right now.
This is the late Tiger's wish.
I believe this is a step toward
the liberation and freedom of fishmen!
However, there is
one worrisome detail regarding the pardon...
Arlong-san!
Arlong!
Arlong-san has returned!  He's back!
If there's something you want to say,
then spit it out, Arlong!
Joining the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
eh, Brother Jinbe?
In other words,
you're becoming a dog of the human Government!
Have you forgotten Brother Ti's words?!
Stop letting grudges and hatred control your life!
You've gotten soft, Brother.
I'm sure that becoming your underling would be the safest option for me,
but I'm not gonna do that!
Big Brother died!
I will be reforming my old Arlong Crew.
And I'll be taking my brethren with me.
This is farewell.
Arlong, you...
If you want to stop me that bad...
then this is your chance.
Just kill me!
A-Arlong-san!
If you can't, then that means I'm free!
I am the fury of fishmankind!
Enough of your insolence!
Jinbe-san!
Fine by me!
Stop this!
Don't let it get to you, Jinbe.
You grew up in the Fishman District together.
You're like brothers.
No matter what happens,
you wouldn't be able to kill him.
Why can't that fool understand...
Brother Ti's real intentions?!
It doesn't matter where he goes.
If he gets too violent, the Navy will take action.
But if they don't, and he does get out of control,
we'll go stop him ourselves.
For certain.
Sheesh!  We're also going back to
doing our own thing, Captain Jinbe.
Macro, you...
Let him do whatever he wants.
So long!
Damn, that freakishly strong bastard!
Hachi, let's go.
The Sun Pirates...
split into three groups,
and everybody went their own way.
A ship drifts to Fishman Island, carrying a shipwrecked Celestial Dragon,
who see fishmen as mere slaves.
Otohime decides to follow this Celestial Dragon up to the surface.
After her return, her dream is soon to be realized,
only to be shattered by a single gunshot.
Next time, on One Pace:
The Shipwrecked Celestial Dragon!
A Bullet that Seals the Future