Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Move!
I will not!
Luffy-chin... Boss Jinbe...
Come on, we just gonna stand around?
Um, excuse me, my father's life is...
I said move, so move already!
I'm going to kick their asses,
even if I have to go through you!
How many times are you going to make me say it?
I told you to wait!
Listen to what I have to say!
What kind of relationship do we have?
We're friends.
That's right.
For years now, it's been a struggle for fishmen and humans to create a simple relationship like ours.
The reason why I told you not to fight with Hody...
is because I didn't want you to start a reckless fight.
Don't act rashly!
If you just beat up Hody, then the people of this island will see you as nothing but another heartless human.
Instead of that,
please become the hero who saved Fishman Island!
Hero?
Don't wanna!
Whaaat?!
We're pirates!
I love heroes, but I don't wanna be one!
Do you even know what it means to be a hero?
Hmm?
Well, think about the meat, right?
Pirates eat meat at huge feasts,
but heroes have to take the meat and share it with people.
I wanna eat the meat!
What kind of logic is that?
Fine.  I'll give you meat, so just do what I tell you!
Okay.
It's that easy?!
To put it simply, I'll have you help me.
As long as you can do that, it'll be fine.
Help you?
Yes, first Megalo and I will
intentionally get captured and infiltrate their position.
And then, when I have their attention,
one of you will stealthily
sneak out of Megalo's stomach.
From inside his stomach?
And then you'll get the Celestial Dragons' form.
What form?
Oh right, Luffy was asleep,
so he barely heard a word of Jinbe's story.
Well, it's a very important piece of paper that
Queen Otohime risked her life to get ten years ago.
The other thing we need is
the key to the King's chains.
Stealing those things...
Do we have someone who can do that?
Leave the theft to me.
I could do it... with Robin's help.
Quite.
So after you've freed the King, I'll ask Luffy-kun to help me.
And then you'll make a grand entrance out of Megalo's stomach.
Everyone will understand that
Luffy-kun and I are working together.
The Princess can wait in a safe location
outside the plaza, ready to take the letter.
Then she can escape with the King and the others,
once they have been freed.
While that is happening, the rest of you
will hurry to Ryuuguu Palace and release our allies.
Once that's done, hurry back to the plaza.
As for how you free our allies in the palace...
Come up with something yourself.
That isn't a plan!
Super-leave it to me!
I've got the Sunny,
so I'll be sure to come up with that something.
If we follow this plan,
how do you think the citizens will react?
You two?
Jinbe-san is respected by both the citizens of the island and the villagers from the Fishman District.
That's right, if everyone sees that Boss trusts Luffy-chin with his life while they save the King,
then I'm sure that everyone will cheer for Luffy-chin!
Straw Hat.
Luffy-sama.
I'm only doing it because
you're the one who's asking, Jinbe!
Being cheered on by everyone will just distract me!
That doesn't happen very often, after all.
With mermaid ladies cheering for me, I could defeat the devil himself!
Thanks.
Well then, it appears to be settled.
All that's left is to do it!
Are you still worried about something?
What should we name this operation?
We don't need a bloody name!
Alright, let's hurry!
Straw Hat Luffy is a human pirate that's on our side, right?
Princess Shirahoshi asked him for help!
He's come with Boss Jinbe to save this country!
Straw Hat!
It sounds like you've become quite popular...
but you shouldn't get cocky
just because you snatched the King away from us!
You're still just human pirates!
100,000 vs. 10!
The Straw Hats' Explosive Moves
Mermaid Princess-san, you are so lovely.
Excuse me, but you wouldn't let me see your panties, would-
Cut that out!  She's the Mermaid Princess.
Okay, can I settle for Nami-san's?
Settle?!
Well, it looks like everyone's finally here.
They totally ignored you!
I said it quietly intentionally so they couldn't hear me!
Nami-swan!  I was the one who saved those idiots!
Have you fallen for me?
Yeah, whatever.
What an idiot, we made it to the exit by ourselves.
Yep.
That's because I saved you!
Pappagg, you saved them?
Here you go.
The Celestial Dragons' form.
Thank you very much, every one of you.
This is Fishman Island's greatest hope,
it's my mother's legacy.
But then again, Weak-hoshi is bit of a liability.
It certainly wasn't part of my plan
for her to be captured,
but I'm not sure how to get her out of here.
Luffy-sama, are you talking about me?
Yeah.
Just that, up until now you've been calling me, "Wimp."
Yeah, I didn't know all the details.
You're not as much of a wimp as I thought you were.
So from now on, you're...
Weak-hoshi!
Anybody can react with anger and hatred
when they are faced with trouble.
Just like that man who was insulting you.
A wimp would never have the strength
to hold all of that hatred inside of themselves.
That's exactly right.
It must have been incredibly trying
for Princess Shirahoshi over all those years.
My sincerest apologies.  This is all happening
because I kept the truth to myself.
That's fine.  You should be proud.
We mustn't let the hatred get the better of us.
Those great people wouldn't want us to.
Don't tell the people on our island anything!
Don't lose yourself in anger and hatred because of me.
You planted a small seed in your heart.
We can hope that the seed
will grow and cover the island.
If a day comes when
everyone thinks the same way as you do...
then there would be no more strife between fishmen and humans,
and the cycle of revenge would disappear.
I don't want to disrespect those long years that you endured...
Alone day after day,
protecting that seed with your life.
But now, we'd like your permission to help protect that seed.
Y-Y-Yes!
Thank you so very much!
You're not a wimp, but you sure are a crybaby!
Straw Hat!  Go get 'em!
Vander Decken wasn't of any use at all.
He was supposed to eliminate Shirahoshi.
Captain Hody!
The legendary Mermaid Princess with her troubling power...
All he had to do was eliminate Shirahoshi quickly.
Hell, and now I've been played for a fool.
Jinbe... I should have figured it out
when you let yourself be captured so easily.
You've really become a human-lover!
You're the type of person I hate the most!
Fisher Tiger and your sworn brother Arlong
were both raised in the Fishman District with you,
and both of them were killed by humans.
But instead of avenging your brother's death, you've gone and made friends with the one who killed him!
You've become even worse than Neptune,
you damned coward!
When I become the king of this island,
everything will change.
This year's World Council Meeting will be the perfect opportunity.
I'll go to Mariejoa and slaughter
all the human kings of the world.
Then the curtain will rise on
our feared undersea kingdom!
We'll drag all the humans of the world
down to the sea floor, and make them our slaves!
Eventually there will be no one left
to oppose fishmankind!
It will be the same in the world of piracy.
All of the pirates will grovel
in front of the New Fishman Pirates!
Look at this!
These are the faces of the pirates who know my strength.
This is your future.
Straw Hat, in the end I will be the one
worthy of being called Pirate King.
Pirate King?
What can a mere ten pirates do?
A mere breath from me is enough to send you flying.
I've got one hundred thousand!
Kill them, New Fishman Pirates!
There's one hundred thousand of them!
How can we fight that many?!
It's impossible!
Nothing good has ever come
from being friends with you guys.
It looks like we may be crushed
before we even get a chance to fight.
Crushed!?  Too scary!
So, one hundred thousand enemies...
It certainly is an astonishing amount.
It's enough to make your eyes pop out.
But then, I don't have any eyes to pop out.
What's one hundred thousand enemies?!  Let's get it started!
Easy for you to say!
You're using us as human shields!
So my time has finally come.
Super Armored Me!
Now, come at me from wherever you want!
We have ten people...
so each of us have to take out ten thousand.
Superior numbers doesn't always mean strength.
It's not like they're Navy elites or anything.  You're cowering for nothing.
Who's cowering, you shitty moss-head?!
You are, you little nosebleed chef!
Hey, Luffy...
L-Luffy-kun.
Luffy-sama.
I'll take his 400 million head!
No, I will!
You think I'll let you?
Kill them.
What happened?!
He took out a hell of a lot of pirates without even lifting a finger!
Hey!  Pull yourselves together!
Dammit!  He dropped half of us in an instant!
Fifty thousand.... just like that?!  What the hell did he do?!
What was that?
What?  What happened?
You can really do it, can't you, Straw Hat Boy?
The Straw Hat pirate did that?
You're amazing, Straw Hat!
Was that haki?
He has come so far in just two years?
The Color of the Conqueror.  He had it all this time?
If he wasn't at least this strong,
then I'd have to become the new captain.
You're amazing, Luffy-sama.
You're Hody, right?  I have to kick your ass.
If you wanna go around and become the king of
some countries, then that's none of my business...
But there's only room for one Pirate King!
He may have just taken out fifty thousand men...
but...
we still have fifty thousand left!
The Straw Hat Pirates won't stop until they've shattered our ambitions!
They are our sworn enemies!
And Jinbe...
is the embodiment of
the worst possible future for fishmankind.
One where Otohime's dreams have become reality
and we coexist with human filth!
Yeah!  Who cares about Straw Hat?!
He's just a human, after all!
As for Jinbe... we must kill the traitor to fishmankind!
Luffy, fifty thousand is going too far.
You took out too many.
Oh?  Sorry.
What're you so fired up over?
I'm gonna take thirty thousand.  You got that, Moss-Head?
Shut it, Mister Nosebleed.
Our race is superior!
Time to show them that!
Let's go!
I don't care how many thousands of you there are!  Bring it on!
Here he comes!
What happened to his hand?!
Right.  Shall we get started too?
I will not let you destroy my Mermaid Paradise!
Will they surrender, or will they be destroyed?
Fishman Island... There are vital pieces of the world's history in this country!
It is not something you should casually destroy!
It's so hot.
Perfect weather for a concert!
An army of fifty thousand...
This is an ideal stage to reveal my surprises!
Surprises?
What are you talking about, Franky?
The Sunny's got some new weapons!  Two of them!
Anyone want to try them?
New weapons?!
If you think you can protect that giant mermaid...
when she's sitting out in the middle of the plaza...
then go ahead and try!
Whoa... Guess I didn't have to worry.
Captain Hody's insanely powerful Uchimizu...
He deflected it with an Uchimizu of his own!
That man is a monster too!
I don't know what you did to gain such power...
but your Fishman Karate lacks discipline!
He's the first fishman to join
the Seven Warlords of the Sea, after all.
I heard that his bounty shot up to more than 400 million after he quit being a Warlord!
What chance do we have against someone like that?!
Don't just stand there jabbering, bring it on!
If you're going to take the Princess's life
then you'll have to beat all of us first!
Attack, Steel Shell Squadron!
Yeah!
Black Rope - Grand Dragon Twist/Tornado
He sliced through the steel shells like they were fruit!
W-What was that huge attack?
The Grim Reaper's scythe or something?
It's not over!
It won't stop!
It's a tornado that slices anything it touches!
Run!  It'll cut you to pieces!
How far is it gonna chase us?!
All the way to the ends of hell.
Use your heads, idiots!
Increase your bubble's altitude!
We'll attack from the sky!
Kill Princess Shirahoshi!
You're all gonna get skewered!
Get them, Harisenbon!
Oh, it's Commander Harisenbon and his men.
The Sea Urchin Spine Squadron!
Skewer that man with the fancy footwork!
A Thousand Needles
You've got nowhere to run now!
Sanji-san, watch out!
Why are you so calm?
Hey!
Thinking back on it, I almost feel nostalgic...
Sanji-kyun!
I ran.
Wait, Sanji-chan!
Like hell I will, you ass!
But I brought my favorite dress for you!
Come here!
You don't have to be shy!
I'm telling you, I'll never wear that thing!
And who's shy?!
On rainy days...
On snowy days...
Even on days of lightning...
I ran, and ran.
Take out the man with the fancy footwork!
You silly thing...
Did you think we'd never catch up to you?
Sanji-kyun!
Can I really let these guys get the better of me?
Until one day, when I was finally cornered...
I ran...
Huh?  He's not here.
And ran...
Sanji-kyun!
I...
was running...
across the sky!
Up there!
Amazing!  Sanji is flying!
Just like those other guys!
Moon Step
That's the CP9's Geppou technique.
Hey, you guys!
What?!  He's flying!
If you have any business with Shirahoshi-chan, you're gonna have to go through me!
Even crying children are hushed when they see me...
I am your knight!
Sanji-chin-sama!
That arrogant bastard!
Now to cook the small-fry.
Let's finish this -dosun!
Bombarding Squad!
Aim for Shirahoshi!
I'm afraid I cannot allow that.
How could you try to hurt the Mermaid Princess,
who is beloved by the whole world?
What's going on?  It got dark all of a sudden.
Welcome to festival night!
What?
Are we...
dreaming or something?
Now, launch the fireworks!
This is great!
It's so beautiful!
Hey!  I told you to aim for the Princess -bokan!
But...
Dosun-san, we're at such a fun festival.
Alright!  You have already been cut.
Feet?!
Sorry for this.
It's really noisy outside.
What's going on?
Hey, you two get out of here!  It's too cramped!
You don't even care about the new weapons,
do you?  You get out!
I got in because it's too scary outside!
I don't want to be left outside either!
Franky, can we use the weapons yet?
Don't be so impatient.
Now, it's time for the show!
I'm starting to get excited too!
Hey wait... I'm supposed to be steering this thing.
It got bigger!
What's going on?
Now, the Sunny Soldier Dock's new weapons...
So excited!
What's gonna happen?
...will be unveiled!
Lethal Poison Squad, go!
Yeah!
Giant feet, giant hands, or whatever...
A single hit from our poisonous weapons
will take them down!
Now wait just a minute!
Soldier Dock System...
Channel Four!
The Black Rhino...
FR-U 4!
That's so awesome!  A rhinobike!
What is that thing?  It looks powerful!
What was that about poisonous weapons?
What is that?!
You think they'll work on this steel monster?  Just go ahead and try to stab it!
Well?  Super cool, isn't it?
Stop them!
Right... Fight steel with steel!
Leave it to me!
Take this!  I'm gonna flatten you!
Hey!
The New Number, Channel Five!
Brachio Tank 5 has arrived!
There it is!  A dinosaur!  I wanna try it!
Amazing!
Did you see my bombardment skills?
Looks like it's got plenty of other features, too.
But... he's supposed to be a shipwright... isn't he?
Commander Chopper reporting in!
A group of enemies spotted at nine o'clock!
Fire!
Commander, you're so cool!
Keep fighting, damn you!
Amazing... Those guys are truly amazing!
There's only ten of them, yet they're fighting
an army of a hundred thousand like it was nothing!
Straw Hat!
We're counting on you!
Boss Jinbe!
They're all getting carried away.
Show yourself, Kraken!
It's huuuge!
They're just ten people.  Flatten them!
That'll be the end of it!
Oh no!  He summoned the legendary beast,
the Kraken!
Get out of the way!
It doesn't matter how strong the Straw Hats are,
if that thing smashes them they're dead for sure!
Alright, it's the Kraken!  He's the captain's slave!
He's freakishly strong!
It's time you learn how terrifying deep sea creatures can be!
Hey, isn't that...
What are you doing?!
Don't hesitate.  I brought you here from the North Pole!
You're my slave!
Serve your master!
You can do it, can't you?!
P-P-Please wait!
Retreat!
Hey, Surume!
It's me!
I made you my pet earlier.  We're friends, right?
He did it!
Luffy-sama!
That tickles!  C-Cut it out, Surume!
What?!
Alright... Surume!  Let's get going!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Stop, Kraken!
You stupid octopus!
Go get 'em, Surume!
Help me... Captain...
Kraken, over there!
Damn it, what's going on?!
The Kraken is acting all friendly with Straw Hat!
Listen up, Surume.
You stay here and protect Weak-hoshi!
I can't believe you're friends with the Kraken.
The relationships you have always take me by surprise!
Really?
Uhm... I'm very pleased to meet you, Surume-sama.
There's still plenty of them left.
Right!  Let's do this!