Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Run!
Huh?!
What is this?!
Everyone is taking evasive action!
The General From the Future Land and
The Crisis of Fishman Island's Destruction
They must be afraid of our military strength!
Now then, let's target the enemy commanders while we have the chance!
Forward!
Hey, Commander Chopper!
The vehicle is trembling!  There must be something wrong!
It's a pitfall!
Serves you right!
How'd you like that?!
Sure-Kill Daruma Drop
Ow...
I just used my fangs to dig the ground full of holes!
Hey!  What's going on?!
Usopp?!  Chopper?!
Now, I'm gonna drop that idiot on the bike as well...
Oh, crap!
It's a pitfall!
Is he a complete bonehead?!
H-Hey!  Are you alright?!
Damn you!  This is super-unforgivable!
Everyone out!
Why?!
Hey!  What are you doing, Franky?!
Why'd you throw the tank commander out?!
Because this is a one-man vehicle!
Time to transform!
Hentai: Transform or Pervert
You already are a pervert!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Stand by!
A transformation!
I'm not done yet!
Brachio Tank 5!
Head Change!
Brachio Tank 5!  Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Docking!
What?!  Docking?!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Alriiiiiight!
What the hell is that?!
Awesome!
Yay!  Yay!
It's the mecha combination of our dreams!
Vegapunk, you genius I never met.
I saw the theoretical design that you had sketched...
and spent two grueling years of trial and error working on it.
By making use of
the shape-adapting alloy, Wapometal,
I've made it a reality!
D-Don't be fooled by his bluff!
So strong!
Don't be impressed yet!
Have a good look...
at the Sword of the Plunderer!
Fransword!
A sword!
Ashimoto: Soles
Attacking from below?!
That's cheap!  It's too dangerous!
Now that you're in the air,
my shoulder cannons will attack you!
Shoulder cannons?!
You're the one firing them?!
Nevertheless...
You're so cool!
Damn!
What a tricky guy!
Omomi: Weight
We're being crushed!
You're so cool, General!
How is that cool?!
What is this?
Have I found some weaklings?
Weak?  How rude!
I'm just a scaredy cat, that's all!
Be careful of gusts.
Do you understand now?
This is the weather science of Weatheria.
Don't underestimate it!
Eh?  Huh?
Where'd Chopper go?
Get him!
Damn it... I was thrown out of the tank.
Guess I've got no choice but to fight.
But there's no reason to fear!
I'm not the same weakling that I used to be!
Bamboo Javelin-Grove
Heracles'n-sensei!
I spent two years in that forest, fighting for my life.
I couldn't drop my guard for a second!
I won't forget that!
Now it begins!
The second chapter of Usopp the Man's Adventure!
I'll rig the entire plaza with pitfalls!
They can bring robots or whatever they want.
When they're trapped in a hole, it's all over for them!
What?
I can hear someone else digging through the earth...
Daruma-san went flying!
W-Who are you?!
It's me!
I'm good at digging through the earth too!
Chopper!
Awesome!  You've learned how to turn into a stag beetle?!
I'm not a beetle!
I improved my transformation points over the past two years.
Now only one of my transformations needs a Rumble Ball.
I can change into all the other forms whenever I want!
You cheeky coral bastard!
I'll tear you to shreds!
This isn't coral, they're horns!
And I...
am a cheeky monster!
How many did you kill?
Z-Zero...
Kraken!
Well done, I didn't think you had it in you.
They believed you and you captured Shirahoshi.
Now crush her!
Your brothers still live in the North Pole.
I know exactly where they are.
We could kill them any time we like.
You are legendary creatures...
so even your corpses should fetch a high price,
don't you think?
Are you telling me that's what you want...
Kraken?
Unbelievable... He's been forcing him to obey
by threatening his siblings?
I'm telling you for the last time!  Crush Shirahoshi!
Surume-sama!  I-I can't breathe!
Surume!
You became his slave... to protect your siblings?
I see, of course you want to protect them.
Are they your younger siblings?  Or older?
Let me protect them too!
Here comes Straw Hat!
Kill him!
You can't -dogon!
Leave it to us -hi!
Straw Hat!
I won't let you get to our captain -hi!
You're mine!
I won't let you...
Get in his way!
Stop Straw Hat!
Huh?  He disappeared!
What?!
Now I'm really fired up!
Oh no!
That is...
the ship of promise...
Noah!
W-Why...
Why is it moving?!
Who'd do this... and how?!
T-This is terrible!
What is it, Father?
Yes, this is strange, but why are you so upset?
It's just some old wreckage.  It isn't important.
You're wrong.
We mustn't let anything happen to that ship -jamon!
The ship must not be moved
before its time has come -jamon!
Captain Hody!
He took so many Energy Steroids
that he turned into a monster, but still...
N-No, look!
Straw Hat!
He sure is tough.
Do you have any idea what Fishman Karate can do?!
He took his head right off!
Alright!  And it only took one hit!
That won't work on me...
'cause I'm rubber!
Compared to Jinbe's attacks, that didn't even itch!
That's right!  It's because you rely on fake power!
Head Armament
Steel Shell Squadron!
You fool!  Your head's gonna shatter!
Bell
Steel lost to his head!
None of them are hitting?!
Does he know where every single one is going?!
You're amazing, Luffy-sama!
That's the Haki of Perception!
Captain Hody!
Luffy-sama... How strong are you?
Straw Hat Luffy is amazing!
So this is the power of a world-famous pirate?
Whaaat?!
T-That's...
the Noah, from the Fishman District!
Why is the Noah above Fishman Island?!
It's clearly falling toward the plaza!
It's going to break the bubble around the island!
Fishman Island will be destroyed without the bubble!
We'll all be washed away!
What's that?!
Noah?!
It's super-huge!
If that ship hits us, the entire island will be crushed!
Who's steering it?!
No, the Noah shouldn't even have the power to move!
What is that?!
It's huge!
I don't know what's happening, but we're doomed!
I wonder, if we're all crushed at the same time...
will the ocean become red?
Don't jinx us by saying such horrible things!
Evacuate!
Flee to the waters outside the island!
E-Everyone...
What is that?
Owie... I slipped.
You're... Decken's subordinate, Wadatsumi!
Cap'n Vander Decken!
I fell off!
Pwease stop da ship!
I don' wanna die!
Decken?!  What is going on?!
Captain Hody!
Are you alright?!
Uh, is this... part of the plan?!
It looks like Decken is moving that ship!
Be quiet, you useless worms!
Damn Straw Hat...
Huh?  How is he still standing?
I even attacked him using the Color of Arms.
Decken, is it?  That insane pirate!
This wasn't part of the plan!
Shirahoshi!
Accept... my love!
Cap'n Decken!  What 'bout me?!
Wadatsumi?
It's no longer possible to save you!
You will become a sacrifice for the death
of Shirahoshi, just like the rest of Fishman Island!
No way!
We're done for!  The bubble won't hold!
This is the end!
Hey, where'd Princess Shirahoshi go?
She's gone!
What?  The Princess!  Princess Shirahoshi!
What?  Shirahoshi disappeared?!
I-Impossible!
I'm up here!
Princess Shirahoshi!
When did she...
Mermaid Princess?!
Shirahoshi!  What is she doing up there?!
Basically, that ship is flying at Shirahoshi!
The woman I love!
M-My life is your target, is it not?!
If you just want to take my life...
then the people of Ryuuguu Kingdom should not be caught up in it.
Please, leave them alone!
I am right here!
Princess!  Shirahoshi-sama!
So basically, that insane Decken-guy...
was planning to crush the whole island, and us with it.
He betrayed me!
Ah, she's going to sacrifice herself for us!
Isn't there anything we can do to help her?
Oh, how...
Oh, how completely beautiful you are, Shirahoshi!  Even your heart shines with it!
You're trying to avert this disaster
and save your country all by yourself, Shirahoshi?
Shirahoshi!
Shira... hoshi.
You truly are
worthy of becoming Vander Decken the Ninth's wife!
Die at the height of your beauty, and live on forever in my heart!
Shirahoshi!
Your Highness!
That Weak-hoshi...
Even after I told her to stay close to me!
Straw Hat is...
Captain Hody!
H-Huh?  Hody-san isn't here!
Look up in the sky!  There he is!
Under Noah?!
You're completely insane, Vander Decken.
However, this is a great trump card!
That bastard... How dare he harm Shirahoshi-chan?!
Sanji, wait!
I'll jump up there!  You take care of the plaza!
Got it!
But anyway Luffy, the ship is underwater!
Do you think there's water inside the ship too, Jinbe?
I'm not sure, but Decken is a Devil Fruit user...
so we can assume that there must be air in there somewhere since he can make the ship move.
If you're going to go, take this.
It's a coral that creates a bubble.
Okay!
Okay, I leave my beloved Shirahoshi-chan to you!
I'm gonna fling you, Luffy!
Do it!