Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Hody's Dark Secret!
The Straw Hats' Arrival
We're almost at the plaza.  Hurry, Megalo!
Father...
Hey, it is me -jamon!
Boss Jinbe-sama!  Megalo!
You're alright after all?
Father!
No way...
Our gallery has grown quite a bit.
You fiend!
Now, this is a nice view!
Prince Manboshi!
Prince Ryuuboshi!
Prince Fukaboshi!
What did those pirates do? {Literally "the subordinates of that pirate crew", but that strikes me as kind of redundant.}
The Princes were wiping the floor with them!
But then the situation suddenly turned on its head!
I haven't rampaged enough -zugon!
Muhi, you're too fired up!
You're gonna turn me into a grilled squid!
The army's soldiers, the ministers, and the Royal Family...
Now, there's nobody left in the country
who can fight us!
What outrageous power.
Please forgive me, Father.
Don't say that!  Their power isn't real -jamon!
But they can still use it
to take the country from us.
Captain Hody, let's execute them!
Roast them!
No, skewer them!
Those royals wanted to coexist with the humans!
They have no pride!
Give them a cruel death!
Put them up for display at the gallery!
Execute them!
Execute them!  Execute them!
Silence.
Decken's crew still haven't
sent word that Shirahoshi is dead.
If I can't lure her here, this will all be meaningless!
Keep your hands off our sister!  She's not a warrior!
What threat does she pose to you?!
Do you think I don't know?
The one I want to get rid of the most...
is the legendary mermaid,
who possesses that most troublesome power.
Hody!
Captain Hody!
We've caught them!
Princess Shirahoshi and Jinbe fell for our trap!
Shirahoshi!
Father!  Brothers!
What luck!
The two people I feared the most, captured at the same time!
This is almost too good to be true!
I really am so sorry.
Just because I fell for their trap, even you ended up...
What's done is done.  Don't worry about the past.
So you came after all, Jinbe.
I used to like you,
back when you were more ruthless.
What happened to you, Hody?  You look different.
It's Boss Jinbe!
I thought he left the island after he resigned from the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I heard that Princess Shirahoshi
had been kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy...
Did Boss Jinbe rescue her?
Alright, we have everyone we need.
It was much easier than I thought it would be.
Now, the only ones left are the Straw Hats, and I don't know what they'll do.
I'm guessing that they're at a loss,
looking for a way inside Ryuuguu Palace.
Even if they come here,
enraged by the death of their companions...
we'll be ready for them.
I've been capturing human slaves
on the ocean floor for the past month...
Thirty thousand of them! {...Seriously? THIRTY THOUSAND in the past month? Is he really saying that an average of a thousand people travel to Fishman Island daily? :/}
And heavily armed fishmen, all seventy thousand of them!
I-I can't believe this!
They've moved here from the closed-off Fishman District.
In all, we've got a hundred thousand outlaws!
There are some women and children around the plaza, but they can't fight.
We'll take care of them after things have settled down.
Of course, the number of human slaves
will rapidly grow soon!
But for now,
we have a hundred thousand new citizens!
The ones who have disgraced our species
will be forced to surrender their houses to you.
Die or run away... They should decide quickly!
You're causing quite a ruckus out here in public.
How undignified.
You shouldn't let yourself get carried away like this...
Hody Jones.
Long time, no see.
What do you want?
I'd like to say something to you,
since you seem to think you've already won.
Madame Shyarly.
I saw that a certain man
would destroy Fishman Island...
in my predictions.
We might end up destroying it.
So you saw me?
No.
The man I saw destroying the island...
was Straw Hat Luffy.
What are you trying to say?
That it won't be you!
One thing is certain...
Somebody holds the fate
of Fishman Island in their hands.
But Hody, I know this much...
It is not you.
I see!  Madame's predictions are never wrong!
In other words,
the future where Hody reigns over this island...
has no chance of happening!
Madame Shyarly!
Madame!
How could he?!
Ridiculous.  What were you implying, Shyarly?
Are you trying to get back at me?!
I'm different from your brother.
True, when I was a kid, everyone in
Fishman District looked up to your brother, Arlong.
But we have gained power!
By now, the mark of the Arlong Pirates is just an empty symbol to unite us.
Arlong's name is completely unnecessary now!
The only one who can crush this country down to its foundation, and recreate it...
is me!
I have the power to do that!
Behold, the size of this mob!
This is my strength!
My plan has been in the works for ten years!
Shall I tell you...
who killed the beloved Queen of Ryuuguu Kingdom?
Your beloved Otohime was killed...
by me!
What?!
Impossible!
Then...
what about that human?
You're fools for not realizing it!
A few days before that day ten years ago...
I don't know who you are,
but if the pay's good, I'll gladly take any job.
For real?!
That's half of your payment.
I'll give you the rest after you've finished the job.
Alright, I accept.
Even this is enough to keep me drinking for a while.
So?  What kind of job is it?
It's an easy job.  Even a kid could do it.
But you have to make sure that nobody notices you!
And then, on that day...
Get back!  They're going up in flames! {Copy-paste from 546. Just this line. For some reason the rest of them appear to be different from that episode...}
Put out the flames!
Run!
Protect the Royal Family!
Hurry and put out the flames!
Otohime-sama's been shot!
Hey!  Give me the rest of my money already!
I burned the signatures, just like I promised!
I won't bother you after this, so just give me the money!
What's going on?!
You foolish human.
Damn it... Damn it to hell!
A human...
killed our country's queen!
Queen Otohime's killer was human!
Hody, you filth!
Father!
Stop it, Hody!
She was quite a nuisance.
Right, Shirahoshi?!
Claiming that revenge against humans was evil...
Preaching all around the island
that we should get along with humans...
And that woman almost realized her dreams.
I hated every single thing about her!
No, she was the kind of person whose influence wouldn't fade even if I killed her!
But to me, your mother...
was someone who just had to die!
Stop!  Stop hurting the princess!
This is too cruel!
I knew.
Shirahoshi!
What?!
W-What?  What happened?!
My heartache from being rejected will never fade.
Wh-Wh-Wha?!
It started moving!
W-What's going on?
Run!
I sent Noah flying straight toward Shirahoshi!
Whaaaaat?!
Noah is half the size of Fishman Island itself!
Which means, if Noah collides with the island...
it won't just kill Shirahoshi,
it'll make the entire island crumble!
There is nowhere to run or hide!
Shirahoshi will live in my heart for all time!
May the entire island perish!
Farewell, my beloved Shirahoshi!
Farewell, Fishman Island!
You knew that I killed your mother?
What nonsense is this, Shirahoshi?!
Father!  Are you alright?
Hang in there!
Shirahoshi...
A few years after the incident, Megalo told me in secret.
Megalo?
Megalo used to be the pet of the Neptune Army.
He saw everything that happened that day.
In that case, why didn't you tell us,
Princess Shirahoshi?!
If I did...
people would probably end up hating Hody-sama.
If that happened, Mother would've been so sad.
It was the final promise I made with my mother.
Whoever the killer was...
We mustn't be angry and we mustn't hate them!
So, whoever the culprit is...
please don't be angry for me.
Don't lose yourself in anger and hatred because of me.
Shirahoshi... You...
No way... So you...
In order to stay true
to Mother's wishes from ten years ago...
you've been bearing the weight of the truth
alone inside Koukaku Tower all this time?!
She doesn't resent the person who killed her mother?!
Even if it was her mother's dying wish, that's practically impossible!
What a respectful brave daughter!
Who else could do something like that?
Don't laugh, you scum!
How could I not laugh at this?!
Right, Megalo?
If you'd just attracted everyone's attention and raised the alarm when it happened,
you might have revealed that I was the assassin.
I'm amazed that you were able to stay silent.
And then you chose this boneheaded brat
to reveal the truth to!
Had you told anyone else,
my plans would have been ruined before they began!
Listen close, Shirahoshi.
In the real world, we call that "Idiocy".
Because you refused to hate me, this kingdom will fall.
Because of you...
your father, your brothers,
you, and your people will all die...
Shirahoshi!
He's wrong!  Don't listen to him, Your Highness!
What you did was not a mistake!
What else could it be?!
Your Highness!
Princes!
Stop!  Please stop this!
Father!  Brothers!
How pathetic!
Hey, hand me a sword.
Jinbe and Shirahoshi, the two people
I was worried about, have been captured.
There's no reason to keep to the schedule anymore.
We will now commence the execution...
of these foolish Royals!
Do it!  Kill them!
Execute them!
Execute them!  Execute them!  Execute them!
The Great Knight Neptune... is really going to be killed!
This is hell on Earth!
Our enemies are a hundred thousand outlaws...
This country is done for!
Madame Shyarly!
Children...
Hey...
That pirate with the hat...
When is he going to come and destroy the island?!
Huh?!  When?!
I don't know.
My predictions only show what will happen...
It could be tomorrow, or a year from now.
I think he should do it now.
If he started wreaking havoc right now, we'd be in trouble...
but the bad guys would also be in trouble, right?!
I want him to come now too!  I don't want the King to die!
Me too!
The children are right.
I think it'd be for the best, too.
Yes... Yes...
Hey!  Straw Hat Luffy!
If you want to destroy the island, then come do it now!
Wreak havoc here, right now!
Yeah!  Can you hear us, Straw Hat?!
If you're still on the island, then come now!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!  Straw Hat!  Straw Hat!
Unbelievable.
They're literally clutching at straws!
Shyarly's predictions have always been accurate
but, just this once, it seems to have been a big lie.
Such futile shouts.
Time to drag those delusional fools back to reality.
Hear me, citizens!
Now, the former King Neptune's...
execution will commence!
Father...
Watch closely...
as the former King Neptune's head flies!
How regrettable...
Die!
Please, protect my father!
Luffy-sama!
T-That's...
Straw Hat... Luffy!
He really... did show up!
Hey, did you see that?
He saved King Neptune!
Yeah... And I'm sure
I just heard Princess Shirahoshi asking him for help...
Luffy-sama!
He came out of the shark?!
He's been hiding in its belly the whole time?!
Why?!
You came out early?
Well, I guess you had no choice.
Hurry, all of you!
What?  Who is he talking to -hi?!
Don't worry.  We were already hurrying.
It would take some sort of impossible miracle...
for Luffy to wait quietly according to plan.
Mirage canceled!
A woman appeared out of nowhere -hi!
Is this it, Jinbe-chan?
The form from the Celestial Dragons?
Excellent, you got it!
No way!  Huh?!
The form's gone!  When did she...
You fool!  What were you doing?!
And Robin's got the keys to their chains.
No way...
The keys are gone!
What were you doing?!
The chains!
What is this?
Robin-sama...
Father!  Are you alright?!
Hey, look up at the sky!  What is that?
That's...
A whale... and a lion?
No, that's not it!
That's...
Lion's Roar Cannon
It's a pirate ship!
Fire!
Now!  Go, whale!
Hoe?!
Princes!  Hurry and get out of here, and take the King with you!
Not gonna happen!  Stop -zugan!
They took the Royals!
Damn it!  Return the Royal Family -gyaban!
What... happened?
It looks like Jinbe made a plan with Straw Hat and his crew.
Look!  There are so many people!
Hey, now!  Are all of these guys enemies?
Probably.  From looking at them,
I'd say there are about seventy or eighty thousand...
No, closer to a hundred thousand.
This is a little harsh.
In that case,
feel free to go nap in your room.
I'll take them all out!
The hell was that?!
I can see that you're itching for a fight.
Let's put on a flashy show, men!
Look!  The Straw Hats are
getting off the ship, one after another!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy!
Do you really plan to destroy the island?!
Why did you occupy Ryuuguu Palace?!
Are you planning to kill the Royal Family too?!
Did you kidnap those mermaids?!
Hey, answer us!
Are you Fishman Island's enemies?  Or are you allies?
Answer us, Straw Hat!
Friend or foe...
You guys can...
decide that for yourselves!