Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Translation & initial timing
Yibis Fansubs
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Feeso
you'll have to be tough.
Soundtracking
Halee
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Video editing
Sewil
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Into the Depths!
The Kraken and the Caribou Pirates
Bro, it's difficult to dig here!
Sabaody Archipelago
Of course it is.
These islands are mostly just tree roots.
Please forgive us!  Don't bury us!
We'll do whatever you want, just don't kill us!
The captain forced us into it!  That damn Black!
As soon as we'd joined the crew...
we planned on taking out...
every last one...
of the infamous Straw Hat Pirates!
Drip!
Hey, please stop it!  He'll die!
You've got Devil Fruit powers?!
S-Stop, dammit!
What's with him?!  Is he a Logi-
Can you believe it?
I assumed that your faces and physiques had changed, it'd been 2 years after all.
But the pirate, Straw Hat...
was just a nobody!
A filthy impostor!
Do you think God will forgive this, Coribou?!
Dig!  Dig!
Indeed, my friends!  Let's bury 'em all!
Oh, God!
I will bury these imbeciles!
Stop!
However, I've seen the real Straw Hat Luffy
with my own eyes.
The former rendezvous point of the Fake Straw Hats
As I said, there was nothing we could do.
We were up against the Dark King Rayleigh.
He could fight off uncle Kizaru.
What could we have done against him?
The only ones that escaped from the plaza were the Caribou brothers with their crew...
and a few members of the fake Straw Hat Pirates.
We captured everyone else,
but the real Straw Hat Pirates dealt heavy damage
to the 2 Pacifista that I brought.
They are the same prototypes that cornered them 2 years ago.
Of course, the Pacifistas' strength can't have changed.
The change must have been in those guys!
During their 2-year absence,
they've grown incredibly.
Send word to Navy HQ in the New World.
The Straw Hat Pirates have completely recovered.
They're gone in the blink of an eye.
Monkey-chan and the rest sure have become tough.
You were watching?
Of course.  I am a fan, after all.
Are you remembering something, Ray-san?
Oh, yeah... I guess.
Hey!  That's a nice ship!
It's a stolen ship.
My house burned down, so I'm living here.
I see.  What's your name?
It's Rayleigh.
I'm Roger!  Our meeting here is destiny, Rayleigh!
Wanna come with me and turn the world on its head?
The world?
Who do you think you are?
Get lost.
Maybe there are no coincidences in this world.
It's possible that everything happens for a reason.
Fate works in mysterious ways.
Whatever the case, Luffy has become a man
worthy to wear that hat.
I suppose it might not be too bad, living a little longer.
The waters around the Sabaody Archipelago - Beneath the surface
The surface is already so far away.
What a sight!  We don't get a view this wide
in the submarine.
We're sinking faster and faster!
Is the water really not gonna come in?  I'm worried!
It feels like we're drifting away from the human world!  I'm tense.
A-Are we gonna be able to return to the surface?
Not that I'm scared or anything!
The ocean sure is beautiful!
Look at this side!
Trees!  No, roots!
Yeah... Now that I think about it, the
Sabaody Archipelago is one giant mangrove, after all.
The splendor of nature!
I've already seen it.
Yeah, 'cause you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up!  Let us be in awe here!
I can hardly believe that the roots
stretch all the way to the ocean floor.
They're so big, I'm speechless.
Hey, Chopper...
There's something behind those trees!
It's humongous!
I'm so excited!  An adventure beneath the sea!
It's like a dream!
Oh, fish!
I think I can catch them!
There are some tasty looking fish over here too.
Cut it out, you two!
What if the soap bubble breaks?!
I'm gonna kill you if you do that again!
Nami-san, before these two do something else stupid,
could you tell us how this coating works?
I guess so, Sanji-kun.
Rayleigh-san gave me some notes, after all.
So, let me explain it to you all.
She moved!  A real life beauty!
Sanji!
It's breaking!  Breaking!  Breaking!
Just how far can you be propelled by a nosebleed?!
Sanji got thrown into the sea!
Sanji!
Come back!
The ocean!  My strength is fading...
Hang in there!
What happened to you, Sanji?!
It's like you've developed
a crippling weakness to women!
It's not like you!
How sad.
What could have happened these last 2 years,
to turn the lady-loving Sanji-san into this?
At this rate, once he meets the mermaids he was longing to see,
he might die from blood loss.
We'll have to get
a blood transfusion for him on Fishman Island.
I wonder if fishmen and mermen have the same blood types as humans.
So basically, like we just saw,
the soap-bubble surrounding this ship has the same properties as the ones on the Sabaody Archipelago?
Don't just calmly continue your analysis of soap-bubbles!
Indeed.
Fundamentally, they're the same.
They'll stretch to a certain extent,
and after that, you'll pierce through them.
In a worst-case scenario,
if we're attacked by sea monsters, we can fire a cannonball at them.
The bubble won't break!
Then what would it take for it to break?
As you'd expect, it won't hold if
a large number of holes are opened at once.
For example, if a sea monster or Sea King
bites the ship, we're done for.
Look out, behind us!
A fight... We're saved.
If we crash into rocks or a trench and
the ship itself takes damage,
then fractures in the mast or hull
could cause the bubble to break.
So we have to avoid that too.
Basically, we have to look out for
sea creatures and other obstacles.
As long as we don't do anything stupid in here,
there's nothing to worry about.
I see!  It's stronger than I expected!
However, of all the ships that set off for Fishman Island...
70% are destroyed.  Be careful.
What's gonna happen to us?!
If I use my Gatling on them,
I'm sure I can catch all of those fish!
Then how about we compete
to see who can catch the most?
Weren't you listening to what Nami said?!
We can't open a bunch of holes!
I'm gonna beat the crap out of you two!
Never do that again!
Dammit!
Hachi said he'd lead us to Fishman Island,
so I didn't think it'd be this dangerous!
Oh, right!
I've got tons of lunch boxes.
And since Sanji's knocked out right now...
Everyone!  Let's have some food!
Yay!  My stomach's rumbling!
My bones are rumbling as well!
Nami, will the ship be safe?
Well, right now we're just riding a large ocean current, so...
See, there's something I need to tell all of you.
Your hidden robotic functions?!
No, sorry, but...
I am afraid that is incorrect, robo.
Whoa, awesome!  Robot-language!
The truth is, Hachi had planned to
come and guide us across the ocean floor...
but I heard he suffered major injuries on Sabaody,
and is now recovering on Fishman Island.
His reason is the same as Duval's.
He fought to protect the Thousand Sunny, which had been left behind on the island.
About a year ago, the Navy found out
where the Sunny was docked.
In the fierce battle that followed,
both of them were forced to retire.
Huh?  Then how'd the ship last until now?
Because there was one more warrior.
The very same man who
scattered us 2 years ago, in fact.
A member of the Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea, and a great man, Bartholomew Kuma.
A few days ago, when I arrived at the Sunny,
I couldn't believe my eyes.
I was waiting for you.
Damn you!  What are you doing here?!
Mission complete.
The Sunny didn't have a single scratch on her.
And when I spoke to Rayleigh afterward...
I am an officer in the Revolutionary Army.
Because of this,
I wish to let this crew escape.
I'm guessing you figured it out too.
He saved our lives back then.
And after we vanished from the island, Kuma-san visited Rayleigh and said...
The time I have left... is running out.
I don't know what they were holding over him,
but he allowed the Navy to experiment on his body,
and they slowly turned him into a cyborg.
Shortly before the great war,
he agreed to undergo a modification that would remove his personality completely.
But there's no way he could've known what we'd do after we were scattered!
And yet he waited for us by the ship?  Even though he'd lost his personality?!
It seems that while he was with the surgeon, Doctor Vegapunk,
he got a promise that a certain mission would be programmed into him.
Guard the ship until
a member of the Straw Hat Pirates returns.
So, for two years he's been waiting for us.
Despite being a human weapon without memories, he's been obeying the orders from his past self.
His methods are completely messed up.
Why would he go that far for us?
He's with the Revolutionary Army.
The only explanation I can think of
is that Luffy's dad is their boss.
I don't really know much about my dad.
But I guess that bear-like guy was a good guy after all.
Kuma.
Well, the fact remains that...
he was the one who allowed us to
survive these 2 years and make them worthwhile.
Though by now, there's no way for us to ask him why he did what he did.
Just keep this fact stored in your hearts...
This crew is indebted to Bartholomew Kuma.
But even if we meet him again, Kuma has become nothing more than a heartless human weapon.
I'm grateful to him, but this raises a lot of questions.
I hope we'll be able to find out Kuma's true intentions one day.
That is all I have to say.
Oh, Sanji, you're awake?
Have a lunch box!  It's from the Island of Women!
The Island of Women...
Why should I be grateful to Kuma?
Do you have any idea where I've been for 2 years?!
What kind of training did you do on that all-women island of dreams, Luffy?!
Now, now, now, Sanji-san.
Shall we sing together?
Don't try to comfort me!
You're making me feel pathetic!
Bro!  There they are!
Ahead!  The Straw Hats!
I can see that, you dummy.
This time I'll get to board that ship, won't I?
I wonder how far we've sunk?
There isn't much light this far down.
We already passed through the sunlight level and
now we're nearing the end of the twilight level.
We must be more than
a kilometer down by now.
It's so quiet.
This feels completely different to the submarine.
It's almost like we're flying through the sky.
A whale!  It's a whale!
Laboon?  Laboon!
No, that's old man Whitebeard!
I see something at 6 o'clock!
A sea monster?  No...
Are you ready, you guys?
Yeah, Bro!
Aye!  Aye!
Our goal is right before our eyes!
We could destroy their ship,
and send the wreckage straight to the ocean floor.
But that's no good.
If we did that, no one would know who did it.
We'll take their heads
and bring them back to the surface.
That's how we'll sing out to the world,
"Caribou is here!"
Aye!
They'll be completely unprepared for a fight!
This is a perfect sneak attack!
Don't mess this up, you guys!
Aye!
Aye!  Aye!
Hey, you guys!
A shadow that looks like a ship is approaching from behind!
What?!
A ship?!
It's headed straight for us!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
They're ramming our ship!
Get away!  The bubble will break!
No way!  They're trying to break into our soap bubble!
Who are they?!
Good job, sea cow!
Aye!
Are they planning to board our ship?
Sea cow?
Wait! Isn't that...
Alright! Shall we get going?
Aye!
Hey, Mohmoo!
You're Mohmoo from Arlong's crew, aren't you?
Do you recognize me?
Hey, Luffy!  Haven't we seen this guy before?
Really?
Die!
Rubber Pistol!
Let's board their ship, men!
Aye!
Someone's coming through!
Are you ready, men?!
Aye!
While these guys... stand there... dumbfounded...
every last one of 'em... will be slaughtered!
Let's go!
Aye!
Men!  Follow me!
Whaaaaaat?!
What's wrong, sea cow?!
Why are you doing this, sea cow?!
How can this be?!
Captain Caribou was left behind!
Bro?!
Now... How about we give them a little greeting?
Fire the Gatling gun at 'em!
Kill every last member... of the Straw Hat Crew!
Don't!
P-Please, don't throw me into the ocean!
That's all I ask!
Anything but that!
You mustn't take another's life so casually!
God!
God is watching!
Right?!
Don't get cheeky with me!  Who was just talking about slaughter and Gatling guns?!
Who are you?
You're the captain of that pirate ship, aren't you?
Hm?!  Roronoa Zoro!
Oh, you're mistaken!  I'm not the captain!
I was, uh...
I was just being used as their slave!
Damn, I'm sick of being on that ship!
Oh, yeah!  Please!
Can you let me stay on your ship for a little while?
Please!  I'm begging you!
You know, I kinda feel sorry for him.
Oh, come on!  He's obviously lying!
What?!  It was all a lie?!
Hey, can I ask you something?
What was with the sea cow that was pulling the ship?
Oh...
What have we here?  Quite a cutie.
You're the Cat Burglar, aren't you?
Don't you dare look at our gorgeous navigator
with those vulgar eyes!
Nami-san, it's gonna be fine... now...
That's getting really annoying!
It's just a sea monster that we caught in these waters.
Using creatures like that to pull your ship is how professionals travel underwater.
Huh?!
So that's how it is!
Stop!  Stop, sea cow!
What happened, sea cow?!
Bro!  I'm gonna save you!
I wonder if there are any sea monsters around?
Wait a second, Luffy.  What are you planning?
We'll start rehabilitating you with photos
since they don't have as much of an impact.
Hey, Nami.
Are we going in a different direction
from the one the Log Pose is pointing in?
Yes, but don't worry.
We should move southwest of the compass needle.
But going directly toward the island would be faster!
Why?
Apparently, if you follow the needle directly,
you'll get caught up in the ocean currents,
and crash into an underwater mountain or volcano
before reaching your destination.
What?!  A volcano?!  The ocean floor is scary!
But I thought that all the currents of the Grand Line
are completely out of whack.
Is there really a current that isn't going to cause us problems?
Yeah, just one.
Everyone!  It's gonna get cold soon.  You'd better put on a coat.
True, my skin is starting to get goosebumps.
Ah!  Though I-
You're all bones, so you don't have skin, right?
We're going somewhere cold?
Aren't we headed for the ocean floor?
Of course the water at the ocean floor is cold.
Even in a bath, the water's warmer at the top
and colder on the bottom, right?
Oh, right.  So if it's the same for the sea,
the water down deep is colder than surface water.
Temperature isn't the only thing that's different...
Will you get over it already?!
In the deeper parts of the ocean,
there are giant currents known as "deep currents"
that you usually can't see.
They are completely different from
the surface currents we've been riding so far.
There are currents beneath the currents?
You sure are knowledgeable!
Only because I have lived for so long!
The currents all have to connect somewhere.
They flow from the east or the west
and then meet up...
Plunging downward and surging back up.
It's almost like an enormous dragon.
Apparently the deep currents flow very slowly.
They say that once water goes down to the ocean floor,
it can take 2,000 years
before it returns to a level that sees the sun.
2,000 years?!
Indeed.  Furthermore, there are countless legends...
about those dark, unknown sea currents.
Monsters, curses, and souls of the damned!
Whaaaaat?!  There are ghosts in the deep seas?!
Huh?!  There are?!  Scary!
How exciting!
Ghosts, huh?
I don't know about all that...
but we're gonna use the downflow to dive
from the surface currents to the deep currents.
By doing that, we'll be able to reach the ocean floor.
So it's a mysterious sea current.
You didn't understand any of that, did you?!
Shall we sing a song, Nami-san?
Nami, I see it!
Really?
The mysterious sea current?!
What's that?
The downflow, Plume!
Awesome!
This is almost like...
an enormous underwater waterfall!
That's so cool!
The water keeps falling all the way to the bottom!
It's unbelievably fast!
Very impressive, nature!
What a massive current!
I wonder how many hundred meters across it is?
Seeing it for yourself is completely different from
hearing stories about it!
I can't see the bottom!  It's pitch black down there!
It's all over!
If we fall at that speed,
we'll crash into the ocean floor.  We'll die!
Are you sure we'll be fine, riding this current?
Don't worry about the ship.
The Sunny was crafted from the Treasure Tree, Adam.
It's the strongest ship there is.
Alright!
Forward!
It can't be!
I hadn't heard that that thing was living down here!
The demon that races through the seas.
The enemy of all humanity!
Straw Hat Crew!  Turn around immediately!
We're doomed!
Oh yeah, you're here too.
There's a monster down there!
It's the Kraken!
The incomprehensibly gigantic monster octopus!
It's crushing several ships at once.
It has been preying on the ships that pass through here.
Please!  I don't wanna die!
Turn around!  If we just wait for a few days,
I'm sure that monster will-
Shut up!  Be quiet!
I just had a great idea!
Let's tame him!
Huh?
What are you talking about, Luffy?!
We'll tame that octopus and make him pull our ship!
Don't be ridiculous!
Look closely, or even if you don't look closely, can't you see how huge that thing is?!
Man, it sure is big...
I don't know how many centuries it's been alive,
but the Kraken appears in countless legends.
It's a mythical beast!