Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Hmm?  What?
I lost sight of him.
The one with stripes.
You fool.  I'm right here!
But by the time you realize it, you'll already be dead!
Take this!
I hear a voice over here!
Z-Zeo-san was...
beaten!
Did you see what just happened, skeleton?
Thanks to my weapon destruction skill, Sword-Crush With My Body...
the tip of your sword...
is crumbl-
I stabbed you, didn't I?
Even after getting stabbed, he's still so prideful!
Feel free to think so... and then be deth-
...and then be destroyed!
You fool!
Huh?!  What?!
I lost sight of him again!  Where is he?!
Hidden God Flail
Six-Six Head
I... figured it out.
During the past two years,
I learned the true power of the Yomi Yomi Fruit.
When someone dies,
their soul typically departs for the underworld.
However, my soul continues to exist in this world...
thanks to a powerful energy
that emanates to keep my body alive.
By playing music,
I'm able to move other people's souls.
I can drag them into the spiritual world,
and even show them illusions at times.
If my soul leaves my body,
people can see its form clearly.
It most certainly exists in this world!
I've done it!
I've taken down one of the Straw Hat Pirates!
No.
The power that keeps me in this world does not come from my organs.
Nor from my muscles.
Indeed...
It's my soul!
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!
Oh!  That got me pumped up!
Alright!
He's bluffing!
Do you understand?
Unless you completely shatter my bones,
damage to my skeletal body doesn't matter!
Shikomizue: A Sword Cane
And...
I had the Longhand Tribe sharpen this shikomizue.
Its name is Soul Solid!
I imbue its attacks with my soul,
bringing the cold of the underworld into our world!
Behold...
my freezing sword!
That's awesome, Brook!
I can't let him outshine me!
Everyone's got something new
to help them in the New World.
Are you really so concerned about your friends?!
Don't worry about it!
All of you will soon be scrap lying on the ocean floor!
Fire Daruma Cutter
Hot hot hot hot!
Damn you!
A guy like you is just holding your crew back!
You're firing one dud after another!
Don't be so impatient, little mole shark.
I'm a cookie cutter shark!
I just...
finished setting my trap!
I'm putting an end to this!
You won't put an end to anything!
Die!
Arming
I'll rip that arm of yours to shreds!
Luffy-sama!
Weak-hoshi!  Take me to the Noah!
Okay!
As fast as you can!
What are you doing?!
I... won't run!
Don't be ridiculous!  Can't you see the Noah?!
I know!  I know, but...
hearing what Straw Hat is doing...
reminded me...
of when I was a kid, twenty years ago!
Of that one human this whole country is indebted to!
This is one great catch!
Wait!
No!
Who are you?!  Don't you value your own life?!
Huh?!
Hey, you're kidding, right?!
Why would he...
side with the fishmen?!
Neptune helped me out once, long ago.
We exchanged the drink of friendship!
S-Spare our lives!
We'll never kidnap fishmen or mermaids again!
Don't cause any trouble in my friend's country!
You snot-nosed brats!
I'm making this island...
my turf!
You mean Whitebeard?  You trust these guys
as much as you trusted that great pirate?!
You know... I actually hate humans...
and this is the fishmen's country... yet he was...
We made the decision with Jinbe when we entered the plaza.
We won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!
You can leave it all to us, Bro-hoshi!
We're friends, ain't we?
He said something like that,
and is putting his life on the line!
Air!
He's as tough as the elite bounties.
My fangs aren't just for show!
Humans don't seem to learn their lesson
until they're dead.
You're weak, and you don't know your place!
So why don't I make you understand?!
I don't have time for this.
It's time we settled this!
Sure, go ahead and try!
Weak-hoshi!  Get back!
O-Okay!
Fishman Way of Yielding
Water Heart
Swarm of Sharks/Rainshower
You're not getting away!
Die!
Just give it up... and die!
Fall... Noah!
Kill all the... fishmen...
who have lost their pride!
He...
He did it!
This time, he really...
beat Hody!
We're done for!  Both us, and the island!
Let's get out of here!
Zeo-san!  Give us a break!
The island's...
Don't be fooled!
We were chosen by the heavens.
Captain Hody and his crew...
could never be defeated by mere humans!
B-But if the Noah crushes the island, we'll all...
Death still counts as revenge.
Our deaths will feed the hatred of humans in others!
This tragedy will become our flesh and blood.
Our malice will live on.
It will be passed on to the next generation,
and we will surely have our revenge!
There he is.
Captain Hody and the commanders are all insane!
It's the humans who made us like this!
Do not retreat!
Direct all your rage toward the humans -bogon!
The calamity that is hanging over all of fishmankind...
is entirely the humans' fault -zugan!
Are the humans really... that scary?
Don't be ridiculous!
True, historically speaking, the humans have-
Stop.
Madame Shyarly.
Look for yourselves.
Right now, in the plaza and in the sky above,
the ones fighting against the pirates from the Fishman District...
are humans.
Are all those guys... really human?
True, some of them look pretty strange.
But still, we must see this for ourselves.
We have no right to say anything if we don't.
Whatever happens now...
you must watch with an open mind!
Anyone who isn't willing to die in battle...
can die by my hands,
and live on in the grudge against the humans!
Stop this!  They are your allies!
I'm saved!  Thank you, Skeleton Mask!
You again?
You sure talk about death a lot
for someone who has never died!
Die and live on in a grudge?!  Preposterous!
Nothing remains after death!
When a creature dies,
there's nothing left but dead bones!
You're really convincing!
Very kind of you!
I really hate people who throw their lives away!
It makes me sick to my stomach.
Even though I have no stomach to be sick!
Aren't you the ones who are throwing your lives away?
All of you staying here
without even trying to run away...
when you humans are the ones
who will undoubtedly die once the Noah crashes!
Granted, I'm not sure you're really human!
Our Captain Luffy is going to be
the Pirate King someday.
And that captain just said...
that he won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!
That we could leave it all to him!
As long as we believe in him, why would we worry about anything?
Now, it's time for me to fulfill my own mission!
I won't take my eyes off you again!
Even though I have no eyes!
How's dis?!
Surprised?!
Yeah, that's more than enough.  Oh, I am so surprised.
Really?
Alright... Let's end this, Jinbe.
Indeed, it's time!
Hey, wait... I lost my swords.
How am I supposed to fight?
Hell if I know.
You're so impudent!
I'm gonna settle this in one hit,
with the debut of my new super move!
One finger... Two fingers...
When I raise the third finger,
I will snipe you and this fight will be over!
What kind of foolish fantasy are you living?!
Wake up from your stupid daydream, you puny bastard!
Can't admit your defeat?!
It's funny... I'm actually surprised too.
I used to spout lies all the time...
but now I can do the stuff I boast about!
What's that monster?!
Where did that thing come from?!
T-That's...
Chopper?!
T-That little runt... grew huge all of a sudden!
Hey!  Hey, hey!
There was no need for you to go berserk!
It's alright, Usopp!
Chopper!  What do you mean, it's alright?!
I'm now able to fight in this form for three minutes,
using the Rumble Ball!
It isn't like it was before!
I won't cause you guys any more trouble!
I don't believe it!
You're not going berserk, you're helping us out!
How dependable you've become!
S-
Saying that won't make me happy, you jerk!
That's just scary!
You gotta be kidding me -dosun!
It doesn't matter how big you become, I'm still gonna blast you to the ends of the sea -gogyan!
You won't be able to blast me anywhere!
Now, bring it!
Chopper!
Chatting with your friends during a fight?!
Know your place!
You're nothing but a hindrance to your crew!
I'm gonna finish you off right now!
Didn't I tell you that I've got a trick up my sleeve?
Now, bring it on!  I'll show you my magic tricks!
Interesting!  You say
you're gonna finish me off in one hit?
Even if the Dried Squid Spear doesn't work on you,
I've been concealing a powerful spear that can penetrate anything!
Light up!
Mortar Bon Spear
You're the one who'll be dropped with a single hit -hi!
I'll pierce a hole right through the robot into the driver's seat -hi!
That is rather cool, but...
it's no use.
Against my ultimate weapon, you are...
just an inferior squid!
I can't fight bare handed.  What should I do?
I can't cut someone down who has no will to fight.
Get lost, damn frog.
Frog?
Yer gonna end dis?  Dat's mah line!
Don't think ya just tricked me into inflatin', ya idiots!
Ah'm gonna roll around an' flatten all yer friends in da plaza!
This is my range, skeleton man.
The moment that you enter this circle,
your bones will all be shattered to dust!
Now, what will you do?!
Now then, if you'll excuse me...
I already entered your circle and cut you.
It is quite cold out.  Please take care.
When did you...
Grazing Song
Blizzard Slash
And now a poem...
May the winds of the underworld...
which can freeze blood...
lift skirts as well.
Die!
What's that?!
These plants have man shaped roots...
that jump at anyone who passes above them...
and cling onto them!
What is it now?!
It sends intruders flying!
And now, with you flying high into the air,
there's no way for you to dodge!
A beast from the surface?  I'll rip it to shreds!
Bad idea.  The bulb on the tip of its nose...
releases a powerful shockwave
that hits anything within three meters!
Dosun!  Dogan!  Bogan!
Now, fly into the horizon!
Gadon!  Megagon!
Cloven-Hoof Palme
Dogyan!
Pi... Pikon...
Squid!  Squid!  Squid!
Take this!  The spear
that even penetrates underwater mountains!
Squid!  Squid!  Squid!
Dried squid!
A beam?!
Fishman Karate Secret Technique
Vagabond Drill
Whaaaaat?!
The water... pierced right through his body!
Da air's leaking.
How do you like the sky, balloon pufferfish?
A human flying in da sky?!
Ya scared da guts outta me!
Think back on the past two years...
Sanji-kyuuun!
Why did I have to go through all that?!
He's on fire!
I'm gonna burn those memories to ash!
I scared the guts out of you?
Well, that saves me some trouble.
When cooking pufferfish,
one has to be careful to remove the poisonous meat.
Have a taste of my poisonous blades!
Knock it off, damn frog.
I'm not a frog!
I'm Fishman Island's number one!
The Hattouryuu-using octopus, Hyouzou!
Hattouryuu: Eight-Sword Style
Remember it!
Purgatory Demon Slash
So sorry.
I confused you with the proverbial frog...
in a well.