Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
So how are they -jamon, Jinbe?
I never would have thought that
the Sun Pirates would align with Big Mom.
Are they really okay with it?
It'd be quite a stretch to call her a reasonable woman,
but she gives us a lot of freedom.
Well, I just thought...
a man like you would never
work under anyone but Fisher Tiger.
Not at all.
I don't mind having someone else as my boss.
Besides, in the New World...
having an alliance with one of the Four Emperors is the best way to protect your crew.
Really?  It seems to me
that you did it to protect Fishman Island.
Because of your actions,
Fishman Island has been able
to use Big Mom's name after Whitebeard's death,
and so we've stayed relatively safe.
Oh, that's just a coincidence.
Normally we would protect the island ourselves, but...
seeing as how we're wanted men...
But, Your Majesty.
I'm thinking of separating myself from Big Mom.
Oh?  Are you going to accept Luffy-kun's offer?
Hey, Jinbe.
Join my crew!
Yes, I have been considering it.
But there are duties and obligations I must take into account.
I've formed promises and bonds through words and shared cups.
Now, if I break those bonds I have to be prepared...
This is a worst case scenario,
but we can't rule out the possibility
that Big Mom's anger could engulf this island.
As always, you try to carry too much responsibility on your shoulders -jamon, Jinbe.
If that comes to pass, then we'll deal with it then.
I have plans of my own -jamon.
Just today, I gained seventy thousand new soldiers from the Fishman District, even if they're rowdy.
Don't worry -jamon.
And besides,
even if this island does lose Big Mom's flag,
there's another flag
I would love to borrow for protection.
The flag with a skull wearing a straw hat -jamon!
I see!  That is a nice flag, isn't it?
Your Majesty!
T-T-T-This is awful!
What is it, Right Minister?  Why are you panicking?
I remembered something awful!
It's about our promise to give all the stolen treasure to Luffy-kun's crew if they found it.
If they do find it,
please make them return the Tamate Box, at least!
What are you talking about?!
I promised them that they could have it, and I won't tell them to give it back now!
B-But...
What?!  If they open it, it'll explode?!
Why would you put a bomb in it?!
W-Well, you see...
Ten years ago,
when someone emptied the Tamate Box,
we figured we'd set up a trap so that if another treasure thief showed up, they wouldn't get away.
So we filled the box with bombs...
and made it so that if it was opened, it would cause a huge explosion.
As the one who holds the key
to the treasure chamber and the Tamate Box, I...
Alright, I understand.
If Luffy-kun and the others find the treasure, you'll explain the situation and ask them to return the box.
I'm really sorry about this!
But what if Luffy-kun and the others open it before they get back?
I'm worried about that, too.
Your Majesty!  Right Minister!
Luffy-san and his group
just returned to Ryuuguu Palace.
Oh!  They made it back without any trouble?
Thank goodness!
I suppose I shouldn't have worried so much.
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!
You gave...
Big Mom...
all the treasure?!
She was saying something about how
she'd destroy Fishman Island if she didn't get candy!
She's crazy!  I mean, I'd understand
if it was meat she was talking about...
But don't worry about it!
I picked a fight with her!
With one of the Four Emperors?!
You picked a fight with Big Mom?!
You're strong, right, Luffy-sama?
That's not the issue here!
Noseopp-sama, you're so scary...
I'm telling you, my name is Usopp!
I'm sorry.
What a bother... This is not good.
I'll have to cut my ties with Big Mom before the whole deal breaks down.
Anyway, don't do anything
that might make Big Mom angrier than she is already.
Of course we won't!  If we get on the bad side of one of the Four Emperors, we'll be obliterated instantly!
Hey, isn't this really bad, Right Minister?
How could this happen?!
Now the Tamate Box will end up with Big Mom,
and if she opens it herself, she'll take the explosion
as a declaration of war from Luffy-san!
This is just awful -jamon!
Well, it's not like there's anything we can do about it.
What's done is done.
We'll reap what we've sowed.
I suppose there's no way out of fighting her now.
That's right!  No matter who the enemy is, we'll-
Why...
did you give her all the treasure?!
That's the problem?!
I'm gonna punch you!
Uh, you already did!
Awlight... Wet'hs go to da New Wold.
The future looks completely bleak!
It's hopeless!  We're done for!
Meanwhile, near the Candy Factory...
Dammit!  Without me noticing,
someone wandered off with all my treasure!
Who did it?!  I'm definitely gonna kill'em!
I know I'd gain favor with that person if I offer them...
a mountain of treasure
and the secret about the Mermaid Princess!
A crowd!
Who are those two guys carrying gigantic sacks?
That's it!  No doubt about it!
Who are those nobodies?!  I'm gonna bury 'em alive!
That's the treasure I stole!  Give it back, damn you!
Hmm?
I've seen him before somewhere -gao.
Ah, here he is.
Wet Hair Caribou.
He's a rookie who's been popping up a lot recently.
Oh, he's worth 200 million.
A-A 200 million bounty?!
It's too late to pray for your lives now!
Go ahead and get filled with holes!
Sir Pekoms!
What's that?
A turtle?
You're a Devil Fruit user?
Of course I am!
But it's just a Zoan-type fruit, huh?!
Die!
Logia-users who think they're invincible
don't live very long.
Half-boiled challengers
are always so disappointing -soir.
Time to go -bon, Pekoms.
Back to Mama.
He took out a man worth 200 million in one hit.
If I remember it right,
Sir Pekoms's bounty is 330 million.
A bounty over 300 million. That's how strong the crews of the Four Emperors are?
Will Luffy-san and the others really be alright?
Meanwhile, in the New World,
in the waters near the Red Line...
Fire!
Hurry!  Another ship emerging at two o'clock!
Pirate ships are emerging from the sea,
one after another!
What's going on here?!
You think you'll make her like you by doing that?
Shaddup!  Back off!
We've finally been freed from Hell!  There's no way...
Here comes a big one!
The captain is in trouble!
I'll hold her tight to shield her from harm!
No, let me handle that vital mission!
Sheesh!
Again?!
Great!  That's our Captain-chan!
Her swordplay is just too beautiful for words!
And that isn't the only thing that's beautiful about her!
Take this seriously, all of you!
Haven't you been trained
to shield yourselves from bombardments?!
If you aren't going to show the results
of your training now, then when will you?!
Captain, that's the mast.
I finished polishing your glasses!
Thank you.
She's so cute!
The lone flower growing in the filth of G-5!
If you keep fooling around like this in battle...
you're going to get yourselves killed immediately!
You G-5 soldiers are just hopeless.
How can you call yourselves marines?!
If you look down on me
for being a girl, you'll regret it!
We don't look down on you!
We're just drawn to your cuteness!
That's what I meant by looking down on me!
You don't understand what a marine is supposed to-
Be quiet, Tashigi.
I'm in the middle of an interrogation.
Pardon me!
I see.  So you were all captured
by the pirate Hody Jones on the ocean floor?
That explains why no rookies
have made it past Fishman Island in the past month.
Captured?!  That's not it, we were his slaves!
But a certain pirate crew defeated Hody's group,
who were also behind the rebellion,
and freed us!
A certain pirate crew?
I-I can't tell you who they were, but...
Y-You dumbass!  Just tell him already!
These guys aren't normal marines!  They're the G-5!
They use pirates as bait to go fishing for sharks,
or burn pirates as firewood on their campfires!
They're a group of insane maverick marines who don't even obey the orders from HQ!
If they arrest us,
there's no telling what they'll do to us!
And of all people, we had to get caught...
by the White Hunter, Smoker!
Vice-admiral Smoker!
Won't you give these guys to us?
P-Please don't!
We'll say who it was!  Spare us!
The ones who defeated Hody's crew...
were the Straw Hat Pirates!
I know,
idiot.
Madame Shyarly, Luffy-chin's crew is about to leave.
Are they now?  Go see them off.
Sure!
Madame!  Can we go too?
What, you all want to go?
Well, I guess I'll have to close the café for a while.
That idiot Hody was blocking our customers,
but they'll be back soon enough.
I hope you'll continue to make the café an enjoyable place to be, girls.
Leave it to us, Madame!
Oh, the crystal ball?
Never mind that.  I've had enough.
I will never predict the future again.
Straw Hat Luffy destroying Fishman Island...
I wish I'd never seen that horrible future.
It would be for the best if it turns out that the prediction was wrong.
She's never been wrong,
so she must be more scared than any of us.
There's no guarantee that a future she's seen
will occur immediately.
It could happen a year from now,
or it could take even longer.
There's no definite proof that she was wrong.
But you know, Madame,
Luffy-chin and his group would never-
Caimie.
Please forgive me for doubting your friends.
I understand now.  We can trust him, right?
We can trust the Straw Hat boy.
Yes!
This is all for you.  Please accept it!
Right, thanks!
Luffy-sama, are all of you leaving already?
We've only just become friends, at least stay one more day...
No, one more week...
No, just stay for one more year!
You kept crying
all the way to the very end, huh, Weak-Hoshi?
I-I'm so sorry!
I'll stop being such a crybaby.
The Mermaid Princess of Fishman Island...
is crying because we're leaving!
I never thought this day would come!
I really wish I could live here for a year!
I understand what you mean!
I've even made a new single
about the dreamlike life here on Fishman Island!
Waking up with a Good Mor-ningyo!
Ningyo: Mermaid
Oh, my dear mermaids!
What a fantastic idea.
By all means, stay here, Nosebleed-kun.
Who did you just call what, Moss-Head?!
Who're you calling Moss-Head?!
Your Majesty!
We really must tell them...
about how the Tamate Box they sent to Big Mom...
will explode if it's opened!
But...
look at them.
It's over.  One of the Four Emperors wants us dead.  We're just going to die in the New World.
Do you think Big Mom will forgive us
if we give her all the treasure we find from now on?
I just can't bring myself to tell them...
that they've already sent her a bomb!
But you know,
it's been ten years since you planted those bombs.
Isn't there a chance that
they may have become duds in that time?
That's right, Your Majesty, think positive!
There's a lot of moisture in Ryuuguu Palace, after all!
Besides, there's no guarantee that Big Mom will open it herself!
Then...
Let's pray that things work out!
What are you two whispering about?
Huh?
What's... this?
A Log Pose used in the New World.
Take it with you.
Trying to navigate with just a single compass needle...
What are we to do with you?
What's that?  A new Log Pose?
That's so cool!
It's got three needles!  Why?
Look at the Log you've used up till now.
It's moving back and forth!  I thought
the Log had adjusted itself to another island.
It has.  From now on,
the Log will only need half a day to readjust itself.
In the previous half of the Grand Line, the Log would adjust itself to the magnetic field of the next island,
and you could reliably continue your voyage.
But you're entering the second half now,
where, in addition to
changing sea currents and climate,
magnetic fields, the one thing you've been able to rely on until now, fluctuate as well!
The magnetic field of some islands might even disappear completely before you reach them!
What?!  But then we couldn't even reach the island!
That would be a disaster
if you only had one compass needle.
But what could you do if you had three?
One of them is shaking like our Log Pose...
but the other two seem to be stable.
The three compass needles
are all aligned to different islands' magnetic fields.
Meaning, you have three different routes
and you can choose the one that looks the safest.
Your decisions can mean
the difference between life and death!
Skilled navigators can look at the slight movements of the needles and figure out the safest route.
To put it simply,
the more unstable the compass needle is...
the more dangerous the island it points to.
It means that something intense enough to disrupt the island's magnetic field is occuring there.
Huh?!  No way!
We're better off not knowing!
It can tell how dangerous things are?!
We can't!  Destroy that Log Pose!
Why?  If you don't pick the safest route, you might...
Let's see...
O-Oh crap!
Noooooooo!
The island in the middle
with the really shaky needle looks fun!
H-H-He heard!
Luffy, you shut up!  I'll decide the route we'll take!
Don't be ridiculous!  I'm the captain!
Please, Captain!  Listen to what your navigator says!
Nami-san is so cute when she's scared!
So cute!  So cute!
The B-side of my single!  "Requiem For Us!"
Alright, guys!  The preparations are complete!
Den-san has taught me how to control our ascent.
Shall we go?
Alright!
Let's go!
Luffy-chin!
Straw!
I'm helping out with repairing the factory.
Will you be alright without a guide?
Sure!  Our adventures coming here were fun too.
Yeah, that's right!  We don't need a guide!
A true man's journey always leads straight into hell!
Yeah, that's right!  This is war, you bastards!
You're beginning to lose it.
Everyone, please come again!
I swear to return!
To the All Blue of my heart!
What a cheap dream you have.
What?!
All I have are words,
but I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
I will pray that your voyage is a safe one.
Thanks!
The next time we meet,
we'll be leading the greatest army on the ocean floor!
Mambo!
Indeed!  We will rewrite the legend of
the great Neptune Knights -mi fa so la ti do!
I look forward to it!
So, where is he?
Ah, there!
Jinbe!
You got it!
Alright, hoist the sails!
Time to set sail!
Straw Hat!
See you later, Fishman Island!
Come back whenever you want, to eat candy and meat!
I like humans now!
Oh, and raccoon dogs and robots too!
I'm not happy at all, you jerks!
Huh?  What?
What about bones?
Stay well!  Luffy-chin, everyone!
Come back for some more Takoyaki someday!
I love you guys!
Ready, and...
We like bones too!
Thank you for being so considerate!
Luffy-sama!
Weak-Hoshi!
Shirahoshi-chwan!
If we can ever... meet again...
then I...
won't be such a crybaby anymore!
Please take me for another fun walk!
A walk?  You wanna go visit your mom again?
No.
This time, I want to go even further!
To the real forests above the sea!
I see.  You've never left the sea, have you?
Okay, sure!
The next time we meet, I'll take you there!
Promise me!
Sure, you got it!
It's a promise!
Hey, Luffy!
Doesn't that put some responsibility on us too?
Luffy-san, promises are something you must keep,
even if it kills you!
Then, Shirahoshi, I promise too!
Nami-chin-sama!
Me too.
And me!
And me.
Of course I promise too!
If we all promise...
It should be alright.
It's a promise!
E-Everyone...
So don't cry any more!
Alright!
Never forget what they did for us.
Of course we won't!
Hey, Daddy!
Buy me a straw hat!  I wanna play hero!
What?  They only sell those on the surface!
Then go up there and buy one!
Don't be a fool!  The surface is where
the terrifying humans who hate fishmen...
What?
Uh, no.  There are guys like him too, after all.
Of course, there are plenty of strong,
kind-hearted people like Straw Hat up there too!
Boss Jinbe!  Perfect timing!
I couldn't help overhearing you.
I'll send a merchant ship to get some straw hats.
Really?!
Indeed.
It's the hat of a hero, after all!
Yeah!
That was the best!
Mermaid Paradise!
Now, everyone, you'd better quit slacking off!
Now that we're out in the sea,
there's no safe place anywhere!
We're gonna be passing through the dark sea again, after all.
What's that, Franky?
I'm making the ship rise by using
these cubes of highly buoyant taolfrepus wood.
I can regulate our speed
by adjusting how many are out in the water.
What is it, Luffy?
When we reach the surface...
we'll be in the same sea as Shanks!
I can't wait to see him!
Then...
I'll entrust you with this hat.
It's my precious hat.
Come return it to me some day,
when you've become a great pirate!
I only have... one regret.
That I couldn't see you... fulfill your dream.
But... I'm sure...
you can make it.
You're my little brother.
Don't just count everything you've lost!
What's gone, is gone!
But ask yourself this, what remains?!
Keep going all the way to the top!
Luffy-san, do you know what they call the second half of the Grand Line?
The final ocean that stretches out
on the other side of the Red Line...
People call it by another name...
The New World!
The New World?
The ocean that beckons
those who'll forge a new era.
The one who conquers that ocean becomes the Pirate King!
Once we make it to the surface...
we'll be in the world's strongest sea!
Finally!  I'll cut down anything in our way!
Wait for me, Laboon!  I'm halfway there!
Sure, I'll take you anywhere!
That's right!  The Sunny can make it!
Nobody has to worry about getting hurt!
Eat as much as you want, it won't bother me!
There's a warrior of the sea on this ship!
Let's go!
You guys!
To the New World!
Aye!