Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
At the Sea Forest!
Arlong and Hody
Zoro?
Boss!  Boss!  Boss!
How can a human move faster than
a fishman in the water?!
Who is that guy?
Don't let that swordsman get away!
Everyone take your Energy Steroids.
What a nuisance they are!
Exterminate everyone in the Neptune Army!
Damn it.
What's this?  Such an unnatural aura.
Damn.  If they're gonna fight like that then we'll massacre everyone!
Zoro!
The palace will be completely flooded soon.
You should grab on to my body!
They're taking out our best soldiers so easily.
They must be using some sort of sinister power.
Just as I thought,
I must get all the soldiers out of the palace.
Hey!  Use this to make sure you have air -jamon.
Ah, thanks!
Hold onto my body tightly -jamon!
Got it!
We can't delay, we must go now -jamon!
Zoro!  Over here!  Grab hold of the old man!
I wonder if my injured back will hold out.
Listen up, soldiers!
We're gonna carve a path out of here!
Don't stay and fight.  Flee the palace!
Zoro, use this!
Here we go!
Neptune's doing something!
Zoro!
Ouch!  Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Men, go now!
Yes, sir!
Ride the current as far as you can!
Damn it, they're running away without fighting!
Boss Hody!  Quickly, take this!
We're out of the castle!  Keep moving!
Go through the connecting channel, all the way to the mainland!
Hey, old man!
Get it together!  I'm begging you!
Age can be so cruel.
I can't move at all -jamon.
What?!
Your Majesty!
King Neptune!
Oh, Hoe.
You've saved us!
I apologize for my frailty.
I couldn't even move my neck -jamon.
Are you okay?
Thank God, Hoe helped him get out!
Go!
I'm out of air.
What?
What's going on?
Your Majesty!
This is terrible!  Hody caught His Majesty!
Wasn't Hody supposed to be incapacitated?
Minister of the Right!  Let's go back!
At this rate, His Majesty's going to be...
You mustn't -jamon!
You must go on without me,
and bring back Fukaboshi and his brothers!
Don't just stand there!  Obey the King's orders!
Yes, sir!
Boss Hody, is it okay to let them get away?
Yeah it's fine, let them go.
What can a bunch of warriors who'd abandon their king do?
But more importantly,
tie up this foolish king.
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry, you guys...
but I won't let you get killed!
What's this?
Who knows?  Probably someone's skeleton.
This place is beautiful!
So this is the Sea Forest?
You see, I've always wanted to come here.
I am truly indebted to you, Luffy-sama.
I hope we can rest and recuperate here.
Mermaid.... Mermaid...
Sanji.
Oh, it's the Sunny!
You're right!  Franky's there, too!
Hey, Franky!  So this is where you've been?
Is that you, Luffy?
Huh?
Well, if you didn't bring a pinup girl with you?!
I'll introduce ya.  This is Wimp.
Oh, Wimp, huh?
Sounds like you need to get your act together.
Yes, sorry for troubling you.  My name is Shirahoshi.
Franky, are you the only one here?
Actually, Robin was here too,
but then she went off in search of something.
She went into that huge coral forest.
Huh.
Luffy-kun.
Jinbe!
If it isn't Jinbe!
It's been quite a while.
It looks like you're quite a bit stronger.  I can see the difference.
I heard you weren't down here,
so I didn't think I'd be able to see you.
What do you mean?
Didn't you get my message to meet me here?
What are you talking about?
I don't know anything about that.
That's strange.
Boss Jinbe-sama,
it's certainly been quite a while since we last met.
I'm sorry for failing to keep in touch with you,
Princess Shirahoshi-sam-
Whaaat!
Princess Shirahoshi!  Why are you here?!
Hey Franky!  I wanna bring
Hachi and Sanji down, so give me a hand.
Huh?
If it ain't the octopus guy!
What happened to ya?
Hachi!  What!
Where did those injuries come from?
More importantly,
why are you on Fishman Island?
Weren't you captured along with Arlong?
Jinbe-san, why are you here?
Franky!  Sanji's next!
Oh no, it's not that bad.
Huh?
Ah, Mermaid Princess!
Before you, I am like an artist with no talent.
For you see, there is no brush
that could properly capture your radiance!
W-Well...
That's... his normal reaction
in the presence of women!  He's all better!
My canvas could never reflect the beauty
that you possess.
Hooray!  Hooray!
Sanji's returned to his normal strange self!
It sure is loud over there... I wonder what's going on?
Why is Princess Shirahoshi here?
Hey!  Who're you?!  Why are you on the Sunny?!
He's Den-chan, the younger brother of Tom,
my carpentry master!
He's fixing the ship's coating.
Is that who he is?
He's the master who's going to
coat your younger brother, huh?
Well, that's close enough!
But Princess Shirahoshi-sama,
I understand why you wanted to come here but-
Still?
Even after the beating I gave him.
How many times has it been now?
He's really persistent.
Listen to me, now!
Why'd you bring the Princess here, Luffy-kun?
It's fine!  I'm here, after all!
That's right!
What is she thinking?
So that's the tomb she was talking about?
She's really been going at it for a long time, now.
This is where her mother, Queen Otohime, is resting.
Vander Decken started his obstinate courtship...
right after the Queen passed away.
Because of this,
the Princess couldn't even attend her mother's funeral,
and she's spent ten years in Koukaku Tower.
She must have so many things she wants to tell her mother.
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
Nami!  Caimie!
Wait.  Princess Shirahoshi is there, too.
Whaaat!
Nami!  Has the banquet started yet?
Nami-swaaaaaaaan!
He's completely recovered.
Hacchin!  What happened to you?
Caimie.
Are you sure?  Hody did such a thing?
Yeah.
To think that the situation
at Ryuuguu Palace is so bad.
So what happened to Zoro and the others?
I don't know.
I thought we'd go back after we found you.
I-I can't...
I can't believe that my father could be captured like that!
Luffy-kun, my apologies.
I didn't want you to get in trouble,
that's why I left a message for you.
But it seems that you've already been caught up in our affairs.
It is important for us to hurry,
but when I met you two years ago the circumstances were different,
and I couldn't tell you this story at that time.
I wanted to offer you my most profound gratitude for stopping Arlong's crew in East Blue.
That was you, wasn't it?
Thank you.
Once again, I'd like to give my thanks.
But at the same time, I must apologize.
Jinbe-san.
The one who set Arlong loose on East Blue eleven years ago...
was me.
King Neptune.
Don't turn back!  Do you want the king's kindness to go to waste?
There's the exit!
Alright!  We managed to get out!
Use the Bubbly Corals!
How can this be?!  Not only did we leave the king in the castle alone...
but the guards were the only ones
who made it out!  What a disgrace!
Stop crying about it!  This was the king's order!
Men!  This is not a retreat!
We will definitely take out the pirates
inside the palace, and rescue the king!
But first, we need to contact
Fukaboshi and the other princes!
As soon as we've gotten in touch with the princes, and got reinforcements from their troops,
we will return to Ryuuguu Palace!
Yes, Sir!
What's the closest city?
Fishverly Hills.
Watch out!
Meanwhile, in the high class area of Fishman Island,
Fishverly Hills.
Run!
Everyone line up!
Hurry it up, unless you wanna die!
That's... What do you expect us to do?!
Step on it.
What?!
It's a test.
Don't be absurd!
Silence!  This country will soon belong to Captain Hody -hi.
Fumi-e: an icon that's desecrated to show non-allegiance
Step on the fumi-e!
Oh no... I couldn't...
Now, step on it!
Northeast, in the Candy Factory City.
C'mon, get to it!
I-I can't.
Forgive me!  I can't step on it!  Not on her face!
Silence!
You're a human-lover if you don't step on her face!
In other words, you're our enemy!
Southeast, in front of the Fish-People Cultural Center.
No way!
Hey!
It should be an easy choice, right?
Either you step on the fumi-e, or you leave the island.
Don't be ridiculous!
Damn it!  Don't we get a say in this?!
Hurry it up.  If you don't like either choice...
I've been told that I may kill you.
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the east.
Leave the country?!  That's nonsense!
This is the only place on the ocean floor that gets sunlight!
We can't live in the humans' world either!
See?  You're aware of the humans' cruel discrimination against us.
What?  What are you doing?
What's going on?!
Humans and fishmen living in harmony is nothing but a foolish fantasy.
Just obey us, and bow down before King Hody.
We will rule the humans, and change history!
North, in the Waterwheel City.
Dosun!
Come on.  You're next.
Just make it easy on yourself.
I can't!
I will crush anyone...
who refuses to step on the fumi-e -dosun!
It's you!
Don't get in my way, Fukaboshi!
What do you think you're doing?
Forcing the citizens of this country
to step on a picture of my late mother?!
And in the southeast, on Coral Hill,
the place Luffy and the others just left.
What should we do?!
We let Vander Decken escape,
and Princess Shirahoshi was abducted by the pirate with the straw hat right before our eyes!
But the princess said she'd be back by dinner.
You idiot!  He obviously forced her to say that!
Apparently the people from the Fishman District are causing disturbances in several cities.
What?!
What's happening on this island?!
Young mermaids are disappearing all over the island...
What if the princess ends up
being sold to the Celestial Dragons?!
Hey!  Another young mermaid seems to have disappeared!
How scary!
This is awful!
That's my doing...
But more importantly, I just saw something amazing!
Big Sized Mermaid!
If a human-sized mermaid
is worth seventy million beli...
Then if I could capture that Mermaid Princess, who is seven or eight times as big...
And then sell her off!
It's such a huge sum, I can hardly even imagine it!
You...
Why, good day to you!
Father.
It is alright, Princess Shirahoshi.
Even if they manage to restrain the king,
they won't get the chance to actually harm him.
Really?
Yes.  I promise I will save the king!
Alright.  Please do, Boss.
But I'd like some time to speak
to Luffy-kun and his friends first.
My dear ladies...
I made tea.
Thanks.  Leave it there, Sanji-kun.
Also, we're trying to have a serious conversation, so quit goofing around.
Oh Nami-san, I love it when you're strict!
You haven't changed, Sanji-chin.
Delicious.
I didn't make it for you!
So, Jinbe-san...
What did you mean?
You said you were the one who set Arlong loose on East Blue.
Jinbe-san...
Yes.
I heard about that.
Long ago, when Luffy and I first heard about the Warlord Jinbe...
Yosaku told us that.
In exchange for a place among the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Jinbe unleashed a terrible guy upon East Blue.
Hmm, did he?
Knowing you, you probably just forgot.
I wonder how Yosaku's doing?
Two years ago, when I read that article
that said you and Jinbe were working together...
It set question marks dancing around inside my head.
I'd always assumed that Jinbe was
the mastermind controlling Arlong from the shadows.
Hey, Jinbe.
If you have some excuse then I'm willing to listen...
but choose your words carefully.
There's no need to hide it.
The hometown of our beautiful navigator Nami-san...
was on the island that Arlong took over.
As a result, she's been put through hell.
If what you just said is true...
then I will never forgive you.
Jinbe-san...
Hacchin!
Your wounds will reopen!  You can't move around yet!
It's true!  The scars we left her...
are so deep that we can never be forgiven, no matter how much we apologize.
I'm going to travel across the oceans of the world,
using my own navigational skills!
And then I'll draw a map of the entire world,
based on the things I've seen!
Then this map you drew of the island is the first step toward your dream?
Yeah!
I am your adopted mother, after all.
You two are my precious family.
Pirates!  Pirates are coming!
Greetings... you disgusting, pitiful humans.
From now on, this village...
No, this entire island, belongs to me!
One hundred thousand beli for each adult.
Fifty thousand beli for every child.
We will kill anyone who doesn't pay this tax!
Die for your ridiculous love.
Nojiko!  Nami!
I love you.
What's this?  A map?
Don't!
I drew that map!  It's my treasure!
Give it back!
You drew this?
Don't, Nami!
Very impressive.
She will be useful.  Bring her along.
Right.
No!  Let go!  Let go of me!
No!  Don't!
Why should I have to feed a human?
Just shut up and keep drawing maps!
Gather up one hundred million beli,
and bring it here to me.
If you can do that,
I will release your village and set you free.
Thief!  She stole our treasure!
It's just a kid!
I don't care!  Kill her!
Damn it!  Chase her down!
Seventy million more.
If I can get seventy million more beli, I can...
Oh, I'm impressed that you came back.
Heh, not like you had any other choice.
Welcome back, my cartographer.
It sounds like you've suffered a lot.
Don't talk like this doesn't concern you!
Indeed.
Whatever happened to him,
I'm never gonna feel sorry for Arlong.
But, two years ago,
before I came to the Sabaody Archipelago,
I never knew...
that the fishmen, despite their strength,
were discriminated against by humans.
When Caimie was kidnapped
and we chased after her, I doubted my own eyes.
Because I saw the Sabaody Park, and it looked exactly like the Arlong Park that Arlong built.
We always longed for it.
I'm not saying this because I want forgiveness, Nami.
Arlong-san hated humans...
He held a grudge against them.
We went too far.
But, ever since we were children...
we longed for the world
that humans lived in, and that's a fact.
Both me, Arlong-san...
and all the others.
Apparently, in the past,
humans and fishmen were divided...
but then Ryuuguu Kingdom became a part
of the World Government two hundred years ago.
In order to form diplomatic ties with the humans...
the king was given a place in the world council.
But humans continued to hate fishmen.
The worst time I've experienced in my life was when the Great Pirate Age began.
I can still remember the fear of seeing human pirates coming and running wild on this island.
I'll never forget it.
Fishman Island was occupied by humans.
The one who saved us was the late old Whitebeard.
The Old Man announced that he was making Fishman Island his turf,
and peace returned to the island.
But it didn't put an end to
the humans' hate of fishmen.
I'm sure you all saw it too, on Sabaody.
The harsh reality.
It's strange how it goes...
Once someone has gained power, they are terrified of change.
The Government decided that
humans and fishmen should coexist.
Yet the ones who held power and made that decision discriminated against us more than anyone else!
The relationship between humans and fishmen
didn't change at all.
Because of that,
two people rose up here on Fishman Island...
in an attempt to put an end to this despicable history.
The first one was Queen Otohime.
Princess Shirahoshi's mother, who encouraged the islanders to live in peace with humans.
And the other was the hero who freed the slaves...
Fisher Tiger.
Something Tiger...
I think I've heard about him before.
He proclaimed that he would
cut our ties with the humans...
and he broke a worldwide taboo.  He went into
the Holy Land of Mariejoa and attacked them, alone.
He freed the slaves.
And after that, he brought all
the former fishman slaves together,
and formed the Sun Pirates!
Sun...
Indeed.  I, Arlong, and Hachi.
Naturally, we were all...
members of the Sun Pirates.
However, having the fishman pirates out at sea, fiercely fighting against the World Government...
made it harder for Queen Otohime,
who was trying to unite humans and fishmen.
Unlike Queen Otohime, who wanted to
endure the present and change the future...
Fisher Tiger abandoned such hopes for the future,
and saved fishman slaves who suffered in the present.
No one can say for sure which one was right.
Let me tell you...
about these two great people, who attempted to change the destiny between humans and fishmen.
And about the screams of their souls.
Queen Otohime, who tried to guide the kingdom to a future where humans and fishmen could coexist.
And the hero, Fisher Tiger, who attempted to free the slaves and fight back against the humans.
The fates of these two, overlapped, and a great event that would change history began!
Fisher Tiger forms the sun Pirates, and has a fateful encounter with a girl who lived through a cruel reality!
Next time, on One Pace:
Otohime, Fisher Tiger, and the Sun Pirates!
The Fateful Encounter!