This is bad. It's too dangerous here!
The Inferno Floor sure is hot.
W-Warden! Please, wait a second!
Please don't fight him just yet!
Get away from here!
We'll be affected by the Warden's poison!
What the hell?
And I'd almost gotten to where that nice smell was coming from, too!
S-Straw-chan! You can't fight him!
That's Magellan, the Warden of Impel Down!
He's got the power of the Doku Doku Fruit!
Doku: Poison
Run away! This guy's too much for you to handle!
Doku Doku? So he's a poison man.
That's right.
Straw Hat Luffy...
The rookie I hear has caused trouble wherever he's gone,
has opposed both Navy HQ and the World Government, and has a 300 million beli bounty.
I never dreamed that man would break into the legendary, impenetrable prison.
As the Warden, this is very disgraceful for me.
I know what you've come here for.
You want to free your brother, the commander of Whitebeard's Second Division, Portgas D. Ace!
After capturing you, I'll take my time with you to learn just how you managed to break in here.
I had hoped I could be of more help to you...
I'd die before telling you that!
Straw-chan! Magellan's entire body is poisonous!
You'll be in huge trouble if you so much as touch him!
Do you really think you stand a chance against a man like him?!
Get back to the Cauldron of Blood where we were before, and turn right!
Straw-chan, just give up on the food, and let's make a run towards Level Five!
That won't work!
The stairway leading to Level Five is guarded by a Head Jailer and three Demon Guards!
We've already sealed off all escape routes from this floor!
No matter where you try to run...
you can't escape!
No! No way!
Hydra!
What is that?!
Is all of that poison?!
A huge cluster of poison?!
Wait, Warden Magellan! We're still here!
What's he doing to his own allies?!
The Hydra's made of a paralyzing nerve-poison!
Excruciating pain spreads through your entire body, and eventually kills you!
It hurts...! Hurry, give me the antidote!
Stay away from me!
Don't get in the way of my attack, you fools!
P-Please forgive me!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry! I'm so hungry!
You've still got your appetite, even now?!
You're definitely not normal, Straw-chan!
Still, it might be impossible to run away from Magellan!
Hot!
Try following me now!
I'm on fire!
Alright! I beat one of its heads!
But this is as far as you'll go!
Chloroball!
That was close!
Put on your gas masks!
Keep out of the center!
The Warden is fighting!
Tear-and-sneezing gas?
Damn, it's Magellan's poison gas!
Why is he fighting down here?!
Who's his opponent?
Maybe that intruder they were talking about?
Releasing poison gas in the depths of Hell? This is serious!
Huh? My eyes are itchy, and I can't stop crying!
Whad da hell? I cad't...
I cad't figdt lige dith!
Whad?!
The dragon stopped!
Venom Road!
If I touch him, I'm done for...
He melted the stone wall!
You're next!
I must save Ace...!
In the end, you and your brother Ace...
...will suffer the same fate!
There'll never be a better chance than now, when Magellan is fighting Straw Hat!
You're insane, you flashy bastard!
Can't you see how many enemies there are?!
It's not about how many there are! Listen closely!
They want to prevent Straw Hat from going to the lower levels,
so they've got the Demon Guards guarding the entrance to Level Five!
This is the easiest escape-route!
If we let this chance go, the net will only close in on us!
This is the best way out!
Straw Hat is bound to lose eventually!
We've got to get back up to Level Three before that happens!
You may be right...
And I haven't heard anything about Assistant Warden Hannyabal having any Devil Fruit-powers...
If I blow the rest of 'em away with the Muggy-Ball,
we might be able to handle him!
That's right.
Get ready!
I've had enough of this infernal floor!
Let's go.
We've just gotta force our way through!
Indeed!
Hannyabal-sama! It's Buggy the Clown and Mister Three!
They're trying to get back to Level Three!
Don't let them get away!
Muggy...
Candle...
Wait!
All troops, pull back!
Gomu Gomu no...
Stamp!
Magellan is capable of silencing the prisoners in the world's greatest prison...
He's the ruler of Hell...
Let's see some determination, Bon Kurei!
I'm so sorry!
No matter what I do, I can't win!
I don't stand a chance at winning!
I'm running away! Sorry!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I'm sorry!
You still have no intention of giving up?
I'll break Ace free and get out of here!
There's no way I'm gonna die before I get to him!
I won't let Ace be executed!
What's with that steam?
If I'm doomed to lose because you're poisonous and I can't touch you,
then I'd rather touch you and...
give up my arms to beat you!
If you don't want those arms,
then I'll grant your wish and take them!
Gomu Gomu no...
Jet Bazooka!
Sheesh, what a pain.
If you'd just passed through and caused a ruckus up above, I could've blamed the Warden!
Reporting in from Level Three Archway.
We've suffered some casualties from the escapees' bomb attack.
Yes, we've captured Buggy the Clown and Mister Three.
I told them they could go through, yet they still attacked me!
Freaking morons!
S-So strong! I never expected him to be that strong!
That Hannyabal...
I don't want to be tortured...
If I'm to be tortured, I'd rather bite off my tongue right now...
I'n godda bide id!
I'll bide id!
I'll weally bide id!
Is it really impossible to stand up to him?
I don't dream of such reckless things.
If I go over there, the odds of getting killed are 200%...
I'm running away!
No looking back!
There's no option... But to run!
To think you could bring me to my knees...
A cornered mouse is a frightful thing.
No matter, the poison covering your arms will be more than enough!
You're suffering, aren't you? How shameful.
Gomu Gomu no...
Twin Jet Pistol!
Poison Pufferfish!
Gomu Gomu no...
Jet...
Hydra!
Pistol!
Mist...?
Poison Cloud!
Is your eyesight growing blurry?
Are your ears ringing?
Both your hands must be useless by now.
The poison will take everything away from you before long!
Hey, guards!
Tell me the truth!
Something's going above us isn't it?
No. Nothing at all.
Stamp!
That's quite enough, isn't it?
Gear Second!
Hydra!
Give Ace...
back!
This is your punishment.
After exposure to this much poison, no antidote will save you.
You will agonize for 24 hours...
and then you will descend to the real Hell!
Ace...!
Well done, Warden Magellan.
What about the fallen Straw Hat Luffy?
He'll die soon enough.
If you leave him there, he'll just be in our way.
Throw him into the central chamber of Level Five.
Yes, Sir!
W-Warden Magellan!
We've got trouble outside the stairway to Level Three!
What happened?!
We don't have the details yet...
Hey...
Hey!
This guy's done for.
He's either dead, or he's preserved for the future.
No way...
M-My fingers...
My fingers won't move...
I can't feel anything in 'em, either...
You've got frostbite, huh? Then you won't last much longer either.
Damn, they're just mocking us.
We can't even eat the bread they feed us.
Huh? Hey, check this out!
A new one got thrown down here.
Hey, what's your name?
How big's your bounty, new guy?
It's too late for this one.
He's received the poison punishment.
What is the meaning of this?!
Hannyabal! How could you let all your troops fall as you stood by?!
Wake up, Hannyabal!
What happened here?!
W-Warden! Please let me go!
I-I'm so sorry! I let my guard down!
I don't want to be tortured!
Goumon: Torture
Asses stink!
Koumon: Anus
Damn that Okama bastard!
He abandoned us!
The culprit was an Okama using Kenpo.
I guess you could say he caught us by surprise...
Spare me the excuses!
He's climbed the stairs and escaped to the upper levels, I presume?
The prisoner was a member of Crocodile's organization, Baroque Works.
A man who calls himself Mister Two...
Uh, I mean, an Okama.
What difference does it make?
He was imprisoned on Level Three.
It should only be a matter of time before they catch him.
What about the commotion on Level Two?
It seems to have finally calmed down.
Send all the soldiers gathered here up to Level Three!
Have Sadi-chan take command and release the Demon Guards!
They'll take care of the rest.
Very well. What about these two prisoners?
Do whatever you want.
Just hurry and clean up this mess. Get Impel Down back to normal!
I will now seclude myself again.
Diarrhea, huh?
Hey! You guys, get up, and look for the last escapee!
Yes, sir. Right away!
Uh... Umm... What do we do with these two?
Oh, I've got something I wanna ask them.
Send them to the interrogation room.
I'll handle them myself.
Understood.
We'll leave you alone then, Assistant Warden.
You saved us!
W-We managed to avoid torture!
Very well, what do we do now?
Ain't it obvious?
We've got to hurry and...
save Straw-chan before it's too late!
S-Save him?
Didn't you hear the soldiers? He was poisoned by Magellan and thrown down to Level Five!
There's no hope for Straw Hat now!
We'd just die like dogs!
I don't care if I die like a dog, an Okama or whatever!
The second I turned my back on Straw-chan and Magellan, I forfeited my own life!
As I ran away, I made a pledge; "Rather than dying in vain here and now, I'll run away,
and as long as you survive, I'll come back and save you even if it kills me!"
I don't mind you making a pledge or whatever,
but why would you go and risk your life again now that you've finally escaped?
Because he's my friend!
That's all the reason I need!
Your... friend?
If we're gonna save Straw-chan, we've gotta do something about the poison first!
That's it! We need an antidote!
It won't be easy to get something so valuable.
And it's probably too late already...
Shut up!
This is something I have to do!
Wait for me! Please don't die, Straw-chan!
What?!
Uh, I mean... What do you mean, you can't make an antidote?
No one who's fought Warden Magellan and been exposed to his multi-layered poison has survived.
We might be able to counteract one of them, but there's no way to cure someone of all of his poisons!
And you dare to call yourselves medical specialists?!
Are you kidding me?!
That is, don't try to fool me!
Just do something!
It's been decided that we're to hand
Straw Hat Luffy over to the Navy alive!
But injecting him with random antidotes might just hasten his death.
I'm afraid he's beyond saving...
That's why I said we couldn't save Straw Hat!
There's no antidote for him.
We're all out of options!
It'd take a miracle to go up against that guy and live to tell the tale.
A miracle?
That's it! Just the person we need is here in Impel Down!
The Okama Queen, Iva-san!
He's saved people whom doctors deemed incurable...
and rescued all the inhabitants of a country on the verge of death!
The legendary, ultimate Okama star, Iva-san!
We've got to go and find him quickly!
Iva-san... Who's that?
Staff Stairway
You're going to Level Five?
That's right.
I've sentenced these two to freeze down there.
Keep moving!
In any case, we've got no choice but to go!
Wait for me, Straw-chan!
But this list of prisoners bothers me...
What's going on?
Emporio Ivankov...
The name of the great Okama Queen, Iva-san, has been crossed out.
Could he have been released already?
Or was he sentenced to death?
Was this prisoner released?
Huh? Oh, Ivankov...
A few years ago, he was, you know...
What are you talking about?
Have you forgotten, Assistant Warden?
Oh, right. That. That thing.
I take it you know what he means? Let's hear it.
With the prisoners here...?
Just say it!
The disappearances that sometimes happen within Impel Down.
It's nothing like an escape.
Prisoners who can't even move suddenly vanish, without leaving a single trace.
The Demon's Tug.
Everyone is afraid of these unnatural disappearances,
and because some think they might've been dragged into the world of demons,
it has earned the name Demon's Tug.
People just...
Vanish?
I wish I hadn't heard that story.
You can say that again.
It's so cold!
And they haven't even opened the doors yet!
Even through all these clothes we're wearing!
We're here.
Be careful of the cold and the Army Wolves.
Now, as usual, I'll take your things.
Huh? What things?
Your weapons and your coat.
What?
Man, we really can't compare to you.
You keep saying "I'm gonna show the prisoners how tough an Assistant Warden I am",
so you go through the Frozen Hell half-naked and unarmed!
All of us guards really admire you!
Wha-?!
And of course, we can't have the prisoners walking around in warm clothes...
They took his coat-
What?!
Take care, now!
Keep in mind, Snail Phones don't work out in that cold!
Be careful!
What?!
I... can't control my hands properly in this cold...
It's cold! It's so cold, it hurts!
J-Just a little more...!
I got them off!
You did it!
1, 2, 3, 4...
Hey, you d-don't think those're the Army Wolves, do you?
Do you k-know why these things aren't up on the Accursed Beasts Floor?
No, why?
I k-k-k-know...
It's b-b-because if they were let loose on Level Two, they'd eat the Basilisk, the Sphinx and all the other beasts!
They're that strong?!
So they're a whole new level of savagery?!
First they take our coats and force us to suffer the cold, and now we've gotta face the Army Wolves?!
Now I'm quivering even more than before...
Then let's get ready to fight 'em off!
We're gonna save Straw-chan!
I don't wanna get eaten, dammit!
You're running away already?!
We've got one unusual fellow here...
They need us to get his time of death or something?
It hurts...
I wanna go save Ace!
It is as futile as a single ant jumping into a storm. {need to check this! I thought I used hurricane here. I am almost certain, unless it was changed post-edit. I will check within a day. skip this line, please. -kae}
You might get cast aside without even a chance of doing anything.
Quit wasting your breath.
After being poisoned that badly, there's no way you'll survive.
Looks like you can't see. Can you even hear me?
Just accept your death.
No way! I won't die!
I... refuse to die...
Until I've saved Ace...!
You wanna save someone else?
You can't even save yourself, ya know.
They got a friend of yours locked up in here or somethin'?
Ridiculous. In prison, you only look out for yourself.
There's nobody gonna save ya...
Nobody'll ever come to save ya...
We're all on our own here.
Get thrown into the sea of fire, and you gotta step on other prisoners to get back up.
If you meet the beasts, you grab whoever's nearby and use them as bait to protect yourself.
Try to help someone else, and you'll end up dead yourself!
So stop raving about wanting to rescue anyone!
You're makin' me sick!
Hey look, someone's coming.
Doesn't look like surveillance or staff...
What's with that guy?
He's naked...
Straw-chan... I'm here to save you...!
In the name of our friendship...!
What's with this guy?
He's covered in blood.
Back there, I...
I'm so sorry I ran away!
How do you know this guy?
I'm his friend!
Straw-chan, I won't let you die!
He left the keys...
Breaking out, huh? I'd never even considered it...
I have to hurry and find Iva-san!
Iva-san?
How should I know where that damn Okama went?
Who are you, anyway?
Emporio Ivankov...
Yeah, he was here a while back.
Isn't he dead now?
What's with that look?
What's the point of searching for someone who's not here?
Nevermind that, how'd you get out of the cage?
Let me out too, okay?
I'm looking for someone named Iva-san.
Hello, you listening?
Hey, can you hear me?!
It's no use.
The guys in that cell have all frozen to death.
Uh...
I heard you.
You want to know about that damn Okama, Ivankov, right?
Do you know something?
Look over there.
You can see the forest, right?
Yeah...
There's a jailer's room over there that no one uses anymore.
I've seen a weird guy coming out of there a few times.
Really?
If you think I'm lying, go see for yourself.
Thanks!
Don't mention it.
Hey, isn't the wolves' den out in that forest?
Oh, really?
A gate to the underworld?
The Demon's Tug? What the hell is that supposed to mean?!
I won't accept such a stupid reason for Iva-san's disappearance!
I've never met him, but people say he's performed countless miracles.
And I believe he's still working miracles here!
Iva-san is the God of the Okama world!
I beg of you! Save Straw-chan's life!
If there's no antidote to this poison,
then you're the only one who can save him!
I can only have faith and keep searching!
Oh, crap!
Straw-chan?!
What are you...
doing...
to Bon-chan...?!
Get away...
from Bon-chan!
S-Straw-chan!
What...
was...
that...?
Time left until Ace's execution...
26 hours.