Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Some things cannot be stopped.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
The tides of time,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
Translation
danpmss
FUNimation
Gaijin
danpmss
FUNimation
Gaijin
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Adventure on Little Garden
I wonder if it'll snow again.
Why would it?
{Oh, it will. You don't know since
you slept through it last time.}It just does. You don't know 'cause you slept through it.
Huh?
Hey, do you think it'll snow again?
{It could snow, but the sea
we were in first is special...}It could snow, but the sea where
we first sailed was special.
{since the seven magnetic forces from
Reverse Mountain mess it all up.}The seven magnetic fields from
Reverse Mountain wreak havoc on it.
However, you shouldn't let
down your guard here, either.
{It'd be rare for this sea
to be wild like where we first sailed,}Rarely is this sea as rough
as where we first set sail,
{but it's still truethere's no doubt that this sea is a lot more difficult harsher than ordinary ones.}but the fact remains; this sea is
much harsher than ordinary waters.
{Never underestimate it.
That's the ironclad rule.}Never underestimate these seas.
That's the ironclad rule.
Hey guys!
Wanna try a special drink I made?
Yeah!
Thanks!
{Say, Usopp.
Make a fishing tackle for me.}Hey, Usopp.
Make us some fishing gear.
Fishing, huh? You might
be on to something!
{Okay. Then I'll make a stylish
fishing rod for you.}All right! I'll even make 'em
nice and stylish for you!
{Wow, you sure can drink.
Hey, is it good?}Wow, you sure can put them away.
So, is it any good?
You're amazing, Karoo!
How is any of this okay?!
Here. For you.
What?
It'll be fine.
{They'll work hard if it storms...
since they don't wanna die.}They'll pick up the pace in a squall. They want to stay alive too.
{That's true, but it makes me feel
like I'm worked up over nothing.}{Good point. Then am I
getting worked up over nothing?}I suppose.
They just seem so distracted.
{This ship just washes away
all your worries, doesn't it?}As long as you’re on this ship, you won’t feel much stress.
Yes, it is quite relaxing.
Hey everyone, look! It's a dolphin!
He's cute!
It's humongous!
Get a move on!
Will do!
Okay!
Yep!
All right!
Take that side!
On it!
Everyone...
Unfurl the sails!
Okay! Ride the wave
and lose that dolphin!
Nami! What's our next heading?
Hold on a sec. Let me check.
Full turn aport!
Okay!
Whoa!
There's no mistake.
{That island and Cactus Island
are pulling against each other.}It's linked with Cactus Island.
The next stop on our trip is...
that island!
There it is!
Our second island in the Grand Line!
Kyuka Island
The Grand Line
Mr. 3.
What is it? A moment, please.
No other tea can
compare to Earl Grey.
I'm bored.
{You say you're bored,
but you don't like working, right?}You insist that you're bored,
yet you dislike work, right?
Right.
{Then, why don't you try enjoying
this joyous free time a little?}In that case, why not try
to enjoy this wondrous time off?
{Being able to take a long vacation like
this is a privilege to officer agents.}Extended vacations are a privilege
afforded only to officer agents.
Also,
{stop calling me by my code
name in public like this.}you mustn't refer to me
Mr. 3
Officer Agent, Baroque Works
{stop calling me by my code
name in public like this.}by my code name in public.
{People will find out
that I'm Mr. 3.}People will discover
that I'm Mr. 3.
You think?
Miss Golden Week
Officer Agent, Baroque Works
By the way, you've been staring
at that piece of paper for days now.
What ever could it be?
An order from the boss.
Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Apparently, Mr. 5 was taken out.
{Humph! If someone had to get taken down,
I wish it were someone like Mr. 2.}Hmph! Though I would've much preferred that it were Mr. 2.
Then you'd get a promotion, right?
{Mr. 5 being taken down isn't
worth making a big deal over.}Mr. 5's defeat isn't worth
making a fuss over.
{After all, that man is just an idiot with devil fruit powers, who was overconfident of his own position.}Alas, he's simply a novice who overestimated his status and abilities.
No matter how amazing
the devil fruit power one gains,
{if he can't fully utilize it,
his existence is a total waste.}if one can't properly utilize it,
that person's existence is wasted.
{Superb criminals execute their
crimes using their superb brains}Only the most superb minds execute the most superb crimes.
To whomever took him out,
why don't we reveal
{the terror of making
a criminal organization their enemy.}the terror that comes from defying
this criminal organization?
So this is Little Garden!
What's "little" about it?
This place doesn't quite
fit its cute name.
{Ahh... It's like a terra incognita.
It's a thick jungle!}Ah! It's like an uncharted island.
The jungle's so thick!
We'll need to be careful.
I'm worried about what
Miss All-Sunday was saying.
But what's even unluckier is
the course your log pose indicates.
The name of the next island is...
Little Garden.
We'll just sit back and relax,
{You'll be wiped out long before
you can even reach Arabasta.}as you'll be wiped out long before
you reach Arabasta.
{A-a-are you saying
a monster may appear?!}L-L-Like a monster
might show up?!
Who knows?
{Let's go to our next destination
without going ashore on this one!}Then at this next stop,
let's stay aboard the ship!
{But the log can't be
stored so quickly.}Y'know, the log could
take a while to register.
Also, we have to
stock up on food soon.
{We didn't get anything
in the last town we were in.}We didn't get anything
from that last town.
There's a river over there!
What? Really?
{I hope there's a barbecue
restaurant in here.}Let's find a barbecue restaurant!
As if there'd be one!
{But you said we were
going to stock up on food.}What happened to
stocking up on food?
We'll collect food to cook later!
Honestly! You got a screw loose?
But it's dangerous to go ashore.
{Just take a look at
the plants here to start with.}For starters, take a look
at these plants.
{I've never seen anything like them,
even in encyclopedias.}There's nothing like them
in any encyclopedia.
Ah!
You're so cute!
You mean me?
Obviously I meant Nami-san !
What in the world is that?!
It's all right. It's just a bird.
And this is just a jungle.
Don't worry.
Right?
What's your problem,
you damn bird?!
A lizard? I wonder
if it tastes good.
{Is that a kind of noise you
hear from just any jungle?}Do jungles normally
make that kind of noise?
That sounded like a volcano!
A tiger?!
It's way too big!
Ah!
What...?! What happened to it?!
This isn't normal!
This is definitely not normal!
{Why does a tiger, king of the jungle,
fall covered in blood?!}Why would a tiger, king of the jungle,
collapse in a bloody heap?!
Ah! It's decided that we're
not gonna go ashore!
{We'll quietly wait on the ship
until the log is stored and...}We'll wait quietly on the ship,
and when the log is ready,
we leave this island immediately.
Right!
{W... We have to go
to Arabasta quickly...}W-We're in a hurry
to get to Arabasta.
Sanji! Lunch!
Lunch?
Yeah! For replenishing energy!
A pirate lunch
with lots of meat and no veggies!
I smell adventure!
W-Wait a sec!
Where are you going?!
Adventure!
Wanna come along?
Adventure! Adventure!
{It's useless... I can't stop him.
He's too enthusiastic...}It's no use. You can't stop him
when he gets this enthusiastic.
{Unbelievable! There's a monster
that beat up a huge tiger in here!}No way! Somewhere in here is a
monster that beats up huge tigers!
Sanji! Lunch!
You got it. Coming right up.
Say, do you mind if I come along?
What?!
Sure! C'mon! C'mon!
Not you too!
Yeah. If I stay here,
{I may start thinking
about all sorts of things.}I might begin to brood.
{I'll go out to take my mind off
things until the log is stored.}Exploring will distract me
until the log sets.
No way! Luffy going is one thing,
but it's too risky for you!
{I'll be fine.
Karoo will be with me.}I'll be fine.
I'll have Karoo by my side.
{He's too shocked
to say a word, though.}His face tells
a different story, though.
{Then, I'll make a
"love lunch" for Vivi-chan.}Then Vivi-chan gets
a sweetheart lunch.
Could you also prepare
a drink for Karoo?
Of course! Leave it to me!
Okay.
{Now then! Two "pirate lunches"
and a special drink for Karoo.}Two "pirate lunches" and a special
drink for Karoo. You're all set.
Okay!
Well, then. See you later!
All right! Let's go!
We'll be back in a little while!
Miss Wednesday sure is brave.
As expected from someone who
infiltrated an enemy organization.
{Well, I'm bored too,
so I'll go take a walk.}Well, I'm bored too.
I'm going for a walk.
A walk?!
Ah! Hey, Zoro!
Wait!
Hm?
We're short on food.
{If you see animals that appear
edible, bring them back.}If you see an animal that
looks edible, bring it back.
Okay, got it.
{I'll bring back one that
you can't possibly capture.}I'll find one that even
you couldn't possibly capture.
Hold it right there!
Huh?!
I can't just let that challenge slide!
{You can capture a bigger one
than I can, you say?!}So you think you can nab
a bigger one than me?
Of course!
You're on, then!
{Look! We'll compete over
how many kilos of meat we get.}Look! The winner brings back
the most kilograms of meat.
{Didn't you mean
to say how many tons?}Don't you mean to say tons?
{You can talk cocky once
you've brought back some prey.}Save the attitude for when
you've brought something back.
Sounds fair to me!
I wonder. Why do they
all turn out this way?
I know how you feel.
No need to cry.
I'm with you on this.
I'm screwed.{I dunno how to phrase this with the limited time the line has, but the idea is that Usopp can't depend on Nami for protection. I figure him looking at her is enough to convey the idea.}
Hey! That's my line!
But wait a sec.
Wh-Wh-What's the matter?!
N-N-N-N-Nami?!
This isn't it. This isn't it, either.
Ouch! Ow, ow! H-Hey, Nami! Nami!
Hey! What the heck
are you looking for?
I remember reading
about it in a book.
A-About what?
Little Garden.
Whoa!
What is it?
{Here, look at this!
There's a shellfish like a squid.}Here, look at this! There's a shellfish,
but it's like a squid.
A squid shellfish!
It looks a lot like an ammonite.
So, a squid shellfish?
{I feel like someone's been
following me for a while...}Why do I get the feeling
I'm being followed?
Just my imagination.
Don't screw with me!
Collier Shoot!
Hmm.
What the hell is this?
Is it edible?
Let me see. Which one was it?
I think I read it recently,
but it slipped my mind.
Hey. Why is there
a sea king on land?
A dinosaur!
A dinosaur?!
Then, this is a prehistoric island!
Huh?
{The land here is stuck
in the time of the dinosaurs!}This island hasn't progressed
past the time of the dinosaurs!
Hm?
{Since there were no exchanges
among islands in the Grand Line}Trade and culture exchange
on the Grand Line is very rare,
due to the harshness
of sea travel here.
Thus, each island establishes
its own unique culture.
{There are islands that have
an extremely sophisticated culture...}Some islands have
become incredibly advanced,
{and there are some others
that remain in the same form}and there are others
that remain unchanged,
{without progressing for several thousand
or tens of thousands years...}their progress halted for thousands,
no, tens of thousands of years.
{The nonsensical climate
in the Grand Line makes it possible.}It's all thanks to the
Grand Line's nonsensical climate.
{That's why this island exists
in the dinosaur time.}That is why this island is stuck
in the age of the dinosaurs.
Amazing!
Don't leap to it!
Usopp! Usopp!
What? What's the matter?
Did you find the book?
Yeah.
This is bad. On this island...
– Ahh!
{What? It felt like Nami-san
just called me...}What? It felt like Nami-san
just called out to me.
{To those residents,
this island is as if a "little garden."}To those residing here, this island
is naught but a little garden.
Little Garden...
is what I shall name this place.
Louis Arnote, Explorer.
So?
Brogy the Giant
What do you say?
Wh-What was that?
C-Could you repeat that?
{I asked you if you
have any alcohol.}I asked if you have any booze.
We don't have much left.
So then, you do have some!
{I-it's not for drinking.
It's for cooking and disinfection.}Wh-What we have isn't for drinking, just cooking and disinfecting.
{But if you like,
we'll give it all to you.}But if you'd like, you can have it all.
Dino...
Dinosaur?
I'm Brogy, Elbaf's strongest warrior!
{Now I've got meat, too.
I'll treat you, my guests.}Now I've got meat.
Allow me to treat you as my guests.
H-Hey.
P-Pretend we're dead,
no matter what happens.
D-Doesn't pretending to be dead
only work on bears?
Whoa! What a great view!
I wanna have my lunch up here.
This is not the time for idle chatter!
Ah! Oh? So there really are volcanoes.
And there's a mountain
with huge holes as well.
Ah!
He's been eaten!
Where am I?
Whoa!
Dorry the Giant
I was watching.
Grappling longnecks in the jungle...
What a lively human!
You're my first guest in a long time.
You're huge! Are you a human?
I'm Dorry, Elbaf's strongest warrior!
A-A giant!
I've heard of them, but this is my
first time actually seeing one.
I'm Luffy. I'm a pirate.
A pirate?! Good for you!
Karoo! Wake up!
Let's run while we can!
{Oh yeah, the ones over there are
Vivi and Karoo. Nice to meet you!}Oh yeah, those two over there are
Vivi and Karoo. Nice to meet you!
Luffy-san just had
to open his big mouth!
Let me invite you to my place!
Home of Brogy the Giant
Now, eat! Dinosaur meat is tasty.
I-I'm not hungry.
Don't hold back!
I don't want to eat.
{Dinosaur meat tastes good,
I'm tellin' ya...}But dinosaur meat is real tasty,
I'm tellin' ya.
{Is he trying to get us to eat
the dinosaur meat first}Is he gonna make us
eat the dinosaur meat...
{in order to fatten
us up a little}...just to fatten us up a bit...
...and then eat us ?
{Yeah, he's acting like
a giant, all right.}Yup. This is textbook giant, all right.
But we're still so young.
Maybe we're at peak flavor.
What a waste.
It's good, I'm tellin' ya.
{If we somehow keep fasting until
the log is stored and don't get fat,}If we manage to fast and stay thin
until the log registers,
we might survive.
But how long will it take
for the log to finish?
{If I don't eat for three days, I'm sure I'll get tempted by this smell of meat and eat it...}After a three-day fast, I'll succumb
to this meat's amazing aroma.
Brogy-san !
Can I ask you a question?
Hm? What is it, little miss?
{H-How long will it take for the log
of this island to be stored?}H-How long will it take
for this island's log to register?
One year.
What?!
Oh no... There's no way
we can fast for a year.
I definitely won't keep from eating.
Well, make yourselves at home!
Home of Dorry the Giant
This is yummy, giant old guy!
{So is that "pirate lunch" of yours,
although it's a little too small for me.}That "pirate lunch" of yours was, too,
though it was a little small for me.
You bet it's good!
That's a special lunch the chef
on my pirate ship made.
{If you say it's bad,
I'll beat you up!}Badmouth it, and I beat you up.
Beat me up, you say?
You're a riot, kid!
Th-They're becoming awfully friendly.
By the way, why are you
living here alone, old guy?
Isn't there a village or something?
Hm? There is a village.
It's a warriors' village called Elbaf.
It's elsewhere in the Grand Line.
Hm?
But there are rules in the village.
Rules?
{For example, if there's a fight in
the village and neither side give up,}For example, if a fight breaks out,
and neither party concedes,
the gods of Elbaf intercede
with their judgment.
{Elbaf's god always gives divine
protection to the righteous one}Elbaf's gods favor one party
with divine protection in battle,
and thus the victor is deemed correct.
Hmm. Elbaf's gods, huh?
I once started such a fight,
{now this island is the battleground
between a certain man and I.}and now this island hosts a duel
between another man and me.
{The righteous one will win
the duel and survive.}One of us will survive,
so that man will be correct.
{But we haven't been able to
settle this for about 100 years.}But even after 100 years,
the matter still isn't settled!
You guys've been fighting for 100 years?!
{It's nothing surprising, since our life span is at least three times as long as yours.}No surprise there. Our lifespan is
at least three times as long as yours.
Three times or otherwise,
{your interest in fighting would
wane in 100 years, wouldn't it?}wouldn't the fighting
wind down after 100 years?
{Is there any point in
continuing to fight?}Why would you
carry on for so long?!
It's a duel to the death, right?!
That's a huge eruption!
Well, time to go.
Huh?
What's that?
An eruption.
Huh?
He suddenly got so serious.
Sorry, I have to head out for a bit.
What? Head out?
{Yeah. That was a signal for the duel
that I've been in for 100 years.}Yes. That was the signal for me
to continue my 100-year duel.
A duel?
With whom? Where?!
And for what reason?!
Reason? I don't remember.
{It became our routine
before we realized it.}Before we realized it,
it had become routine.
{The eruption of the central mountain
is the signal for the duel.}When the central mountain erupts,
it's signaling for the duel.
What?!
Locked in a death match for
100 years, and with such hatred...
What in the world caused this fight?!
Stop it.
It's not like that.
Right. It's a matter of pride!
I forgot...
the reason a long time ago!