Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Some things cannot be stopped.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
The tides of time,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
Translation
danpmss
FUNimation
Gaijin
danpmss
FUNimation
Gaijin
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Dorry and Brogy
Huh? A-Are you okay?
Whoa. They're so huge!
H-He blocked the blow
with his helmet!
If he was off by even a hair,
he would've died instantly!
What a fight!
Each attack is meant
to be a killing blow!
And their duel has lasted 100 years?
But that's good news for us.
Now we can escape. Let's go!
Usopp?
Incredible.
Reason?
I don't remember.
Even without a reason, they put
their heart and soul into fighting.
I know! How annoying, right?
You don't get it!
This is what a battle
between real men is all about!
Meaning?
To use an analogy, they each
fly a warrior's flag in their hearts,
and those flags are more
important to them than life itself.
They would never
let them be torn down.
And so, to protect these flags,
they've fought for 100 years!
Now do you get it?
This is, without a doubt,
an honorable battle
between true warriors!
Whatever. Stuff like that
doesn't interest me.
Now, hurry up!
I'm gonna watch this a little longer.
They embody exactly what I want:
to be a brave warrior of the sea!
I wanna be as honorable as them!
Huh? So you wanna become a giant?
What the hell?!
Were you even listening to me?!
Hey, weren't you gonna
watch those guys?
If there's a village
full of warriors like them,
I wanna go there someday.
We both long for home,
don't we, Dorry?
That's why I'll beat you
and go back to Elbaf, Brogy.
73,466 duels.
73,466 draws.
Hey, you overgrown lizard.
Out of our way.
Leave it to me.
Ten Thousand Kilo Press!
Greetings, Mr. 5.
Nice ability you've got there,
building an instant cottage
in the jungle.
Let's be clear, though.
This mission is still ours.
We'd appreciate you staying out of it.
We won't make
the same mistake twice.
– “Mistake”?
– Hm?!
That's incorrect. You two are weak,
Mr. 5 and Miss Valentine.
Well, don't pout about it.
Take a good look at this.
I'd like to thank you for the
opportunity to visit this island.
Dorry the Blue Ogre
and Brogy the Red Ogre,
of the Giant Warrior Pirates.
There are old tales about them.
This is a wanted poster
from 100 years ago!
And now they reside here
on this very island.
Their bounty remains at
one hundred million belly per head.
Two hundred million belly
for the two of them.
Two-hundred-million-belly bounties?!
But they're giants.
Only the most superb minds
execute the most superb crimes.
All you have to do
is follow my instructions.
With a little ingenuity,
we can even cut through mountains.
Dorry! I got us some booze,
courtesy of our guests.
Great! It's been a while
since my last drink. I'd love some.
I see. His guests
are your friends, huh?
I saw a long-nosed man
and a woman.
That's Usopp and Nami!
How funny! They said
they weren't gonna leave the ship.
I guess they do like adventures!
Then, in a way, you could also say
that I got this alcohol from you.
By the way, Dorry-san,
is it true the log takes
an entire year to register?
Why, didn't you notice
the human skulls lying around?
Most people who come to this island
die before their log is ready.
Some are eaten by dinosaurs.
Others starve or
succumb to the heat.
Still, others attack us,
and we in turn kill them. They all die.
It seems that one year on this island
is too long for humans.
Then what can we do?
Even if we could survive for a year,
if that much time passes, who knows what will become of my country?
Yeah, it'd start to get pretty boring
if we stayed an entire year.
Isn't there a better way, old guy?
Hmm.
We do have an eternal pose,
but it's to our hometown, Elbaf.
You could even say we're
fighting for this eternal pose.
Do you want to try
taking it by force?
That's no good.
That's not where we wanna go.
We just wanna go to the island
after this one. Right?
Yes.
If we lose the route to Arabasta,
there's no point in moving forward.
See?
Then why don't you take a chance
and sail ahead anyway?
If luck is on your side,
you'll reach your destination.
Maybe we'll do that!
Who knows? We might just make it.
You know, long ago,
there was someone who left before the log was ready.
What happened to him?
How should I know?
He must've gotten to the next island.
That must be it!
What's so funny?
I can't understand
what they're thinking!
A brave warrior of the sea?
What's that?
I'm talking about you ! I wanna
be just like you two someday.
Hm? You mean a giant?
See?
That's not it!
I hope to live proudly
just like the warriors of Elbaf!
So, that's it!
We live so much longer
than you humans,
so we often think upon
how we will die.
Your assets, your life...
All will eventually cease to exist.
But if we die as warriors of Elbaf
with our pride intact,
that would be an honorable death.
That pride is an everlasting treasure
that is passed on in the land of Elbaf.
So, pride is your treasure?
That's so cool!
I've decided! From now on,
I will call you master!
Huh?
Giant old guy!
What's going on?!
Why did his drink explode?
That alcohol came
from our ship, didn't it?!
It exploded in his stomach!
That other giant must have
laced it with an explosive.
Were we even watching
the same thing?!
After 100 years of fighting,
they'd never do something like this!
Then who in the world…?
You bastards did.
It wasn't Brogy.
We are proud warriors
that hail from Elbaf.
Other than you,
who else is there to suspect?
We need to run!
Talking to him won't be of any use!
Probably just as useless to run.
Hold this and stay back.
You can't mean…
You plan on fighting him?
Sorry ‘bout this, old guy,
but I need to shut you up.
Both of you, stop! Please!
Dorry-san, please listen!
We're in the dark about this too!
We're clueless about the explosion!
Please don't fight!
You need to stay put! Your insides
are in bad shape right now!
How dare you...
do something so detestable!
Gum-Gum...
I'm sorry.
Rocket!!
Luffy-san !
So he has...
the powers of a devil fruit.
I underestimated... him.
Luffy-san ! Are you all right?
How's the old guy?
I think he's okay.
You made the right call.
He might not have calmed down.
I'm really ticked off!
Huh?
Like the old guy said,
that explosion isn't what the
other giant would do,
and my friends would never do
a stupid thing like that!
Then who could have...?
There's someone else
on this island.
In essence, mental anguish
sways the outcomes of conflicts.
Confusion has set in,
all thanks to a mysterious bomb
served by an invisible foe.
Now, regarding our first target,
Dorry the Blue Ogre,
finishing him off was unlikely,
but the damage his stomach received must have been considerable.
So, let us enjoy our tea
and await the start of the next duel.
And, what, we let the other giant
finish off the injured one?
That's right.
A very roundabout
way of doing things.
That's because these warrior types
act exactly like wild boars.
If we avoid a direct confrontation,
we can fight with minimal risk.
After all, we are no match
for their raw strength,
but our brain power
more than compensates for it.
Seriously! Can't you get it
on your own, Miss Golden Week?
Out of curiosity, what's the plan
with the Straw Hat gang?
Straw Hat...? Oh, the small-timers
who discovered the boss's secret.
We will lure them out one by one,
starting with the easiest among them,
right to my service set.
My motto: Wicked deeds are best served with a dash of foul play.
There are countless ways to defeat
your enemies without lifting a finger.
Mr. 3, refill please.
Hey. Me too.
You guys!
Take time to savor it!
Ah!
That mountain... Isn't it...?
There's the signal.
It's quite active today.
You're going?! Your wounds
from that last battle still haven't–
It's nothing! We're both
in the same condition!
Making excuses during a fight to
the death would disgrace my name!
Hey! Wait, old guy!
Don't go!
You can't go, Dorry-san !
You need to keep still!
You'll die if you
push yourself too hard!
I, warrior Dorry, am here.
At the very least,
I will fight to uphold
the name of Elbaf!