Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Some things cannot be stopped.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
The tides of time,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
Translation
FUNimation
Gaijin
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Foul Play
Impossible...!
Awesome! He picked up
that entire rock formation!
Luffy-san !
What're you doing, old guy?!
Get this rock off me! Hey!
We can't stop.
Over 100 years ago,
we commenced this battle.
But if I abandon it now,
I would abandon the right
to call myself a warrior.
If I am no longer a warrior,
I will cease to be me.
I was wrong to suspect you.
Elbaf, the god of war,
has passed his judgment.
He has decided that this is my fate.
I didn't have his divine protection.
That is all.
God?! Divine protection?!
None of that stuff matters!
You'd die just because
some god told you to?!
Someone is trying
to mess with your duel!
It's not a fair fight! This duel's over!
I'm right, aren't I?!
Be quiet!
You've only lived a mere
10 or 20 years.
Elbaf's divine teachings
wouldn't resonate with you.
Who gives a crap about that?!
Hey! Move this thing! Hey! Old guy!
Hey! Old guy! Hey! Dammit!
It won't budge!
All right, Master Brogy! Good luck!
You got it, Usopp!
I'm gonna wipe the floor
with him for sure this time!
Go get 'im, warrior of Elbaf!
You've got this!
You're great! You're awesome!
You're powerful!
You're huge! You're big! You're me!
Going back to his pointless duel?
A pointless duel?! You heathen!
Brogy's a brave warrior of the sea!
I plan to be just like him!
What gives you the right–
Anyway, let's get back to the ship.
We are not staying a year
just for the log to register!
We'll wait for everyone there
and come up with a plan.
Hold it! Not so fast!
I am absolutely useless
in a fight against dinosaurs!
As such, we cannot possibly
traverse the jungle to reach our ship!
Then what was all that about
being a "brave warrior of the sea?"
You caught me thinking out loud!
I want to become a man
who's proud of the way he lives!
No choice then.
Luffy's party is
at the other giant's home.
Guess we'll head there.
Listen, Nami.
Someday down the road,
if I wind up losing everything,
and greet death all alone
on a deserted island,
as I lay dying, I will proudly proclaim:
"I am Usopp!
Brave warrior of the sea!"
Yeah, yeah.
Then will you hurry it up
and get your warrior act together?
Oh.
Yeah!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
Yeah. Truly the nectar of the gods.
Overstating things a bit,
I see! Let's go!
What's wrong, Dorry?!
You're a bit sluggish!
Don't kid yourself!
I'm the same as ever!
Move, you stupid thing! Come on!
Just when I've gone and met
such an awesome warrior!
Luffy-san...
Why would he go this far
for a giant he just met?
It's out of character for a crook
with a bounty on his head.
Who was it?! Who messed
with the giants' duel?!
Come to think of it...
Karoo is gone!
Damn. I'm lost.
I at least recognize this tree.
I'm sure it was a left
at the tree wrapped in vines.
Oh! It's you, Nami!
Perfect timing!
See, I sorta lost my way,
so I wasn't sure what to do.
What're you doing here, anyway?
Hey, what's the deal?
Dinosaur!
Dinosaur! Dinosaur! Dinosaur!
Hey, you! You're going too fast!
That guy...
Luffy!
What a relief!
What're you doing here?
N-Nami?
Nami! Nami! Nami! Nami!
This is bad.
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Ow-ow-ow...
It's horrible! A dinosaur ate Nami!
Wait! What?!
One moment we were running
through the jungle to escape it,
and the next she was gone!
What have I done?!
I let my crewmate get killed!
H-Hold on! Calm down, you two!
You said she suddenly disappeared,
but did you check and make sure?
Are you crazy?! I was too terrified
to check and make sure!
If not a dinosaur,
then it was a wild beast!
What else could it have been?!
I don't know.
But if someone from Baroque Works
followed us onto this island,
then it would make sense if
Nami-san was taken instead of you.
What?! Baroque Works
might be on the island?!
Wait... why wouldn't
they go after me?
Because there's only a slim chance
you're on their hit list.
Ah! That makes sense!
Plus, that alcohol
might've been meant for us, too!
That alcohol?! What do you mean?!
Brogy brought your alcohol to Dorry.
And when Dorry drank it,
it exploded inside his stomach.
What?! Our alcohol exploded inside his stomach?!
You're saying he continued
the duel all busted up like that?!
Just see what happened to me
when I tried to stop him!
You can't be serious!
Those two've fought on equal ground
at full strength for 100 years!
It's probably the most
honorable battle ever fought!
Yeah.
They can't settle the fight
like this now!
What's wrong?!
He's still fighting.
Yes. Dorry the Blue Ogre
is quite stubborn indeed.
Perhaps I should assist one of them.
One century.
It was a long battle!
Elbaf, the god of war,
has passed his judgment.
He has decided that this is my fate.
I didn't have his divine protection.
That's all.
– Luffy!
– Luffy-san ?!
Who was it?!
Show yourself!
Mr. 3. I think I heard something.
How amusing! An underdog loser,
yelping out here in the jungle!
Seventy-three thousand...
four hundred sixty-seven duels.
Seventy-three thousand
four hundred sixty-six draws...
and one win!
Tears of joy over your victory?
Simpletons have it so easy.
Though, perhaps I'll
congratulate you for now.
Tears of joy?!
What would you know?!
Just who are you?!
Mr. 3. Please excuse the code name.
I'm a mere wax sculptor.
And this is my assistant and
realist painter, Miss Golden Week.
What's more,
I've already captured you.
Wh-What is this?!
All right, Luffy!
I dunno who we're dealing with,
but I'll go take care of them myself!
I'll come with you!
Yes! Please come with me!
I'll need the moral support!
There's no need for that!
It's you guys!
You can have him back.
We don't need him.
Karoo!
Why, you!
Hey, who are they?
They're from that last town!
What are you doing here?!
Karoo has nothing to do with this!
That's right. This bird has
absolutely nothing to do with this.
The only one we considered
a threat was that straw hat guy.
The plan was to make the bird
call you away from that guy,
but the duck was just too obstinate.
Now! Call for your owner!
Quack especially loud,
and we'll let you go free!
Fine! Want us to make you quack?!
Call for the princess!
Call for help this instant!
Open your mouth, you damn bird!
But it looks like Straw Hat's
already out of the picture.
So the duck's no use to us now.
Karoo!
What a stupid bird!
Why, you!
Are you the ones
who made the alcohol explode?!
Yes, that was us. Who's this guy?
Is he on the list?
No. Perhaps he's a shipmate.
Let's make him disappear too!
So, you interfered
with the giants' duel!
It was them?! I'll kick their asses!
You're the ones who'll disappear!
Oh? You're gonna start something, Miss Wednesday?
What makes you think
you're a match for officer agents?
Peacock Slasher!
Take this!
Lethal Exploding Star!
Yes!
Thanks for the updraft!
Nose Fancy Cannon!
Pitiful man!
Usopp!
Ten Thousand Kilo Press!
Give it a rest.
Why so agitated?
We're not going to kill you just yet.
We only came to capture you.
All per Mr. 3's orders.
Mr. 3?! The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
Does that mean he's here?!
That's right.
He's a candle man who controls
wax secreted from his body.
A candle man?!
You guys are gonna pay for this!
You wretch! What is all this?!
Isn't it obvious?
I'm creating a work of art.
Just be a good little girl.
Did you honestly think you could
escape from Baroque Works?
Even that guy with the bounty
of 30 million was no match for us.
I can finally say thanks for
what happened at Whisky Peak.
You wannabe pirates had it coming
for sticking your noses
in such a sensitive operation.
We've already captured your
swordsman friend and the other girl.
You caught Zoro?
Then you guys're dead meat!
Oh?
You talk awfully big
for a guy who received one of my
Kicky Bombs to the face.
Those don't hurt one bit!
I'm gonna kick all your asses!
Pitiful.
Luffy-san !
Die!
Chump!
Luffy-san !
Luffy-san ! Luffy-san !
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Luffy-san !
Usopp-san ! Karoo!
Damn you!
Give it up! Give it up!
Once solidified, my candle jacket
is as hard as steel!
You giants may have brutish strength,
but you're weak when
compared to these bonds.
Brainpower wins out in the end.
I won't stoop
to needlessly face you head on.
Upon tasting of victory,
you lowered your guard,
Brogy the Red Ogre.
Don't glare at me like that.
You're so terrifying !
You should be thrilled!
The duel has finally arrived at its long-awaited end.
Didn't you fight for a whole century
with your so-called pride on the line?
Shouldn't the taste of victory
be especially sweet, then?
Even if the fruit is borne
of another's assistance?
Am I wrong?
Filthy sneak! You didn't!
But indeed!
The final victory belongs to me!
Were you aware that your massive, long-standing bounties
amounted to 200 million belly?
Today, that is still the case.
You scum!
I feel as if I've stumbled upon
a long-lost treasure!
So that's what you're after, huh?!
Mr. 3!
Here she is.
Our company's little traitor.
What took so long?
I was getting sick of waiting.
Your underhanded scheme went too far, Mr. 3!
You arranged for Dorry-san's
alcohol to explode!
What?!
Alcohol?
You mean the drink I gave him?!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
Yeah. Truly the nectar of the gods.
So, that's what you meant?! Dorry!
You wretched girl! Who said you
could give away company secrets?
Well, no matter. Not that it
will do you any good now.
Candle...
Lock!
Mr. 5!
Bring the swordsman and the girl!
We're about to begin!
Extra-Large Candle Set!
Th-This is Mr. 3's ability?!
What's going on?!
Here they are.
Disgraceful.
Getting bested by these lowlifes
was beyond embarrassing.
I'm disgusted with myself.
You can't help that you're weak.
Huh? What was that?
None of your concern!
Just set up my candles already!
Set up?
What is that?!
Nami-san... Mr. Bushido...
Vivi! What happened?!
Weren't you with Luffy?!
Yes, I was, but–
If you mean Straw Hat,
I took him out myself!
And I didn't even break a sweat.
Is that right?
Welcome, one and all,
to my service set!
Is this how it feels
to be a candle stuck in a cake?
What's that spinning thing up there?
And I can't move my legs.
Makes sense for them
to keep us immobilized.
They're the enemy.
Damn. Too hard.
And I can't get a solid hit on it
from this stance.
Something's raining down!
I hope you enjoy my candle service!
The wax particles
settling down on you
will soon transform you
into wax sculptures!
You'll become perfect
models of humankind,
such that I never could have
achieved with my skill alone!
Behold the birth of wax statues
that literally have souls!
Now die, in the name of art.
Screw that!
Why do we have
to become your works of art?!
Brogy-san ! Get back up
and crush these maniacs!
You'll turn into
a wax statue too, you know!
Man, that's a huge person.
Nothing you say
will move him to action!
Despite a proud victory, he's realized
the absurdity of his tears of joy.
He slew his friend Dorry,
with whom he fought for 100 years,
but he utterly failed to notice the
injuries Dorry had already sustained!
Or, perhaps, were you actually
crying for your dear friend?
Whatever the case, there's no turning
back the hands of time, you fool!
I knew.
I knew about it.
From the moment
we resumed our duel,
I knew Dorry was hiding something.
You knew, huh?
A likely story!
If so, then why didn't you
call off the duel?
Anyone could see there was
no restraint in your killing blow!
A coward who knows
nothing of valor in battle
would never understand
the truth behind my tears!
And how could you know?!
Should I dishonor a warrior
who hides his injuries
and does battle anyway?!
A wounded warrior who chooses
to keep fighting asks not for mercy!
And now, I know
the reason behind it.
Now that I know, I'm going to
settle this with my own two hands!
That's the very least I can do
to honor my dear friend Dorry!
Brogy-san !
– Brogy-san !
What an annoying, talkative monster.
U-Usopp.
Usopp.
You gonna let them
get away with this?
No. No way.
Are you... angry too?
Okay then! Let's all three of us
go kick their asses!
Brogy-san !
What a halfwit!
I underestimated just how brutishly
strong these giants can be!
It's clear now that simply
restraining you won't be enough!
Wax Wax Arts: Handcuffs!
I'm just getting started!
And now, for the finishing touch!
Take this!
Just try to move now, will you?!
This is deranged...
And now, accelerate, candle service!
Turn these people into wax figures!
M-My chest is starting to burn.
The wax mist is
getting into our lungs!
At this rate, we'll turn into
wax statues from the inside out!
Yes! Yes! The more you appear to be in pain, the better!
Expressions of pain and agony
are the very things I seek in art!
May you solidify
while filled with terror!
You call this art,
you creepy topknot freak?!
And how dare you
do that to Brogy-san !
This'll come back to bite you
in the ass! You hear?!
Scream and holler all you want!
For 100 years,
day in and day out,
we fought and fought.
We dueled to maintain our pride
as warriors of Elbaf!
So then, how is this what
you promised, Oh Elbaf, god of war?!
If this is how we are
to meet our end, Oh Elbaf,
do we not deserve better?!
Should we not die in battle?!
What a great look!
Yes! That sorrow!
That grief! That struggle!
What a marvelous work of art!
Oh Elbaf!
Oh, no! My hands won't move!
I don't wanna die this way!
Can't we do something?!
My body's already becoming stiff!
What do we do?!
Zoro! Do something!
Hey, old man.
You can still move, can't you?
So can I.
Whaddya say we crush these guys... together?
Hold on, Zoro! What are you doing?!
You're not seriously–
Yeah.
Don't joke about
cutting off your legs!
It's not a joke.
It's the only way outta here.
And you two?
What about us?!
It's futile!
Even if you escape,
they'll just catch you again!
There's no way to know that
unless we try!
After all, we're gonna
kick the bucket if we stay here.
Instead, let's put up
one hell of a struggle!
I'm not gonna lie down
and die for this scum!
Right?!
What the hell? Is he crazy?
A mere bluff! What he's
threatening to do is ludicrous!
It's all an act!
You're pretty cocky, kiddo.
How embarrassing. I had just about
lost the will to fight.
But your fiery spirit
has me raring to go!
You can't be serious! Right?!
And how will you fight once you're free?!
Who knows?
But... I plan to win.
What's with these guys?!
They're off their rockers!
What kind of man is he?!
Still, I've seen this look
somewhere before.
Princess Vivi!
Are you resolved to stay alive?
W-Wait! I'll fight, too!
– Vivi!
– Good to hear.
Let's do it, kiddo!
Ridiculous! Do you even
have a plan of attack?!
Hey, you guys!
I'm gonna kick your asses,
just you wait!
What?
Let's do it, Usopp!
Yeah!
Bird!
Luffy! Usopp!
Karoo!
Master Brogy!
We'll avenge you!
Usopp!
Beat those guys beyond recognition!
Send them flying far away from here!
Yeah! I will!
They spoiled the old giant guys' duel!
Do you really have
the highest bounty in the East Blue?
My, how Navy Headquarters'
standards have fallen!
Whoa! That hair is weird!
Shut your mouth!
It's a burning number three!
Shut it!
Break this pillar first, Luffy!
We're about to turn into wax figures!
Oh? You're in trouble?
Nope. No trouble here.
Hey! Your leg!
Yeah. I got about
halfway through it, I'd say.
How can you calmly say that's "no trouble"?!
Like she said, could you
bust this pillar for us, Luffy?
After that, go wild.
Yeah, sure thing!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Dunno what it is,
but we're gonna break it!
Oh, yeah! Got it!
I'm not the same man as before!
Hurry before we turn solid!