Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Some things cannot be stopped.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
The tides of time,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
Translation
FUNimation
Gaijin
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Luffy vs. Mr. 3
Zoro! What are you doing?!
I'll need to pose if I'm turning solid.
This is no time to be playing around!
I'm not playing.
Anyway, do something about
your leg! It hurts just looking at it!
Then quit looking at it.
Only an idiot would believe
cutting off his own legs
is the best plan of escape!
You've got it wrong!
I was gonna cut 'em off
so we could fight.
That's even stupider! Get serious!
Just give it a rest!
Honestly! You have no
common sense then!
We haven't even found
a way out of this situation,
yet both are oblivious
to their present danger.
Hey, kiddo. So you're
just going to sit back now?
Sure am. I'm trusting
someone else to finish this fight.
Fascinating.
Mr. 3. They don't seem
concerned at all.
I could say the same
about you, Miss Golden Week!
Urgh!
Hey, now's the chance
for your own cool pose.
That's not something I'll do!
Mr. Bushido! Please take this
a bit more seriously.
I'm always serious.
You mean always stupid!
It's as if they're mocking us!
Like you've any room to talk!
This is most irksome!
All right!
This man doesn't seem
to pose any danger.
Mr. 3!
We'll finish him off.
Finish him off?
Don't be ridiculous.
Just look!
Your attacks didn't even faze him,
and now he's here, alive and well.
Evidently, he's a bit more
than you two could handle.
I'll leave the rest of the rabble to you!
As for Straw Hat Luffy, I'll add him
to my collection of wax figures.
This windbag is full of hot air!
You've crossed the line!
Time to eat dirt!
Small-timer.
Let's do it!
Alright! Preparations are complete!
We got your back, Luffy!
Did you say something?
Now you're mine!
Candle Lock!
What is that ?!
Luffy-san !
Damn. He got caught already?!
Bird brain!
What's this? It's heavy, like a mallet!
Piece of cake!
Now for your hands!
Oh! This is perfect!
Candle Lock!
Whoa!
Old giant guy!
Sorry to bother you!
What?! What's he up to?!
Gum-Gum...
Mallet!
He did it!
Yahoo!
Lucky! The mallet broke
from my legs too!
Huh? Huh?!
Still alive...
We survived...
Our situation hasn't changed at all!
That was dangerous!
Why didn't you guys run away?
We can't move! Can't you tell?!
What? Really?
But you guys told me
to break the pillar!
Was that wrong?
Mr. Bushido, why exactly are we
putting our lives in his hands?!
Why? That's the
only choice left to us.
Plus it looks like
my arms are stuck now.
Please take this seriously !
Hold on. It feels like my body
is solidifying more and more now.
I can't... move... anymore.
You fools!
With the candles closer to you,
you'll harden so much quicker!
Now you will become
my human wax candles posthaste!
Who does that arrogant bastard
think he is?!
Hey! You guys are
gonna be wax figures?
That's what we've been trying to tell you!
Just destroy this set, Luffy-san !
R-Right! Okay!
How dare you try and interfere!
Wax-Wax Arts: Harpoon!
Exploding Star!
Pretty bland. You don't use
high-quality gunpowder.
My exploding star... he ate it!
This is bad. It really is fast.
Good thing I posed beforehand.
You moron!
Luffy-san ! Please, hurry!
All right! That pumpkin's
the problem, right?!
Hang on!
Gum-Gum...
It's no use!
Candle Wall!
Bazooka!
Hey! Outta the way!
That would be my line.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
interfere with my creative activities.
Candle Lock!
Thanks for the mallet!
Gum-Gum...
Drat!
Candle Wall!
Mallet!
Hooray! Hooray!
– M-Mr. 3!
– Impossible!
Luffy, hurry and break this set
while there's still time!
Don't wanna.
Quit joking around and hurry!
No.
This isn't the time for your antics!
Luffy-san ! Please!
What should I do?
I don't wanna save you guys.
What are you saying?
Colors Trap.
Hey! Luffy!
There's no time! Do something
about this thing already!
Yeah, I know.
– If you know, then hurry!
– Come on, Luffy!
I know, but...
But I don't wanna save you.
Yeah, you keep saying that!
Meanwhile, we're almost wax figures!
Understand?! We're about to die!
Yeah. But for some reason,
I just don't care anymore.
It's not about whether you care!
D-Dammit!
What the hell's with him?!
If he doesn't get moving, our friends're gonna die!
I'll bring him to his senses!
Let's go, Karoo!
Wh-When did you...?!
Give it up. He's already
fallen into a trap.
That's right.
See where he's standing?
Where he's standing?
Let's see here.
What's that?
There's a strange black symbol.
What's so important about that?!
You're right. It's nothing.
It's just paint.
Paint?
To sum it up, it symbolizes the end for both you... and your friends!
Karoo! Let's just run for now!
They're flying the coop!
Let's get 'em.
Full speed ahead!
Hey, you! Wait!
I haven't gotten on yet! Karoo!
Alright! Hey! Stop! Lemme on!
Why the hell are you afraid of me ?!
Miss Golden Week!
This is your doing!
Colors Trap: Betrayal Black.
Touch the black paint,
and you'll want to betray your
friends, no matter what they say.
What does she mean?!
Tell us what happened!
That girl is a realist painter who can
recreate the colors of emotion.
Wha...?
Her refined sense of color
can be used to manipulate
those who interact with her paints.
Manipulate?! That's not good!
That simpleminded idiot is
already easy enough to manipulate!
Then... can't he just
step off the paint?
Luffy! Get away from there!
No, don't!
Luffy-san ! Whatever you do,
do not move from that black circle!
I'm begging you!
Vivi! Why?!
We absolutely do not
want you to save us!
Oh, yeah?
I see now.
He's being made to do the
exact opposite of what he's told.
Huh?
Th-That was a bit weird just now.
Luffy-san ! Hurry!
Alright! Time to save you!
Aw, forget it, you guys!
Gotta laugh!
Why?!
You little...!
Now what?!
Colors Trap: Laughter Yellow.
Hey now. Stay still.
It's on his clothes!
Luffy! Hurry and take off that vest!
N-Never mind that!
I just wanna laugh right now!
Son of a...!
At the pace it's raining down,
we won't last another minute!
Did you guys only come to fool around?!
Look! When Usopp ran into him,
the paint on his back smudged!
Did she do something to me again?
Hey, you! Knock it off, you cheater!
Was my Laughter Yellow a riot?
Shut up! Are you nuts? You dummy!
Anyway, I gotta break that pumpkin!
Gum-Gum...
Colors Trap: Bullfight Red.
Bazooka!
Where're you aiming?!
You're not allowed to break it!
You'll make Mr. 3 angry!
What the hell?!
The same way bulls
need to charge at red capes,
you now can't help but attack
my bullfight red mark.
Too bad.
You suck!
I'm gonna send you flying!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Having fun?
It's no good.
This isn't his kind of fight.
His powers are useless here!
And the finishing touch!
I'll mix the Laughter Yellow
on your back with Sadness Blue!
Colors Trap: Tranquil Green!
This tea is tasty.
You moron!
So now what?
See? I told you you should've posed!
Too late for that.
How are you still so calm?!
Damn! They're freakin' fast!
Nose Fancy Double Cannon!
You missed! Way to go, Karoo!
My turn!
Lethal Lead Star!
We gotta return
to Luffy and the others!
All this running around is pointless.
No kidding!
I didn't want to use it
on such a small-timer,
but there's no dodging this.
A .44-caliber,
six-shot, flintlock revolver.
A new model from the South Blue.
It's rapid-fire,
and when I use it,
no one'll see it coming.
Luffy's acting strange because of
that paint the bad guys mentioned!
They're related somehow!
Not to mention, he had some on his
back when I crashed into him earlier.
I'm sure of it!
I gotta take care of that paint!
Hurry!
Ahh, such lovely tea.
So nice.
Luffy! Are you kidding me?!
Such... lovely... tea...
What are you doing, you dumbass?!
It's all over for you.
This ability is second to none.
Lethal Fire Star!
How dumb can you get?!
Who shoots their own allies?!
Wasn't he gonna shoot?!
Breeze Breath Bomb!
Oh yeah, my breath is explosive too.
Dammit! This is insane!
There weren't even bullets?!
Karoo! You okay?!
Hey! You awake yet?!
Y-Yeah.
I'm awake! Thanks!
He attacked his friend
on purpose to burn his vest
and destroy the trap!
I've had enough of that paint!
I won't let you kill anyone else!
Now I'm pissed off!
Something's not right.
Definitely not right.
It's been too long,
and everyone's still gone.
Something must've happened to
Nami-san, Vivi-chan, and the rest.
If so, now's not the time to be
cooking up this lizard.
Nami-san ! Vivi-chwan !
Hey! You out there?! I love you!
What's this?
Who cares if you're pissed off?
Just look at your friends now!
What's your point?! They're still alive!
You sure 'bout that?
When Miss Golden Week
finishes painting them,
they'll be exceptional wax figures!
You're too late, Straw Hat!
That's correct!
Your time is up, and now you
will taste the bitterness of despair!
Deploy!
Candle...
Champion!
What's that?
They say he took down someone
worth 42 million belly with that thing.
It's Mr. 3's artistic masterpiece!
Come, Miss Golden Week!
Paint me using your artistry.
Then can I relax?
Yes, of course! I'd actually
prefer you stay out of this!
Like this, I am invincible!
The wax armor encasing me is
hard as steel, yet so flexible!
My form now...
has no weak point!
S-So cool!
This is no time to be admiring him! Fight!
All right!
Gum-Gum...
Paint job complete!
Now, then!
Pistol!
Champ Fight: Field Combine!
Gum-Gum...
Stamp!
It's no use!
Not good! Luffy's attacks
won't work on something so solid!
Damn! The wax mist!
Wax?
Yeah! Why didn't I see it sooner?!
Just the fact that it can mist
means it can melt!
Luffy! Fire melts this guy's wax!
No matter how hard it is,
wax is still wax!
Zoro, Master Brogy, and all the
others hardened only moments ago!
We can save them!
What?! For real?!
Yeah. For real.
Don't just admit it like that!
Okay, so you've realized the truth,
but you're out of time
and out of luck!
I'd say there's at most 30 more seconds!
After that, their hearts
will have stopped completely!
Darkness now closes in on them,
their bodies wracked with pain,
as they experience
the terror of dying!
I don't need 30 seconds!
I'll save them now!
Lethal Fire–
Breeze Breath Bomb!
Usopp!
Didn't you hear the man say
your luck's run out?
Dammit! There's no time!
Just give up!
Listen. Take this rope.
Oh? This looks like fun!
Whatcha planning?
Can I join in, too?
Karoo. Run.
Run!
Just keep running around
all the candles!
It's pointless! Give up!
'Scuse me.
Crescendo Stone!
Let's see how many kilograms it takes till you break!
10 kilograms!
100 kilograms!
200 kilograms!
300 kilograms!
Damn nimble bird!
Give it up! Give it up!
They've already become
my masterful works of art!
I don't think so!
I won't lose them
to a weirdo like you!
If fire can melt them,
then I'll use this fire!
Don't pull! Stop!
Luffy! That small flame
won't work fast enough!
Light Karoo's rope on fire!
The bird's rope?!
It's a special rope...
soaked in oil!
Okay! Everyone! Wake up!
Hey! Wait! Stop!
Things're gonna heat up,
but bear with it.
Stop!
Yeow! Hot! Hot!
That fire's huge!
Are they gonna be okay?!
You've done it now, Straw Hat!
How dare you lay waste
to my candle service set!
You'll rue the day!
Get back here, you jerks!
Dammit! Take us seriously!
Now you guys've done it!
Playtime is over!
I'm gonna shatter your neck...
into itty bitty fragments!
Lethal 10,000 Kilo Guillotine!
Was using that much heat
really necessary?
Complaining already? Show a little gratitude toward your savior!
You're right. Thanks!
This doesn't seem real! We're alive!
The wax melted? What a pain!
We can't afford to blow
another mission!
Mr. 5!
Lethal Exploding Star!
Are you stupid?!
I'm a human bomb! You've seen
that explosives don't work on me!
You took the bait!
Too bad for you! I'm a liar, you see!
That wasn't an exploding star!
It was a special tabasco star!
Spicy!
I already checked its
effectiveness the hard way!
You lousy pirates!
I'll blow you away
with a full-body explosion!
There won't even be bone fragments left!
No! Stop!
No! I'm sorry! It won't happen again!
Flaming Oni...
Giri!
Fiery blades. Not too shabby.
Zoro!
Yo. Good to see you're alive.
Yeah.
Master.
That leaves two foes remaining.
Bird!
Don't let them get away!
Real men don't spoil people's fights!
Nice of you to drop by!
Welcome to my Wax-Wax Mansion!
What is this?!
Well, then.
Can you pick out the real me?
It seems you picked a fight
with the wrong people!
Our team's intellect is unparalleled
in all of Baroque Works!
A brute like you, acting on instinct
alone, has no hope against us!
I am Mr. 3.
I flawlessly execute any mission
to which I am assigned.
Now, then! Step inside!
But the moment you turn your back
to me, you'll get a dagger...
right through the heart.
Gum-Gum...
Stamp!
How... did you know...
I was here?
Instinct.
Indeed, afternoons are best spent with a cup of Earl Grey.
Hey, wait a minute!
This is no time for me to be
sipping tea all fancy like!
Nami-san and the others might be
waiting for me to save them!
All the same, why's a relaxing place like this in the middle of a jungle?
What's that?
Oh.
It's a transponder snail.
Heya, you've reached
Restaurant de Merde.
Making a reservation?
Quit fooling around, you idiot.
Aren't you a bit late
with your report?
Oh? Report?
And who might I be talking to?
It's me.
Mr. 0.