Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Some things cannot be stopped.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
The tides of time,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
Translation
FUNimation
Gaijin
Raws
Neo-Raws
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Straight Ahead!!
Whoa! Look!
Behind him!
A rainbow! There's a rainbow!
Even his tears are gigantic!
It's practically a waterfall!
I understand how you feel,
Master Brogy!
Dorry! How are you–
It seems I blacked out.
Mr. 0?
Wasn't Mr. 0 the name
of the enemy boss Vivi-chan mentioned?
Which means the guy on the other
end of this transponder snail...
is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
I issued your orders several days ago.
What's taking so long?
It says "Mr. 3." So he's the owner
of this transponder snail?
I think I got it figured out now.
This is an enemy hideout,
and a guy named Mr. 3 came
to the island to take Vivi-chan's life.
Dammit! {This was no time
for me to be hunting!}I wasted
all this time on hunting!
I hope everyone's okay!
Why the silent treatment?
I asked you a question.
Have you eliminated Princess Vivi
and the Straw Hats?!
Yeah, mission complete!
I got rid of everyone
who knew your secret.
So there's no need
to go after 'em anymore.
I see. Well done.
As we speak, the Unluckies
are headed your way
to confirm your mission is complete
and to deliver a certain package.
Unluckies? Package?
An eternal pose that points
to the Kingdom of Arabasta.
You and Miss Golden Week will head
to Arabasta. The time has come.
{We're about to begin our
most important operation.}We will commence with our
most critical operation to date.
{Details will come after you reach
Arabasta. Wait for my orders.}Once in Arabasta,
await further orders.
Who the hell are these guys?!
Hey. What's the problem?
N-No worries, it's noth–
What the hell?!
You wanna kill me?!
Bring it on, you damn monkey!
I'm tellin' you...
to cut that out,
you overgrown chicken!
What was that?! What happened?!
{Oh, uhh, no! It ain't-
I mean, it's nothing!}Oh, i-it's nothing. Nothing at all.
That damn Straw Hat was still alive.
It's okay, though. I finished him off.
No need to worry.
Still alive?
{You just said your mission
was complete...}You told me
your mission was complete.
Didn't you?
Well, yes.
I thought it was, y'know?
{But he was much tougher
than you'd believe...}But he was a lot tougher
than he let on.
{In other words...
the report you gave me was a lie.}In other words, what you
gave me was a false report.
{Umm, well... I suppose so,
when you put it that way...}Um, well... I suppose
that's what it sounds like.
{But I've gotten rid
of him for sure now.}But! I stamped him out
for good now.
{So there's no need to send
any more after 'em. Okay?}So, no need to send anyone else. Okay?
Enough.
{Just head straight
to Arabasta from there now!}You're to head straight
to Arabasta immediately!
{It's probably...
because of the weapons...}It must've been...
due to the weapons.
The weapons?! Of course!
{Not even Elbaf weapons
could keep up with two giants}These weapons,
though forged in Elbaf,
{fighting to the death
for 100 years straight!}are completely worn out after a
century-long duel between giants!
Of all the crazy luck.
What a miracle!
Hey, Brogy! Don't clutch me!
It upsets my wounds!
{I'm so glad you're alive,
friend of mine!}I'm overjoyed you're alive, old friend!
What miracle?
This was bound to happen.
{The fact those weapons
are still intact after 100 years}What's crazy is those
weapons remain intact
{of constant bashing
and clanging is even crazier.}despite the punishment they took.
Not to mention their owners.
This is truly a glorious day!
I give thanks to the gods of Elbaf!
Oh, Brogy?
{Was chopping me down and knocking
me out that happy for you?}So cutting me down and taking
me out was a joyous occasion?
You dimwit!
You have the wrong idea!
Ouch! Watch out for my wounds!
You want some more?!
Yeah! I'll drop you again!
Cool! Cool! Cool!
Why are you guys at it again?!
{And no further radio
contact from now on.}And you will practice
strict radio silence.
{We don't want the Navy
catching whiff of us.}It'll keep the Navy
from catching on to us.
{All further orders will be sent
via letter, as usual.}From here on, you'll only receive
written orders, as in the past.
That is all. Good luck, Mr. 3.
Miss All-Sunday.
Yes?
Have Mr. 2 stop by Little Garden.
{Eliminate Mr. 3 on his direct course
to Arabasta from Little Garden.}On his way to Arabasta from Little Garden, Mr. 3 needs to disappear.
{That's quite aggressive, sir.
Mr. 0, Crocodile.}How cold-blooded of you, Sir "Mr. 0" Crocodile.
We have enough manpower as it is.
Is there a problem here?
{No, I'll do as you wish.
I'll make arrangements at once.}Hm? No problem. I'll make it happen.
Well, he hung up. So, let's see...
Just who were these guys?
What's this?
Captain Smoker. Captain Smoker!
{I've just intercepted
an intriguing signal!}We intercepted
an intriguing transmission.
What?
What an incredible full temper!
The great wazamono blade, Kashu!
Tashigi! Hey! Tashigi!
Only on the Grand Line can you
find a named blade so readily!
Tashigi! Hey!
Are you deaf, you sword freak?!
Y-Yes, sir! What is it,
Captain Smoker?! The coffee is–
Just get over here and listen to this!
{That's a black transponder snail,
a listening device!}That's a black wiretapper snail!
Black Wiretapper Snail
Listen close. We just picked up
this conversation between two men.
Ready, Chief?
Let's play it back.
Y-Yes. If you would.
...'s me. Mr. 0.
Princess Vivi and the Straw Ha...
Straw Ha...? The Straw Hat Pirates!
Yeah, mission complete!
{further orders...
via letter, as usual...}{Rewritten line of origin: From here on, you'll only receive
written orders, as in the past.\i1}... you'll only... written
orders, as in the past.
That is all. Good luck...
The rest is indecipherable.
The signal was faint, but we made out
four keywords in this conversation:
Princess Vivi; Straw Hat;
written orders; and Mr. 0.
Mr. 0? Could that be a code name?!
Perhaps he's connected
to that suspicious swordsman
we arrested back in Renaisse.
Mr.11
(Frontier Agent)
Baroque Works
Mr.11
(Frontier Agent)
Baroque Works
Connected to him... Mr. 11?
Yeah, seems like it.
A criminal organization
with numerical code names
that sends {orders via letter to
get tasks done}written orders. Sound about right?
Mr. 0? Criminal organization?
Beats me.
I've no time for riddles.
{Then what was that letter with orders
that we found in your pocket?}Then why did we find a note
with orders on it in your pocket?
I thought I burned that letter!
Th-That was... well...
{Oh? But there wasn't
anything in your pocket.}Strange. We didn't find
anything in your pocket.
Princess Vivi...
{That's the name of the princess
of Arabasta, as I recall.}If memory serves,
she's the princess of Arabasta.
However, she's currently missing.
{Isn't Arabasta
in the middle of coup, too?}Arabasta's in the
midst of a coup, right?
Could this mysterious
criminal organization
and the Straw Hats
somehow be involved?
Who knows?
But this is the only clue leading us
to the Straw Hats right now.
So, we're going to–
Yeah. Contact headquarters
and requisition an eternal pose!
Yes, sir!
We're going to Arabasta,
the Kingdom of Sand!
We had completely forgotten
about the bounties on our heads!
{But I was the reason they came
to this island in the first place...}If it weren't for me, they would have
never ventured to this island.
Ow!
Don't give me that.
Yeah, Vivi! Why're you
so down in the dumps?
Rice cracker?
Wait, where'd those come from?
All right! {For now, let's have
a rice cracker party!}Time for a
rice cracker party!
Rice crackers aren't very exciting.
{Really? We can even
make toasts with them!}So then, raise a toast with 'em.
See? Does anyone blame you?
Cheers!
Look! What a waste! Honestly!
{Geez! You can't just
waste food like that!}Seriously, you'll just
ruin the food like that.
What're you doing?! Give it here!
Who said you could have mine?!
– Give it {}back! It's mine!
– Says who?!
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just a bug.
{Still, waiting a year for the log to point to the next island is pretty serious stuff...}Still, it's no joke that the log takes one year to register the next island.
{Yeah! It's definitely
no laughing matter!}You're right! It's no laughing matter!
You saved us. We would like
to repay you in some way.
Oh, in that case,
you old guys should fix our log!
{I'm afraid logs are the only
thing we can't help you with...}I'm afraid even we aren't capable
of helping with your log pose.
Nami-san ! Vivi-chwan !
And the rest of you bums!
Hey! Sanji!
You're all safe! Thank goodness!
{That jerk suddenly shows up only
after we needed help!}Of course that flake shows up
only after we need him.
What in the hell?! Are you Mr. 3?!
Hey! How do you know about Mr. 3?
Nami-san !
How risqué you are!
Wanna risk my fist?
Allow me, Nami-san.
You'll catch cold dressed like that.
Please, wear this.
Thanks.
All that aside, I just finished talking
with Mr. 0 via transponder snail.
You talked to the boss?!
Yeah. I found this weird hideout
in the jungle, you see.
He seemed to think I was Mr. 3,
so I told him I eliminated everyone.
So that means he thinks we're dead?!
{So we're finally free
of people chasing us,}Even if we've shaken those chasing us,
we still can't go anywhere!
Can't go anywhere? Do we still
have business on this island?
{Just after I managed
to get a hold of this, too...}I mean, I just got
a hold of this, too.
Uh? What?
It's an eternal pose to Arabasta!
– Hooray!
– Now we can set sail!
Hooray! Way to go, Sanji-kun !
Thank you, Sanji-san !
I'd almost lost hope!
No, no! It was my pleasure!
I'm glad I could make you so happy!
All right, everyone!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
Oh no, Luffy!
{We only have three left!
We can't have a rice cracker party!}With only three left,
we can't have a party!
What?!
All of that can be put on hold!
Let's go, Captain! {We don't have
time to be lounging around!}We can't waste a single second!
Oh, yeah! Hey, you.
You haven't forgotten
our hunting contest, I hope!
Regarding that, I'm easily the winner.
I caught a rhino this big !
A rhino? Is something
like that edible?
Of course!
A hunting contest?
{Those words sound
familiar somehow.}Somehow, this all sounds
somehow familiar.
Yes.
All right, round old guy
and giant old guy!
We're outta here!
{Oh, I see. Well, you do seem
to be in a hurry.}Oh? Well, you do seem anxious to leave.
{That's too bad,
but we won't stop you.}Sad, but don't let us stop you.
Best of wishes for your country.
Yes! Thank you!
See ya! Don't die anymore!
Master! I will visit Elbaf someday!
You'll see. Mine's way bigger than yours.
You wish!
I'm gonna be
a brave warrior of the sea!
Our friends are setting sail.
Yes. We can't just sit here.
There's a monster in the western sea.
Dorry, how are your wounds?
These? I'll live.
{This axe and that sword
are just about done with.}My axe and your sword
are about finished.
Any regrets?
{I do. This axe fought alongside me
for over 100 years.}Indeed. This axe has been my partner in battle for well over a century.
However, if it's to help them out,
then it's worth it!
That settles it.
See?! Mine's a lot
bigger than yours!
Look closer! My lizard's enormous!
Are you blind or something?!
My rhino's much more humongous!
It doesn't matter!
They both look delicious!
Mind your own business!
Huh?
– Look! Mine's bigger!
– No, mine is!
{How long are you
gonna keep at that?}And just how long do you two
plan to keep at it?
{We don't need all of it, so cut up
what we do need so we can set sail!}Just cut 'em up and stow
what we can so we can set sail!
Yes, Nami-san !
Hey, Usopp! I'm clearly
the winner, right?!
I don't really care.
Can't you call it a draw?
There are no draws in a challenge!
Move your asses!
Right!
Set sail!
They said going straight will take us
to the western end of the island.
Hey. {Couldn't you have
gotten any more meat on board?}Is this all the meat
we could carry?
{Yeah, right! Don't be stupid! We
can't preserve any more than that.}Use your head!
We can't stow more than this.
Do you wanna sink the ship?!
Look, it's the old guys!
They came to see us off!
Ahead is a great obstacle...
...that prevents people who come
to this island from reaching the next.
You fought desperately
to protect our pride.
{As such, no matter what
manner of enemy there may be...}Therefore, no matter the enemy
that may rear its head...
{we will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!}...we will keep it from
trampling your pride, friends!
{Have faith in us,
and continue straight ahead!}Have faith and keep straight!
{Straight ahead,
no matter what happens!}No matter what happens,
sail straight ahead!
Got it!
What's this about?
Wh-What's the word?
We'll sail straight ahead,
no matter what happens!
We bid you farewell!
Let's meet again someday.
Without fail.
Look! Ahead!
There you are, Island Gorger!
{You will open the path,
in the name of Elbaf!}You will make way,
lest the pride of Elbaf fails us.
Wha...?
Something's appeared!
What is this guy? A goldfish?
A g-giant goldfish?!
Wh-Why does that sound familiar?!
Work the rudder! Hurry!
We're gonna get eaten!
Usopp! Hurry!
I... I can't!
Go straight ahead! R-Right, Luffy?!
Yeah! Of course!
{Don't be stupid! This won't be
like what happened with Laboon!}Don't be stupid! Laboon was
one thing, but this is nothing like him!
I know. Don't worry.
Here, have the last rice cracker.
I don't want it! If we don't turn
the ship, we're gonna be–
Just give it up, Nami.
Luffy! We can trust
those guys, I take it?!
Yeah!
Are you crazy?! Are we really
sailing straight into that beast?!
No! No turning back now!
You've really grown, Island Gorger!
You monstrous goldfish!
His size isn't the only surprising thing.
{There's also the size
and length of the dung he produces}This monster eats islands whole
and poops them out in colossal turds.
{I recall a giant piece of dung
named Nihiland.}I recall one such floating
dung heap was named Nihiland.
{And that we landed on it long ago,
thinking it was actual land!}We actually landed on it long ago,
mistaking it for an island!
Today makes me
nostalgic for adventure!
As I watch that crew,
I'm reminded of the old days!
The one thing we've never pierced
is the bloodstained snake!
{Observe, the most powerful giant
spear, as passed down in Elbaf!}Behold! The mighty, legendary spear as taught only to those from Elbaf!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
What's the point?!
We've already been eaten!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Dominion!
We're flying right out of it!
Don't look back!
We're keeping on straight ahead!
It's huge! So huge!
They cut... the very sea itself...
This is the strength of Elbaf warriors!
It's incredible!
Friends!
Now go!
Long ago, there was a group of
ruffians on the sea...
known as the Giant Warrior Pirates.
The two pirate bosses,
Brogy the Red Ogre
and Dorry the Blue Ogre,
stood unrivaled in might.
Since ordinary people could not
stand a chance against them,
they were left mostly unchecked.
But they say that the one
who finally put an end to them
was a mere little girl.
You see what our
bosses caught today?!
{Yeah! It's stuck in my mind!
My excitement won't stop!}Yeah! It's all I can think about!
What a day to be alive!
Each one of 'em bagged
an insanely huge sea king, after all!
Even though we're Elbaf giants,
nobody can take down those jumbo-sized monsters!
Nobody but the bosses, that is!
Right, men?!
– Yeah!
– You got that right!
{Those ones were definitely
the biggest ones...}These ones are
definitely the biggest yet!
Yeah! Bigger than anything
we've ever caught!
So which one was bigger?
– Which...
– ...one?
Yeah! Who won the hunting contest?
Look, Brogy! Mine is slightly bigger!
Keep dreaming! Mine's a whole
three centimeters longer!
– Say what?!
– What?!
Bosses! Please stop!
Incidentally, Brogy. There's
one thing I can't seem to remember.
No, actually, same goes for me.
The central mountain!
No need to dwell on it!
Let's settle this, once and for all!
{Yeah! We can think
things through after that!}You're right! We'll sort things out afterward!