Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
KaitouYahiko
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Parallels
Captain Smoker! Terrible news!
A message from headquarters!{We received a message
from headquarters! - Ohms}
{They've received word that a Monkey D. Luffy and his pirate crew are headed here, to Loguetown! - OG}Monkey D. Luffy and his crew
are headed here, to Loguetown!
He just earned a 30-million-belly
bounty in the East Blue!
{30 million...
That's worthy of congratulation. - OG}A 30-million bounty...
Congratulations are in order.
{He's an incredibly evil villain who even defeated Don Krieg and Arlong the fishman! - OG}{He's an incredibly wicked rogue; he defeated Don Krieg and the fishman Arlong! - Ohms}He's so villainous that he even took out
Don Krieg and the fishman Arlong!
Quiet!
{Damn your shouting.
You made it fall apart. - OG}Your damn shouting
made it all fall apart.
I'm sorry, sir!
It's no good to let
things stress you out.
I think it's best to do things
at your own pace.
Don't you agree?
Y-Yes, sir!
So, what is this about?
Right! It's about a group of pirates!
{Word has it they may
show up in town today, yes! - OG}{It's just been a while since such
a formidable pirate group showed up! - Ohms}It's been reported that they may
show up in town today... Yes!
Why so stressed?
{Have any pirates who've set
foot into this town ever escaped - OG}Has a single pirate been able
to escape this town...
since I took command?
N-No, sir...
Then calm the hell down.
Captain "White Hound" Smoker
Marine Headquarters
You're gonna screw up my pace.
Yes, sir...
{Reporting, sir! We have word that pirates
have appeared at the port! - OG}{Reporting in, sir! We have word that
pirates have appeared at the port! - Ohms}Reporting, sir! We have word that
pirates have arrived at the port!
Please head there immediately!
{It must be Luffy's group!
They've definitely set foot into town! - OG}{It must be Luffy's group!
They've already arrived! - Ohms}It must be Luffy's crew!
They've set foot in town!
Thirty million, huh...? I hope
he at least puts up a fight.
Sir?
Just talking to myself. Forget it.
Don't you wanna look at this?!
"Justice"
Captain! Please give
each unit their orders!
No need.
{But you need to consider
how powerful he is! - OG}But he might end up
being pretty strong!
Never mind that. Where's Tashigi?
Y-Yes. She mentioned
she'd be busy this morning,
but that she'd attend the training drills.
{That dumb girl.
Where the hell'd she go? - OG}That clumsy girl.
Where'd she run off to?
Yay! A triple-scoop ice cream!
{Hold on, now!
You'll drop them if you run! - OG}Slow it down!
You'll drop them if you run!
C-Captain Smoker!
M-My ice cream...
I-I'm very sorry about my daughter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry 'bout that.
My pants ate your ice cream.
Here, buy yourself five scoops.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
Th-Thank you!
Thanks!
{Loot everything there is!
Don't leave a single potato behind! - OG}Loot everything! Don't leave
a single potato behind!
{I, Gally the Crescent-sama, will use these vital food supplies on my way to becoming King of the Pirates! - OG}{I, Gally the Crescent-sama, will need these food supplies to become King of the Pirates!- Ohms}I, future Pirate King Gally the Crescent, will
need these food supplies on my voyage!
Hand it all over thankfully!
Hey.
Who's in charge here?
What do you want?
So you're Monkey D. Luffy?
{I'll test you and see if you're
worthy of setting foot into [/i1]my[/i0] town. - OG}{Let's see if you have what it takes
to survive in my town. - Ohms}I want to test you to see if you're
worthy of setting foot in my town.
What a ripe load of crap!
Get 'im!
Captain Smoker?
Yeah. He's one of the toughest
guys from Marine Headquarters.{Yeah. He was one of the toughest
guys from Marine Headquarters. - Ohms}
This town used to be a hangout
for pirates headed for the Grand Line.{This town used to be a haven
for pirates headed to the Grand Line. - Ohms}
{But ever since he took over,
every single pirate who's come into town - OG}But ever since he took command,
every pirate who's come to town
has wound up behind bars.
His strength is extraordinary.
He's a monster.
They even say he has
devil fruit powers...
Devil fruit powers?!
Incredible, Captain! You captured
Luffy's crew in no time flat!
Are your eyes just for decoration?
This guy obviously isn't Luffy.
What?
{The world'd be ending if this
shabby fly were worth 30 million. - OG}The world would end before
this guy is worth 30 million.
Th-Then, where is Luffy?
He'll show up soon enough
The fun's just getting started.
Huh?
{How did I wind up
at the harbor? Seriously? - Ohms}And now I'm at the harbor.
How did I get here?
Hey!
Is he one of these guys?
I'm not sure. Probably not...
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
Execution platform...?
I got lost on my way to it...
I've never seen you
around here before.
Yeah! I just arrived on this island!
This town sure is huge! It's way
different from Windmill Village!
{Why're you looking
for the execution platform? - Ohms}So why the execution platform?
I wanna see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!{I wanna see the place
where the Pirate King died! - Ohms}
So you don't know where? Well...
Wait. Follow the smoke.
Oh! That way?! Thanks!
This sucks.
{I was trying to get to the execution platform,
but now I'm somewhere else completely. - OG}{I keep trying to get to the execution
platform, but I keep getting lost. - Ohms}I thought I was headed to the execution
platform, but this can't be the place.
Oh, well. I'll get there sooner or later.
Is it this way?
Let's see...
Gold... Roger?
Do you work here, old guy?
It said "Gold Roger"
on the sign outside.
Is that this place's name?
Scram.
This ain't a place for a runt like you.
Besides, we're closing for good today.
You're going under?
{It didn't go under!
I'm shutting it down myself! - OG}We're not going under!
I'm shutting it down myself!
Now get lost!
I was just curious about the name.
I'm a little lost.
I'm trying to get to
the execution platform...
Can you tell me how to get there?
What's that on the table?
A skull?! It's huge!
{This is what became of a guy
once known as Killer Giant. - OG}This is what became of a guy
who folks called Killer Giant.
{A villain who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife. - OG}{A fiend who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife. - Ohms}He's a fiend who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife.
{But Gold Roger sent him to
his grave with just one blow. - OG}{Until Gold Roger finished him
with just one blow. - Ohms}But Gold Roger sent him to
the afterlife with just one blow.
Gold Roger did?!
With lightning-like speed!
This is the wound he received!
The man may have lived horribly,
{but with his dying
breath, he conceded, - Ohms}but with his dying breath, he muttered,
"Roger... My hat's off to you...
{you will always be
honored among pirates." - Ohms}May you be eternally
honored among pirates."
Awesome! That's so cool!
{When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a bit later, - OG}When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a little later,
{I was more happy than I was surprised—I was more excited than I should have been at my age! - OG}{I wasn't surprised, just happy
and excited he was the one to do it. - Ohms}Happiness overcame my surprise,
and my excitement belied my age!
And then, twenty-two years ago today,
Roger died on the execution platform.{22 years ago today, Roger died
on that execution platform. - Ohms}
{Ever since that day, everyone proud of their great strength has tossed their hat into the pirate ring. - OG}{And ever since that day, every cocky upstart has tossed their hat into the pirate ring. - Ohms}And since that day, every cocky upstart
has tossed their hat into the pirate ring.
It was the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era!
But look what's happened!
This town's full of nothing
but cowards and scum now!
{Men crazy enough to challenge that
sea of evil are all but gone now! - OG}Men crazy enough to challenge
that evil sea are all but gone now!
That's why this bar is
closing down for good today.{That's why this bar is
closing for good today. - Ohms}
I'm going to the Grand Line, too!
Huh?!
Gold Roger's so cool...
He's how a pirate should be!
That's why I set out to sea.
I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
get the One Piece,{I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
find the One Piece, - Ohms}
and become King of the Pirates!
Those're some mighty big words!
And in this bar, of all places!
I only said what I meant.
Kiddo!
If there're still patrons like you out there,
maybe I'll hold off on closing this place!{If there're still patrons like you out there, should I hold off on closing this place?! - Ohms}
How should I know if there are?!
{You're right!
There's no way of knowin'! - Ohms}Good point! Of course
you wouldn't know!
{I haven't been in this
good a mood for ages! - Ohms}I haven't been in this good
a mood since back then...!
I'll treat you to a drink!
I don't drink alcohol.
Sure! I have just the thing!
Let's have a toast!
To the eternal King of the Pirates!
Amazing! That's
an elephant bluefin tuna!
That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern ocean.{That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern waters. - Ohms}
I caught it with a pole and line!
A pole and line?!
An elephant bluefin tuna...
Okay, then, haul it away.
– Okay!
H-Hold on a second!
Hm?
How much is it?! Let me buy it!
I bought a lot, a heck of a lot!
Now my preparations to be a brave
warrior of the sea are complete!
All I've got left is...
Oh, yeah! I forgot the most
important thing. Goggles.
{A top-class sniper needs to have top-class goggles! That's just basic! The most basic of all! - OG}{A first-class sniper needs to have first-class goggles! That's a necessity! - Ohms}The best goggles for the best marksman!
Does it get anymore basic than that?!
{Investing every last bit of money
to get the best goggles around - OG}{I gotta spare no expense
on these goggles - Ohms}Sparing no expense on
the best goggles around
is the very essence of
being the best marksman!
Goggles! Goggles!
{This is it! These goggles are perfect!
It's gotta be these! - Ohms}These ones! These goggles!
They're just perfect!
Ma'am!
{You got a good eye!
Them's the latest North Blue model there! - OG}{You got a good eye! Them's the
latest model from the North Blue! - Ohms}You've got a good eye! They're
the latest model from the North Blue!
{I got 'em from an import ship that
leaves the Marines only once a year! - OG}{I got 'em from a Marine import ship
that only visits once a year! - Ohms}I got 'em from an import vessel that
only leaves the Marines once a year!
What's the matter? No money?
I only deal in cash,
so what's it gonna be?
{N-No, it's... Oh! Right!
Backpack, backpack... - OG}N-No, it's... Oh!
Right! My backpack...
I'll take these goggles, please!
My! What a cute little girl!
Yes, yes, yes, yes! You're in luck!
This is the only pair in town!
Hold it right there!
I saw them first, so–
Huh?
Hm?
Butt out, old man!
O...?!
Old man?
Stop! Stop right there, you!
{Listen! Let's set the record straight!
I am [/i1]not[/i0] an old man! - OG}Listen! First things first!
There's no way I'm an old man!
I'm more like a big brother. Got it?
Huh?! What're you
talking about, old man?!
Dammit, you said it again!
{Gimme those goggles back!
I found 'em first! - OG}Just gimme those goggles already!
Huh?!
You got a problem?! Huh?!
Keep up yer damn complainin'
and I'll call the Marines!
M-Marines?
Yep! I'm friends with
a Marine captain in this town!{Yep! The town's Marine captain
is like a family friend. - Ohms}
The old smoky man!
Wh-Who is this girl?
Don't you know who I am?!
{I'm Great Captain Usopp!
I destroyed Arlong's fishman pirate group! - OG}I'm the great Captain Usopp!
I destroyed Arlong's Fishman Pirates!
{It was truly a battle to the death! There I was, surrounded by 200, no, 300 fishmen! - Ohms}It was a dire battle! The fishmen had
me surrounded 200—no, 300 to 1!
All alone, I punched, threw, stomped,
kicked, and tore them all up!{I beat them all mercilessly
single-handed! - Ohms}
Thanks to that, I now have
a 30-million-belly bounty on my head!
I see. 30 million...
Yep! That's right!
Papa!
Papa?! Now you're calling me Pa–
Ah!
Here's a present for you, Papa!
Happy birthday!
Oh, Carol...
{What a nice, angelic girl you are!
I love you, Carol-chan! - OG}What a considerate little angel
you are! I love you, Carol!
And I love you, Papa!
Wh-What's with this family?
{But guess what! That old man there
is trying to swipe your present! - OG}{But this old man was being mean
and trying to swipe your present! - Ohms}But listen! That asshole old man there
is trying to swipe your present!
Now, now! "Asshole" is a bad word.{Z - "swipe" doesn't translate to English as being rude or bad-mannered, just a bit slangy. I think we can take some liberties here.}
You should mind your manners, okay?
{Are you the gentleman who's
picking on my precious Carol? - Ohms}You wouldn't happen to be picking on
my adorable Carol, would you?
P-P-Picking on...?
That's not all!
Huh?
You have a bounty of
30 million belly, I hear?
Let's see here...
Are those the new wanted posters?
Yeah, I got 'em from
the outpost just now...{Yeah, I just picked 'em up
from the Marine outpost... - Ohms}
Six hundred thousand...
One million three hundred thousand...
Seven hundred thousand... Huh?
Thirty million... Straw Hat Luffy?
For a starting bounty to be this high...
Hold it, boy.
Y-Y-Yes?!
No, you see, sir,
I'm obviously not the person
on that poster! I was just lying!
{My funny plan to trick people was
a great success! Ha ha! Well, bye! - OG}{It was just a silly
little prank! Well, bye! - Ohms}My silly little prank was
a great success! Well, bye!
That's you, isn't it?
Th-Th-That's right!
It sure is! That's me, all right!
But know this!
{Just you try and lay a hand on me!
My captain Luffy won't sit by quietly! - OG}If you lay a hand on me,
my captain Luffy won't stand for it!
He's an evil, cold-blooded,
devilish man!{He's an awful,
cold-blooded, devilish man! - Ohms}
{No one's ever defied him
and lived to tell about it! - OG}{No one's ever crossed him
and lived to tell the story! - Ohms}No one's ever crossed him
and lived to tell the tale.
{You got a kid, right?
You should really value your life... - OG}{You got a kid, right?
You shouldn't be risking your life... - Ohms}You've got a kid, so you really
ought to value your life more...
I see. It doesn't sound worth it.
{Yes, given that this Luffy fellow is worth 30 million belly, he's clearly no ordinary man. - OG}{It's clear that this Luffy fellow is no ordinary man, since he has a bounty of 30 million. - Ohms}A bounty of 30 million makes it clear
this Luffy fellow is no ordinary man.
Papa! You're obviously way stronger!
{You're the strongest
in the whole wide world! - Ohms}You're the strongest in the world!
Carol, it's all right.
{All that matters is that I make
enough money to live happily with you. - OG}As long as I earn enough
to provide for us, I'm happy.
You're far more important to me
than being the world's greatest!{I have nothing to prove and your
safety is far more important to me. - Ohms}
Papa...
{The guy's backing off
'cause of what I said! - Ohms}He's actually backing off
after I said all that!
Alright! In that case...!
So you realize how terrifying I am?!
Take my advice! Just hand
those goggles over to me!{Take my advice! Just hand
the goggles over and move on! - Ohms}
Huh?!
Don't worry! I'll pay for 'em!
So just give 'em here!
{Why're you saying that right after
he's just about to let you go– - OG}Why the hell would you say that
when he was about to let you–
Papa?
Then let's do this.
I assume you have no problem
with us settling this in a fair fight?{I assume you have no problem
with us settling this like gentlemen? - Ohms}
A fight...?
Here!
{Y-You're not talking
about a duel, are you? - Ohms}A fight...?! Y-You're not
talking about a duel, are you?!
If you win, the goggles are yours.
One, two, three, four,
five, six... thirty pistols?!
D-Don't tell me you're...
Daddy the Father?!
A duel!
There's gonna be a duel!
{Daddy the Father's
gonna face somebody! - Ohms}It's a duel with Daddy the Father!
Did he say Daddy the Father?
Daddy the Father is the greatest
gunslinger bounty hunter!{Daddy the Father is like the greatest
gunslinging bounty hunter out there! - Ohms}
Everyone in the East Blue knows that!
{I wonder what the idiot who'd
challenge him to a duel looks like! - OG}So what kind of idiot would
challenge him to a duel?!
Oh, that kind.
Good luck, long nose!
{Don't worry if he beats ya!
We already got a place dug for ya! - OG}Don't worry if he beats you!
We've already dug your grave!
H-How did things turn out like this?
What's wrong with me?!
The rules are simple. We both
walk ten paces and then shoot.{The rules are simple. We both walk
ten paces and then turn and shoot. - Ohms}
Y-Yeah...
What are you doing?!
Nami!
{Facing Daddy the Father
in a duel... Are you suicidal?! - Ohms}Facing Daddy the Father in
a duel... Have you lost your mind?!
Sh-Shut up! It just kinda happened,
so shut up and watch!
You get one shot. Are you ready?
Yeah.
Yeah...
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
This is bad... Really bad...
There's no way I can possibly
beat Daddy the Father...
Six!
Am I going to die here?!
This can't be happening!
Seven!
I just started my adventure!
I haven't even gained any courage
or manliness or anything yet!
Eight!
Later!
Papa!
You're amazing, Papa! You're so cool!
Man, how pathetic.
What a lame duel.
I thought he'd have more guts
than that. What a disappointment.
{What's with you?!
Tryin' to cheat like that! - OG}Who do you think
you are, trying to cheat?!
{You coward! Weakling!
Can't you even fight honestly?! - OG}You cowardly weakling!
Can't you at least fight honestly?!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I'm just a lowly, pathetic man!
{Taking the life of someone like
me wouldn't gain you anything! - OG}You'd get nothing out of
killing someone like me!
Right?! Right?!
Can't you just let me go?
W-Wait!
Nami!
{Y-Yeah! If it's money you want,
she has tons of it! - OG}R-Right! If it's money
you want, she has plenty!
Just please don't shoot me!
Please spare my life!
Hold on, now!
Now you're groveling behind a woman?
Anyway–
No! Forget what I just said!
{She's just an innocent bystander
who has nothing to do with this! - OG}She's an innocent bystander!
{Even if I wind up getting shot,
I can't let her get caught up in this! - OG}I can't drag her into this,
even if it means I get shot!
Usopp...
Please! I beg you!
"Usopp..."
Kid, your name is Usopp?
Yeah.
It couldn't be...
Do you know a man named
Yasopp of the Red Hair Pirates?
Yasopp? That's my old man's name.
Y-You've met my dad before?!
Then you are his son...
Papa?
{I've never once told a soul
what happened on that day... - OG}I've never once told a soul
what happened on that day,
but I'll make an exception.
It happened at a hot,
dry port town, much like this one.{It happened in a sweltering
port town like this. - Ohms}
Let's do it, Ensign Masterson!
We each get one shot!
One! Two! Three!
Kill me! Now that I've lost a duel,
I have no reason to live...
What are you doing?
Your daughter?
Give it back...
{A Marine ensign of all people,
carefully treasuring something like this... - OG}{To think a Marine like you would
treasure something like this... - Ohms}An ensign in the Marines, carefully
treasuring something like this...
You must really spoil her.
Don't lecture me, you filthy pirate!
Fine by me!
You were great, Yasopp!
It was nothing.
{The pain of this wound just goes
to show how inexperienced I am. - OG}{The wound I took shows
I have a lot to learn. - Ohms}This wound really shows
off my inexperience.
But you took on Daddy Masterson!
You won because you're you!{You won because you're
already awesome! - Ohms}
Yeah, we never would've
stood a chance...
Thanks, Boss!
{I appreciate your watching
the duel without saying anything! - OG}I appreciate you watching
the duel without saying a thing.
That's the stuff!
You want some, Ensign?
Family, huh?
Family's not so bad.
But I'm no good at it.{Havin' a family's not so bad.
But I'm no good at it. - Ohms}
Huh?
{I got a son of my own.
His name's Usopp. - OG}I've got a son of my own.
His name's Usopp.
Haven't seen him in years now.
I hit the high seas around
the time he was a toddler.
Why? Do you not love your son?
It wasn't about that.
It was about the flag...
I heard the call of the Jolly Roger.
You tell 'im, Yasopp!
Now, then...
There's nothing I can do for my son.
{We don't need another hopeless
father like me out there! - Ohms}Even one hopeless parent
like me is one too many.
Always stay by your daughter's side.
You can't let her feel lonely.
Though I'm in no position to talk!
{I lost our duel!
Yasopp! Finish me off! - OG}I lost our duel! Yasopp! Finish me!
Don't give me your lousy pity!
Forget it!
{You Marines might hang us by
our necks right after you catch us, - OG}{You Marines might have to
hang your enemies, - Ohms}You Marines might hang us by
our necks the moment you catch us,
{but we pirates are free to let you
live or die however we please! - OG}but we pirates are free to kill
or spare who we please!
So long!
{Papa! You lost to a pirate, Papa?!
He spared your life?! - OG}{Papa! You didn't really
lose to a pirate, did you?! - Ohms}Papa! You lost to a pirate,
and he spared your life?!
But that's amazing!
Your dad must be really skilled!
Usopp?
Would you normally...?
Would you normally tell
some pathetic boy like me...{Would you normally
tell someone like me... - Ohms}
{a story about you shamelessly
having your life spared?! - OG}a shameless story about
having your life spared?!
You told me that to give me courage!
{Most people would be vain
and keep a story like that secret! - OG}Most people would be too
ashamed to tell a story like that,
{You told me even though you
knew it'd make you less cool! - OG}but you told me even though
you'd become way less cool!
{Regardless of how brave my
old man might be! Right?! - OG}{Just so I would know
what my old man is like! - Ohms}Regardless of how brave you
showed my old man to be. Right?!
No weakling or coward
could do what you just did!
Carol! Your dad is
the bravest man alive!
You can find strong guys anywhere!
But I've never seen a man as
strong and kind as your dad before!{But the ones who'd risk their
honor for others are rare! - Ohms}
{I... I can't give in, either! I gotta be
brave, or I'll shame your dad! - OG}I... I can't throw in the towel! I gotta
be brave, or I'll shame your dad!
Daddy! Give me a chance!
Face me in another life-or-death duel!
I won't cheat this time!
All right. This will be
our real showdown.
Choose the weapon you're
most comfortable with.
Good. Now, then. Let's see...
Try and hit that weather vane.
That weather vane? Over there?!
Miss it, and...
Y-Yeah! You can shoot
me right through the heart!
Usopp!
My life is on the
line for real this time!
There's...
There's no way he can shoot
that far with that thing...{There's no way he can
hit it with that thing. - Ohms}
You missed!
No, Papa! Don't shoot him! Papa!
I can't shoot him. Usopp shot
right through its crown!{I can't shoot him 'cause he
shot right through its crown! - Ohms}
H-He really did!
Right through the crown!
Usopp!
You're an excellent shot.
I'd expect no less of Yasopp's son.
Never forget that bravery.{If you hold onto the bravery
you just showed, - Ohms}
{you'll be just like your
old man someday! - Ohms}You'll be just like your
old man someday!
Go to the Grand Line.
I'm certain Yasopp is there.
Daddy...
You're pretty good, old man!
Aren't these...?
It's okay! See ya!
Papa!
Carol, you should know better.
It's bad manners to say, "See ya!"
Right! Sorry, Papa!
{I'm going to grow up to be a nice
lady worthy of being your daughter! - OG}I'm going to grow up to be a proper
lady worthy of being your daughter!
So will you forgive me?
{You're already worthy
the way you are! - Ohms}You're already about as
proper as they come!
{Well, I'm still going to be
an even nicer lady! - Ohms}I'll be even more proper!
{Even when people say he's a
disgrace behind his back now, - OG}Even if people consider him a disgrace,
{he's fought all this time
to protect the one he loves. - OG}{he'll continue to protect
the one he loves. - Ohms}he's only ever fought to
protect the one he loves.
I'm going to be
a brave man like Daddy!
I'm gonna become a real warrior
and stand before my dad someday!{Someday I'll be a great warrior
and stand before my dad proudly! - Ohms}
I know it!
You?!
That's quite the warm weclome...
and I'm a regular, too.
I'm not the one you
should be angry with.
I only come here as a loyal customer.
It's the pirates' fault that
they're all cowards these days.{It's not my fault that the pirates
around here are cowards now. - Ohms}{Blame the pirates for all
the cowards these days. - Z}{Z - is it the pirates who are cowards (afraid of Smoker?) or is it that the pirates have made the regulars afraid to come to the bar?}
You had a customer? That's rare.
I'd like some rum.
There's no booze here for you!
Don't be so cold-hearted.
Today's a special day.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's the stuff...
I can still see it like it was yesterday...
How Roger looked at the very end...
It was a humid afternoon,
just like today...
{His hands were shackled as he was led down the main street toward the town square, - OG}Hands shackled, he was led down
the main street toward the plaza
where the execution platform stood.
{Yet, he walked like
a triumphant general. - OG}{Yet, he waltzed along like
it was a victory parade. - Ohms}Yet, he marched down it
like a triumphant general.
Wealth, fame, power...
{Gold Roger had attained everything
the world has to offer... - OG}Gold Roger obtained everything
the world had to offer.
Even though he was
walking toward death,
he was the embodiment
of a pride-filled king...
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Do you have any last words?!
{Take this off for me.
It's itchy beyond belief. - OG}{Mind taking these off?
They're beginning to chafe. - Ohms}Do you mind removing these?
They itch like you wouldn't believe.
I can't do that!
You think I would run?
Guess I'm on my own.
All right, let's get this over with.
Hey, Pirate King!
Where did you hide
all the treasure you found?!
Is it in the Grand Line?!
{You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure! - OG}{You had it, right?!
That legendary treasure! - Ohms}You found it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
Shut up, you!
That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
Who said you could speak?!
It's yours, if you can find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
Execute!
That's how it all began...
Hey!
A new wanted poster!
Put it up somewhere noticeable!{Hey, here's a new wanted poster!
Put it where people can see it! - Ohms}
{C-Captain Smoker!
Sorry for the rudeness, sir! - OG}C-Captain Smoker!
Pardon the intrusion, sir!
U-Umm...
That straw hat...
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
There it is...
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died...
The place where it all began...