Guys! I see an island!
Hmm...
Looks like it's an uninhabited island.
Ready the anchor! We'll land on the island!
Well then, go find some foodstuffs.
Yeah!
Listen. No rats or frogs, okay?
How self-centered you are. Once it's in your stomach, it's all the same.
Hey, Chopper. Were you able to find any medicinal herbs?
Yep. I've collected most of them, but there may be even rarer ones on this island.
More importantly, something's been bugging me for a while.
I wonder what this weird groove is that runs down this path...
Come to think of it, yeah, I wonder what it is.
It looks as if a bicycle passed by.
Hey, hey. This is an uninhabited island, right?
This can't be a trace of a bicycle when there's no one here.
That's true.
Hey, we're almost through the jungle!
We're suddenly out in a large open space.
Ahh!
What's with Chopper?
He's headed to that rock. Is there something there?
Ahh!
That darn Chopper!
He must be trying to have that huge mushroom all to himself!
Hold it!
What's the matter, Chopper?!
Looks like something happened. Let's go!
Ow, ow, ow... Hm?
Havy HQ Admiral
Aokiji
Whoa! What the heck is this?!
Ahh... Hmm?
A raccoon dog?
I'm a reindeer! See? I've got antlers!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Who the heck is this?!
What happened?!
What's going on, Luffy?!
What's with you guys?
What's with you?!
Wh-Who's that huge guy?
Who's that guy?!
Robin!
What's wrong, Robin-chan?!
Wh... Why are you frozen?
Robin...
Oh-ho-ho?
Now, now. Don't be so bloodthirsty, guys.
It's not like I'm here on orders.
Since it's a nice day, I took a stroll here.
Orders?! From what organization?!
Oh, my, my, you've turned into a good-looking woman...
Nico Robin.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Translation
FUNimation
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Soundtracking
Halee
Infoboxes/Title Card
BernieCrane
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Editing
Feeso
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Quality Checking
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
Timing
Datenshi
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Navy HQ Admiral Aokiji
To think that he got Robin this shaken up...
Who is he?
He's a marine.
Navy Headquarters Admiral... Aokiji.
Admiral?!
A... Admiral? He's that high up?
There're only three officers in the Navy who hold the position of Admiral.
Akainu...
Aokiji...
Kizaru...
The only one above them is Fleet Admiral Sengoku, who reigns as the top official in the Navy.
That man is one of the three men called the World Government's ultimate powerhouses.
Wh-Why is someone like that here?!
Why don't you go deal with big-time pirates with several-hundred-million-Berry bounties?!
G... Go someplace else!
Hm?
Oh, my, my...
Here's another sexy lady with super big bazongas! Are you free tonight?
What's the big idea, you tall, lanky jerk?!
Pay attention, you jerk!
Hold on a sec, you guys, geez...
Did you hear what I said?
I said I just took a stroll, didn't I?
Don't get so worked up.
To start with, you guys are... whatchamacallit... you know...
"Wh-Whatchamacallit"?
Err...
I forgot. Oh, well.
You don't make much sense!
What the heck's with this guy?!
Hey, Robin, aren't you mistaking him for someone else?
There's no way someone like him is a Navy Admiral!
Hey, hey... Don't judge others by their appearance.
My motto as a marine is "lazy justice."
That totally matches your appearance!
In any case, well...
Oh, excuse me for a sec...
Standing made me tired. Umph.
Then why were you sleeping standing up?
Anyway, to make a long story short,
I have no intention of capturing you guys, so don't worry.
I came to check the whereabouts of Nico Robin, who disappeared after the Alabasta incident, that's all.
Just as I thought, she's been with you guys.
This guy sure is apathetic, isn't he?
His audacity shows he's a leader, in a manner of speaking.
I'm going to at least report this to Headquarters, though.
With another wanted person, the total bounty for you guys has now changed.
100 million... plus 60 million... plus 79 million equals...
I don't know exactly, but I'm sure it's not too shabby.
Why don't you calculate it?
Rubber!
Hold on a sec! Hold on, Luffy!
Stop it! Stop it!
Let me go! What're you guys doing?!
What's the point in us picking a fight?!
He's one of the strongest marines!
So what?! Then are you saying we're gonna hand over Robin without a fight?!
You jerk!
Well, you guys... I'm saying I'm not gonna do anything, aren't I?
I'm gonna beat him up!
Stop it, Luffy!
Like I said several times already, I took a stroll.
Oh, it was a stroll? Then don't go passing a place like this! Leave!
You don't make sense.
Luffy kinda has the upper hand here.
S-So you're a marine... I wish you had told us sooner.
Who are these people?
Hey, get hold of yourselves.
Then this isn't an uninhabited island?
Well, they're probably the passengers who drifted here from a wrecked ship.
About a month ago, there was a report that a passenger liner went missing in this area.
Well, then... Okay. I'm going back, but before that...
You guys, get ready to depart right away.
Fortunately, there's an inhabited island not so far from here.
You should go there to get the treatment you need.
Hey, you guys! You don't have to listen to this guy! He's a marine!
Is there a problem?
Oh... That's right. It's fine, it's fine. That's right. It's fine.
Normally, marines are your friends and we are the bad guys, huh?
It's no time for laughing!
He said he'd help those guys.
But does he have a ship?
Besides ours, I didn't see any other ships anywhere.
There's no ship. They don't have a Log Pose, either.
How are they supposed to go to that nearby island?
Oh, they'll be fine.
Nothing you say sounds convincing, you know.
It's true...
Hm?
That man can make it happen.
All right, done!
We loaded up food and water. With this much, you'll be fine for a while.
It's nice to work once in a while.
Yeah, it feels good! You're quite a sensible guy!
He hit it off with him after all.
So what're you gonna do?
Are you gonna swim while pulling these guys and this stuff?
No way.
Step back a bit.
Wh-What the heck?!
A sea animal! I bet that's the guardian of this area of the sea!
What?! Hey, you! Run!
Watch out!
Rubber...
Ice Age!
Devil Fruit...!
Th-The sea... froze!
This is the power of a Navy Headquarters' Admiral.
This will probably last at least a week.
Take your time and head in that direction.
You'll get to an inhabited island in four days.
It's a little cold, so dress warmly while walking.
Is this... a dream?
The sea has become ground!
We can now cross the sea! We can get off of this island!
Mr. Marine! Thank you!
This is a miracle! A miracle without doubt!
Well then, we'll get going now.
Yeah. I'm happy for you guys.
Be careful.
I guess there're different kinds of pirates, huh?
We can't thank you enough.
Not only did you treat our injured, but you also shared your food and water with us.
Don't worry about it.
They say that even a chance meeting is due to karma from a previous life, so...
Take good care of the children so that they don't catch a cold.
In this state, the food will probably stay fresh for a while.
Bye-bye! Thank you!
Thank you very much.
We'll never forget your kindness,Straw Hat Pirates!
See ya! Take care!
Be careful on your trip!
Good, good.
Whoa, it's cold. It's cold.
This is completely like winter.
I can ice skate!
Whoa! That's amazing, Chopper!
Boy, it's cold, it's cold!
I'm gonna freeze!
Hm?
Hmm...
What?
How should I put it... You're just like your gramps, Monkey D. Luffy...
Wh-What?
You're free-spirited, or should I say you're hard to figure out?
G-Gramps...
Gramps...?! Luffy's?!
Hey, what's the matter, Luffy? You're drenched in sweat.
Well... N-N-Nothing. Um... well...
Your gramps really helped me out a while back.
The reason I came here was to have a look at Nico Robin and you.
On second thought... maybe you should die now, huh?
The government is still taking you guys lightly,
But if I delve into your history, I can tell that your group has a backbone.
Although your group is small, since it's still gathering shrewd members,
it'll probably become a problem later on.
The circumstances that initially led to your search orders...
All the actions you took up until now...
The speed of your group's progress...
I've been dealing with outlaws for a long time...
And it worries me to think how you'll turn out.
Th-That's too sudden!
You said earlier that you just
came to check things out!
The reason I especially regard you guys as dangerous is...
You, Nico Robin.
So you're after Robin after all! I'm gonna beat the crap out of you!
Her bounty amount isn't just an indication of her strength.
It also indicates the level of danger she poses to the government.
That's why you got a 79-million-Berry bounty on your head at the age of eight.
I'm impressed that you survived as a child.
You betrayed people and ran away. You gained people's favor and used them.
You've survived in the underworld by being quick to switch sides.
So this is the group that you chose as your next hideout, huh?
Hey, you jerk! How insulting you are!
What grudge do you hold against Robin-chan?!
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have any grudge against her.
If we are somehow connected...
It's that I let her get away once, that's about it.
It was a long time ago.
You guys will eventually realize it, too.
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret that you took in a troublesome woman.
As proof, the organizations Nico Robin had something to do with up until today
all got annihilated... Except for her.
I wonder why... Nico Robin?
Stop it, you jerk! Her past doesn't matter!
I see... You really did a good job befriending this lot.
Just get to the point already! If you want to capture me, go ahead and do it!
Treinta Fleurs!
Robin! Stop it!
Oh, my, my... Maybe I talked too much.
How disappointing!
I had too high an opinion of you, thinking you were a little smarter than that.
Clutch!
Ahhh! He shattered into pieces and died!
N-No... We're screwed...
H-Hey! Guys! Run! Let's get out of here!
That wasn't nice.
Ice Saber!
I wasn't going to kill you, but...
Slice Shoot!
Rubber...
Pistol!
It's cold!
He froze them!
Those three... all at once...
O-Oh, no! They have to be treated right away!
If they get frostbite, their limbs will become gangrenous!
What're you doing, Usopp?! We have to go help those three now!
I-I really would like to, but my body can't move. Did I get frozen, too?
No! You're just too scared to move!
Luffy!
Sanji! Zoro!
Robin! Run!
You've come across some good friends.
But you're still you, Nico Robin!
No...! I'm no longer...
Robin! Watch out! Run!
I'm...
Robin-chan!
Robin!
You bastard!
Don't yell... She'll still live if you defrost her carefully.
But her body has become fragile, so be careful.
If her body is broken, she'll die.
For example...
If you smash it like this...
Robin!
No!
Stop it!!
Hm?
That was close...
Good job!
Amazing, Usopp!
What the hell...?
Usopp! Chopper!
Run to the ship! Treat Robin and save her!
G-Got it!
Hurry up...! But gently, okay?
It's cold!
You idiot! Think of how cold Robin is!
Don't bother...
It'd be better for the world not to save that woman.
Not to split hairs, but a pirate group is a collection of people like that.
You got that right, lady.
Get out of my way, would you?
Nami-san!
We can't...
Just let you...
Wait, you two!
Don't interfere. I wanna fight him in a duel.
Let us settle this fight, just you and me!
That's fine...
...but since I don't have a ship to take you back in, I'll kill you, okay?
She... can't breathe, can she?
I think she's probably in a state of suspended animation.
Th-Then won't she die if we don't hurry up?
But if we warm her rapidly, her body will break.
We need to restore her body temperature from the inside.
I-Is this really gonna work?
I don't know... but this is the only way...
You can't just say you don't know! Robin's life depends on you!!
But I've never seen a human whose entire body got frozen like this!
Sure, Aokiji said she was still alive,
but to me, it's surprising that she's still alive!
Don't whine! If you can't do anything, then no one can save her!
You're the doctor on this ship!
I know that! Just shut your mouth for a while!
Chopper!
Ah... What?! Why?! Just the three of you?!
We'll explain it later!
We're gonna go back right away!
Do something about our frozen arm and leg!
Ahh, okay. Let's see...
We have to melt those frozen areas with water immediately.
But we're using the shower room for Robin right now.
Is she okay?!
It's too early to tell.
What?
So will this do?
Once you melt the ice at low temperature, come up to the ship while rubbing the affected parts!
Nami! Help us treat Robin!
Okay!
Why are you guys here? Where's Luffy?! What about Aokiji?!
Luffy said he wanted a duel.
A duel?! And you guys left Luffy there by himself?!
Those were the captain's orders.
Hey! Even if it was the captain's order, you can't just do that!
Aren't you guys a little too cold-hearted?! Luffy is...
Shut up!
It's a duel. Can't you understand?!
Stop it! This is no time for that!
We're... in a crisis right now.
Whether this decision is his passing whim or whatever,
if anything should happen, be prepared to respond to that!
As I thought, you're an odd one.
Rubber...
Storm!
Ice Time...
Let us settle this fight, just you and me!
Darn... I was tricked.
Since I accepted the duel, this fight ends when I win.
Now I see...
If I mess with the others now, I'd be the senseless one here...
Right, Captain?
Or...
Did you seriously intend to defeat me?
Let me say this.
In the future, Nico Robin will grow...
That woman will definitely grow to be too much for you to handle.
You guys will no longer be able to shoulder the burden of the brutal fate
that Nico Robin was born into.
That's what it means...
...to let her on your ship...
...Monkey D. Luffy!
Breaking you right here, right now and killing you would be very easy,
but we owe you one.
This settles our debt to you for defeating Crocodile.
Also...
Err... Well, I guess I don't have to talk about that idiot Smoker.
See you around!
There he is!
Luffy!
He didn't get broken into pieces!
Good, good...
Lets carry him!
Let's hurry to the ship!
Don't talk at the same time!
According to this island's log, their next destination is...
Hm?
Water Seven... The city of water, huh?
Oh, my, my... They're really getting closer to our Headquarters.
Oops, sorry about that.
Both of them...
Their hearts...
...started beating!
All right!
Luffy!
Robin-chan!
No! You can't go in yet!
You'll make a racket, right?
Hey, Dr. Chopper. I'll make something for them.
Y-You calling me "doctor" wouldn't make me feel happy, you jerk!
Ah, when they wake up, some drinks that can warm them up would be good.
I'll carry them to the lounge later.
Aye-aye, sir!
Nami, are we gonna sail out?
No, we aren't, with our captain like that.
We've already got the log, but let's stay here for today.
Hm?
What's the matter, Usopp? Are you feeling drained?
I wonder if strong guys like him are coming after us from now on...
All I did was get flustered.
Get some sleep, you idiot. You're exhausted.