Don't let up!  Fire!
Punk Hazard Island, Central Lake
-Luffy's Group-
They won't listen to us!
What are you doing now -pooh?!
Legson isn't helping at all!
Oh, a Devil Fruit user, is he?
That makes things easier!
Fire!
Aim directly below their boat!
W-We've gotta retreat!
What are you talking about, Usopp?!
Forward!
You don't understand the situation at all, do you?!
Those guys are trying to sink us into the lake!
You cannot escape from me, Brownbeard-sama!
I'm a former pirate
whose bounty was 80,060,000 beli!
Take my attack of rage!
Dammit!  They...
We're falling!
Oh no!
Alright!  We did it!
That's Boss for ya!
He capsized their boat!
Have you learned your lesson?
Now you can struggle all you like,
until you sink to the ocean floor!
Aaaah!  It's so cold!
More than a few minutes here and we'll become icicles!
Y-You had plenty of time to fight back, Luffy!
But you kept on saying such dumb things.
So... you should be more careful what...
Sowwy... It'th awright...
I dun' wanna make'em my friendth anymo'...
Alright, finish them off!
Hey, Usopp!
Take both of them for me!
I'm gonna slice'em up!
H-Hurry... I'm almost...
I'll finish this quickly!
Hey!  What's wrong, Zoro?!
Sharks!  Why are there sharks in the lake?!
You fool!  This is technically the ocean!
This hole was ground zero of the fight
between Aokiji and Akainu.
Cracks tore right through the island,
so sea water flowed in and made this lake!
Of course there are ocean creatures here!
Zoro!
Sharks!  Scary!  Sharks!
Zoro got eaten by sharks!
Aim carefully!  They can't do anything now!
They're everywhere!  We're doomed!
Blast them to smithereens!
Why?!  I never imagined my life would end like this!
This is the end!
Fire!
What?!  What happened?!
Brook!
Most frigid of winds,
cuts colder than the arctic.
Feel the underworld.
Damn you, you filth!
Ah, I did not have time to warn you.
I froze your gunbarrels...
so if you shoot, they will explode in your faces!
Who are you, skeleton-mask?!
You are unworthy to hear my name.
It's Brook.
You still told it to me?
I returned from the underworld,
and dedicated my second life
to my captain with the straw hat!
I am known as the Soul King!
When did he pull that trick with our guns?!
We won't let you get away with this, you damn-
"Won't let you get away with this?"
That's my line!
Damn you!
How dare you?!
I will not lose my crewmates a second time!
Only ice!
Damn he's fast!  He's too strong!
The sharks have all been killed!
Hey!  Where did they go?!
Here!
You came at a perfect time, Brook.
I'm glad you're alright!
As it happens, I was chased here by a strange fellow...
You've really done it now,
you half-man half-beast freaks!
Do you really think my training was so weak...
that I'd die to something as trivial as sharks?!
But... the human body... can't train against the cold...
Freezing... I'm turning into ice!
I told you... you guys...
that trying to cross the frozen lands...
in these clothes...
But look... We're in luck.
We should be thankful... that we met them.
Boss!  We won't let them take another step!
Wait!  There's something familiar about these guys!
That one will do...
I'm going with the fourth guy from the right!
I've decided...  I'll take the one next to him!
I'll take that one...
The one that girl at the far left is wearing...
What are they saying?
Those clothes look so warm!
Alright, go!
Get one for me, too!
Are they... coming for our coats?!
How crude!  What are they, highwaymen?
Now I remember!  It's that hat!
That's one of the rookies
from the Worst Generation two years ago!
That's right... He's Fire-Fist's little brother!
The pirate worth four hundred million, Straw Hat Luffy!
F-Four hundred million?!
Help me!
Hurry!
This way, children!
We've gotta find the back door!
Wait!
Go back!
It was that man!  It was he who cut me down!
What?  Really?!
So does he have your body?
No... he most likely does not, however...
Then this can wait until later!
Please, wait!  He might know something!
Our first priority is to find a backdoor!
We're not going back to meet the Navy!
The samurai was with them.
Hurry!
I can't let the Straw Hats escape, either.
What's this?!
It's like some sort of thin film or something.
What was that?  It felt weird...
I guess that's not important right now!
Now hurry and run, damn kids!
Huh?  Did I drop my cigarette?
Follow me!
Sheesh, what are you doing now, Sanji-kun?!
I'm particularly super this week!  Finding a backdoor will be easy!
Guys?
Pull back, Vice-Admiral!
His power is just too damn creepy!
We can't fight this guy!
I can't allow a single one of you to escape.
He attached it to the bedrock of the island?!
He reshaped the ship into some weird object!
Dammit!  Without the ship, we can't get back to base!
The Warlords report to the Government!
Attacking us is against the rules, you know!
Trafalgar!
I'll report this to HQ!
You'll be stripped of your position!
No need to worry.
What's this?!  Cut it out!
Huh?  Snail Phones?
What?  It's gone!
No way... Mine too?!
Those are ours!
He took all our Snail Phones!
I cannot let you report anything you've seen
on this island, not to the Government or HQ!
Do you think we're just going
to let you act like the pirate you've always been?!
Smokey!
Even if you are a surgery-man who ate
the Ope Ope Fruit, and can operate on everything!
Don't get in the way of his attacks, men!
He cut me!
Huh?  I'm alive...
You're in my way!  Get out of the circle!
Circle?!
As long as you're inside the circle that Law created,
you're like patients strapped to his operating table!
This is his operating room.
He can freely control and operate on
anything within this space.
He is the Surgeon of Death!
Trafalgar!
If that's what you're trying to do...
Stop it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is no match for him!
Captain-chan!
C-Captain-chan got cut in half!
Hey!  You're still alive, right, Tashigi-chan?!
What...
What a disgrace!
To lose a swordfight without fighting to the death.
If you're going to cut me, then kill me, Trafalgar!
You have the attitude of a master swordsman,
if nothing else.
Remember this, Miss Marine!
The weak don't get to decide anything, not even how they die.
Damn you!
That sword...
can't even reach me.
But if this is what you want, I will gladly cut you again.
You bastard!  Don't humiliate Captain-chan!
Captain-chan, leave this to us!
That messed up bastard is gonna be filled with holes!
Bullets?!
Where'd those bullets come from?!
Where'd our bullets go?!
Those were the bullets you fired.
I swapped them with the snow over there.
Is he invincible?!
Get down! He's planning to cut us again!
There's no way to block his attacks!
That bastard!
Captain-chan, run!
Captain-chan!
Smokey!
Surgeon of Death... Trafalgar Law!
I can sense a nasty energy.
The tip of that jutte is made of Sea Stone, isn't it?
Watch out!  That crazy thing he made...
The ship's falling!
Let's get out of here as fast as we can!
We're just in the way!
Captain-chan, we've gotta get out of here!
But...
They're way out of our league!
Run!  Get out of the circle!
The frozen lands
- Luffy's Group -
That was really loud.  Maybe it's Sanji and the others?
Hey, Crocotaur!
You sure you don't know anything about my friends?
Shut up!  I'm not telling you anything!
Fine!  Then run faster!
How humiliating, he's just a kid...
and he cruelly stole my underlings' coats!
You damn highwaymen!
This crocodile-guy
doesn't seem to regret his actions at all.
Anyway, Brook...
You've got no skin, so it can't be cold for you, right?
Why did you take a coat as well?
I do have feelings.
I feel sorry for Nami and the others.  They didn't change clothes before they were kidnapped.
I hope their arms and legs haven't fallen off from frostbite.
Stop it, Robin!  Don't worry in such a cruel way!
Master, what do we do?
Sir Law and Smoker are fighting a huge battle.
What is Law thinking?
The plan was to just chase them away.
Well, the pirates who had escaped earlier...
took the kids from the Biscuits Room...
and ran into Law and Smoker at the entrance!
Did the Navy see the kids?!
Yes.
So the worst has happened.
This means that the island will be investigated!
Even if we wipe out Smoker now,
the Navy would surely become suspicious!
Those pirates are in here, after all.
Why are you back so soon, Monet?
This is them, no doubt about it.
Perhaps we should have been more careful?
Oh, right, I forgot to mention...
Vegapunk's dragon and Brownbeard's Centaur squad
have both been defeated.
What?!
Impossible!
In other words, the crew you kidnapped, ship and all, had other members...
who had found their way into the burning lands.
Now they've crossed the lake, and are almost here.
I thought they seemed oddly strong, and what do you know...
Newspaper: The Straw Hat Pirates Back at Full Strength
It's really them, isn't it?
The Straw Hat... Pirates?
The ship's flying around like a leaf!
Captain-chan, how's your body?
Did we manage to reattach it properly?
Hey, that right arm of yours... That's my left leg!
Whose feet are my arms?!
This is awful!
We can't contact HQ, and we have no ship!
I thought the Seven Warlords were our allies!
Tashigi, remember this.
No matter what, pirates will always be pirates.
Pirates... will be pirates.
I never trusted you Warlords to begin with.
That may be wise.
Law!
Is this place important to you?!
You must be getting orders from someone!
What are you scheming... on this island?!
First answer me!
What are your schemes?!
You can't see the whole picture
until you look at it from the outside.
Smoker!
My heart...
I don't have to tell you anything.