Then take me on your
next voyage, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate too!
As if you could
ever be a pirate!
Why not?!
Luffy.
Just bein' a good swimmer doesn't
mean you'd make a good pirate.
I'm good at fighting too!
My punches are like pistols!
Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
He means you're too much
of a kid, Luffy!
Seriously, you're as old
as my own kid!
I'm not a kid!
I'm a grownup!
Now, now.
Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
Wow! Thanks!
--See, you are a kid! Ha!
--That wasn't fair, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Stupid cheapskate Shanks!
Pardon us.
Oh... So these are "pirates".
Look pretty damn dumb.
Welcome...
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here
to tear up the place.
Sell us some booze.
10 barrels oughta do.
I'm sorry.
I just ran out of alcohol.
That's odd.
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
No, what they're drinking
is the last of it.
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
There's an 8 million Berry
bounty on my head, you know.
One bottle ain't even enough for
a bedtime drink! Don't insult me!
Now the floor's all wet.
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Oh, I'll do that!
Seems you like to clean.
Then maybe you'll find
this more fulfilling.
Not worth our time if they're
out of booze. Let's go!
Later, wimps!
Are you all right, Captain?
Are you hurt?!
Oh, I'm fine.
No problem at all.
--He got you good, boss!
--Talk about lame!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
you're not men -or pirates -
if you laugh after
something like that!
I can understand
how you feel,
but he only spilled
some booze on me.
It's nothing worth
getting mad over.
Whatever!
--Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
--Shut up!
Wait, what're you eating?!
That box! Did you eat what
was in that box?!
Y-yeah...
Spit it out! Right now!
Every last bite!
W-what're you doing, Shanks?!
What... was that?
What you ate was
the Gum-Gum Fruit!
The Gum-Gum Fruit is known
as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your
body to rubber,
and makes you lose the ability to
swim for the rest of your life!
Eh?! No way!
You dumbass!
People were drinkin'
and havin' a nice time.
What's the idea, boy?
Dammit! Apologize!
How dare you make fun of
Shanks and his crew!
Did I say something
to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Mayor!
You see the looks
on those pirates' faces?!
He got covered in booze
but didn't say a word!
Talk about pathetic!
Pirates are just
a bunch of wimps.
They're nothing
but talk.
Stop it!
Stop making fun of Shanks
and the others!
They are not wimps!
Stop, Luffy!
Stop making fun of Shanks and the others!
You stupid bandits!
You oughta watch
your mouth, boy.
No one who's ever made me
mad has lived to tell the tale.
Wait!
Let the boy go! Please!
I don't know what
Luffy has done,
nor do I intend
to fight with you!
If you're not offended,
I'll even pay you!
Just, please!
Spare the boy's life!
Mayor!
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
But no, it's too late
for him now.
After all, he's made me angry...
You're the bad guys!
You mountain apes!
You're a lost cause, kid.
You can regret all this
in the next life!
--Luffy!
--Please! Let him go!
I was wondering why
the bar was empty...
...looks like it's those
mountain bandits from before.
Captain!
Shanks!
So you pirates
are still here, huh?
Have you been scrubbing the
village clean this whole time?
Luffy!
I thought your punches were
as strong as pistols?
S-shut up!
I dunno why you're here, but you'd
best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and he'll shoot
your head off, wimp.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow
your head off!
Put your life on the line.
Huh?!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
What the hell're
you talkin' about?
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
--N-now you've done it!
--These bastards fight dirty!
--Dirty?
--Cut the crap.
What, do you think you're
dealing with saints or something?
You're looking at pirates!
Shut up! You got nothin' to do
with this in the first place!
Listen, bandits.
Whether I'm splattered with
alcohol or food or even spit on,
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
But!
No matter what the reason,
anyone who hurts
my friends has to pay!
Shanks...
Has to pay, huh?!
Lousy pirates!
Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this.
Should be easy enough.
Don't get cocky, bandit.
If you wanna fight us, then go
drag a warship here or somethin'.
So strong!
H-hold on!
The kid attacked us!
You are a wanted man.
Damn it!
A smokescreen!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down!
Luffy's gone!
What do we do, guys?!
Quit freakin'
the hell out, boss!
It won't take us long
to find him!
I can't believe this guy...
I made a clean getaway!
They'll never expect a mountain
bandit to escape onto the sea!
Dammit! Let me go,
you stupid ape!
I hope you die!
You wish! You're the one
who's gonna die!
After all, you've made me mad!
So long!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum,
but I couldn't even
hit them once! Dammit!
Sorry! I got no use
for you anymore!
W-what the hell?!
Help!
Shanks!
Get lost!
I'm in your debt,
Luffy...
Makino-san told
me everything.
You fought for us.
Hey, don't cry!
You're a man!
But... Shanks!
Your arm!
It's only an arm.
It's no big deal.
I'm just glad
you're alright...
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Well, yeah, but I won't
ask you to take me anymore.
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather
a crew every good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the greatest
treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates! I'll show you!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back
to me someday!
Once you've become
a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!