Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Formatting
Sewil
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Roger and Rayleigh
Wait!
What's going on here?! Save me!
Good grief...
There are even more of them than I thought.
You guys sure have some weird powers!
Yours is the strangest of all.
Really?
I can't believe that the mortar cannons didn't work on all three of them!
Seems like they've earned their reputations!
Think this is the time to be impressed?!
Somehow, we've got to hold them off until Admiral Kizaru arrives!
Think we're gonna wait for that?
A head!
Wait, don't throw me!
How can you talk?!
I don't know!
Also, my body feels hot for some reason...
Your body?!
You have a body?!
His body is burning up over there!
It's so hot!
My body is burning!
You can feel it?!
Will someone pour some water on him?
I thought I was gonna die...
Everyone, be careful!
That guy...
Don't get into the circles he creates!
Room.
Y-You mean this?
Yeah, it's this thing...
We were cut!
What's going on here?!
Just relax...
This'll be over soon.
Bone Balloon!
This arm is the arm of a giant!
Don't hesitate!
Ready your weapons!
Shoot!
Shoot all of them!
But Commodore!
Our weapons...
They're flying away!
W-What the...?!
What?
What's with that guy?!
This is no time to get distracted.
W-What the?!
Hey, that's my leg!
Then whose leg is that?!
You've got too many torsos!
Like I didn't know that!
Giant Pistol
Eat this!
Hey!
It's already this bad?
Amazing!
My eyes must be deceiving me!
Oh, man...
You're overdoing it, Captain...
Why, these guys aren't half bad.
They sure are impatient...
Hey, what happened to you, Straw Hat?
You're ruining the mood.
Really?
Well, I guess we've pretty much ruined their formation now.
Commodore, it seems all the pirates have come out of the auction house.
They're planning to run away!
Well, these brats shouldn't underestimate us!
Our reinforcements are on their way!
We've gotten the three hostages out through the back door.
Aim the mortar cannons at the people who don't have abilities!
Firing squad, get behind them!
All forces, prepare to attack!
Take out these pirates!
Here they come.
The enemy seems to have run out of strategies.
Now it's just a brawl.
I'm back to normal!
Well, see ya later, Straw Hat.
It was a pleasure meeting you in person...
But I won't show you any mercy the next time we meet!
But I'll be the one who finds One Piece!
Hey, Kid!
What are you just standing around for?!
Hey, Killer.
On the route that we took to get here...
Whenever we said we were gonna find One Piece, people just laughed at us...
Although I killed anyone who dared to laugh...
But after this...
we're going to an ocean where anyone who doesn't have the guts to say it will die.
Let's meet again in the New World!
Let's go, you guys!
Yeah!
Trafalgar Law!
How dare you do that to my mate back then?!
Bepo.
Huh?
Captain, are you going back there?
Oh, Sanji!
Luffy, look over there!
Hey!
Young master and friends!
Flying Fish guys!
Huh?
Did you just say I'm handsome?
More importantly, we're all set to go!
Aren't we, men?
Yes!
Life is rosy!
I'm not too happy about relying on those guys again,
but I guess we've got to hurry.
Right, let's go!
There's no choice!
Lullaby Parry
The two of you, hurry and go while you have the chance!
Yeah...
Don't fall asleep!
Are you an ally of the pirates, you scum?!
N-No, I'm not!
I ain't even a pirate!
Neuve Fleurs
Nine flowers
What?
Twist
T'was scary...!
Head!
He was traumatized back when Navy HQ tried to kill him, and yet...
He endured it, huh?
That's amazing!
Shaddup!
Think this be the right time to be talkin' about traumas and stuff like that?
We've got to help the young masters, whom I owe my life to, out of this pinch!
Old man, Franky, go on ahead!
Sure, thanks!
Don't let them get away!
How many of them are there, anyway?!
My blood is boiling!
You sure are an energetic old man!
Hey, hurry up, the three of you!
Sure!
Don't let the Straw Hat Crew get away!
They're responsible for all this!
Shoot them! Shoot them!!!
What is that?
Thunderbolt Tempo
That's Saint Rosward's slave!
How'd he get those chains off?
Wanna come with me,
pirate, Captain Jean Bart?
It's been a long time since anyone called me that!
As long as it means that you'll free me from the Celestial Dragons,
I'll gladly become your subordinate!
You should save half of that graditude for the Straw Hats.
They're still following us, even after we destroyed the bridge...
Of course they are.
The marines will probably be there when we return to the city, too.
Let's hurry and get off the island.
Kid!
Chief Kid!
Up there.
It can't be...
Why...
are you on this island?!
What a quick witted bear!
We can't even touch him!
How can a bear speak?!
I'm sorry...
He's too sensitive!
Hurry up, Bepo!
Damn!
They destroyed the bridge!
You're new, so you're my subordinate.
As long as I'm not a slave, anything is fine!
Captain, look at that!
Eustass and...
That's...!
What's one of the Seven Warlords doing in a place like this?!
Trafalgar Law...
So, you know my name?
Captain!
We're right next to Navy HQ and Mariejoa...
It wouldn't be strange running into anyone here.
The marines are coming at us from behind!
This guy isn't gonna let us pass, is he?
Trafalgar, you're in my way!
You want me to kill you?
I told you not to order me around, didn't I?
I'm running into a lot of big shots today...
I don't wanna meet an admiral on top of all this, so...
I shall make you let us pass...
...Bartholomew Kuma!
Grove 8
Hound Pets Hideout
Are you alive, Peterman-san?!
How could they do this to our boss?!
Damn it!
But...
I never thought Duval would look
so handsome under his iron mask!
Then, if you ever need anything, just call me!
We'll be your arms and legs until you're ready to go to Fishman Island!
Sure!
Thanks a lot, you guys!
Don't mention it.
Stop winking already.
Also...
This belongs to the mermaid, right?
My backpack!
That idiot, Peterman had it.
Thank you!
Now, let's go, Rosy-life riders!
Yes, Handrosy!
They've got quite a few different names for him, huh?
They're probably still trying to find a good one.
Let's hurry and get inside.
We've got to stabilize Hachi!
Hey, Shakki!
We're back!
Oh, Ray-san, welcome back.
That was fast.
I'm really impressed that you guys found him, Monkey-chan.
Hachi is badly injured, so we've got to get him to the bed fast.
What happened?
Never mind, I'll get a bed ready for him.
What?!
On the pirate king's ship?!
Yes...
I was the vice-captain.
I'm Silvers Rayleigh.
Nice to meet you.
Vice-captain?!
You didn't tell them, Hacchan?
We only needed him to coat the ship...
Oh, you didn't notice?
I totally know that name!
It's written down in so many books...
That's definitely a name everyone's heard at least once...
Gold Roger?
There might have been a rookie
by that name, or maybe there wasn't...
How does that octopus know a big shot like you?
Well, Hachi helped me out once when I was stranded at sea over 20 years ago.
He saved his life.
He was just a child at the time, though.
Hachi and I used to get along pretty well before he joined the Sun Pirates.
Arlong's crew, right?
But...
If Gold Roger was executed 22 years ago...
How come you, the vice-captain, are still alive?
Your crew was captured by the navy, right?
We weren't captured.
Roger surrendered to them.
I suppose the government claimed that they'd "captured" him, to show their power.
The Pirate King surrendered?!
Why?!
He could see the end of our journey.
It was probably about four years before he was executed...
Roger caught an incurable disease.
Huh?
It was a disease that nobody could cure or stabilize.
Even Roger suffered from it, but...
But one man, the most well-known doctor of his time...
A man called Crocus of the Twin Capes, had the skill to ease his suffering.
We asked him for help, and he joined as the ship's doctor for our last journey.
And then, three years later, while holding off Roger's disease...
We did what they said was impossible, and conquered the Grand Line.
C-C-Crocus-san?!
From the Twin Capes...
Oh, how nostalgic!
What?!
I thought that old man had been at those capes for fifty years!
So he was part of the Pirate King's crew?
Come to think of it, he did say he'd been a ship's doctor for a while.
So he was a pirate for those three years?
If you met him, then that must mean that he's still well.
Crocus only had one condition...
That we let him look for a certain pirate crew whom he wanted to find.
Hey, Brook!
That must mean he went off to sea to look for you guys!
So Crocus-san even did something like that for us?
He was only a crew member for three years...
But he was, without a doubt, our comrade.
At my age, I would really like to see him again.
So, what happened after you conquered the sea?
After that...
Roger became known all over the world as the Pirate King.
It's not like he'd been called the Pirate King all along.
Titles like that didn't mean much for a man on the verge of death...
But, Roger was happy about it.
He was a man who loved doing everything in grand style...
Be it celebrations or battles...
Even though he knew he wouldn't live much longer, he seemed to enjoy himself...
Eventually, at the captains orders, the Roger Pirates disbanded.
We all went our separate ways, and one after another, everyone disappeared.
I have no idea what our comrades whom we risked our lives with are now, nor what they are doing.
Then, one year after the crew dissolved...
Roger turned himself in and was arrested.
It was decided that he would be executed in the town he was born in...
Loguetown in East Blue.
I hear that on that day...
Countless pirates who are famous today...
Were gathered in the square.
The Pirate King's execution was the center of attention for the world.
I didn't go.
These were the last words he said to me...
I'm not gonna die, partner.
I'm sure both the world government and the navy were surprised.
They had intended for the execution to be a warning to all the pirates who saw it...
But Roger's last words raised the curtain on the Great Pirate Era!
My treasures?
If you want them, they're yours!
Look for them!
I left it all at that place.
Just a few seconds before the flame of his life went out, it flickered...
And he turned it into a blazing flare that covered the entire world.
I've never laughed as hard as I did that night.
I've never cried as much as I did that night...
Nor have I ever drank as much as I did that night.
He led a marvelous life as my captain!
Seems like we just heard quite the story...
It sounds like a completely different story coming from someone who was involved...
Then, it's almost as though Roger intended to start this pirate-era!
I can't say anything for sure about that.
Roger died.
The ones creating the current era are those who live right now.
I'm sure there were a lot of people who received something from Roger in the square that day.
Shanks, whom you know well, was one of them.
Pops, you know Shanks?
If you're from East Blue, then maybe you know a pirate named Buggy as well?
Buggy!
Those two were swabbies aboard our ship.
Shanks was on the pirate king's ship?!
What, he didn't tell you?
It was about ten years ago...
I encountered him by chance on this island...
He'd lost his trademark straw hat and his left arm.
When I asked him why, he excitedly started telling me about you.
Rayleigh-san, I was really surprised...
There was a kid in East Blue who said the exact same thing Captain Roger said.
Those exact same words as the captain!
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 27
I see a warship approaching the port!
The admiral has arrived!
Ah, Kizaru here.
I've arrived.
Requesting a response.