Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Infoboxes
Timing
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Flying Fish Riders
See you guys later!
We'll never forget what you did for us, Straw Hat!
The sun...! Thanks for giving us the sun back!
Everyone! Be careful to not get yourselves wiped out!
Don't say crazy stuff like that!
Lola! Thanks for the Vivrecard! Stay well!
If you meet Mama, give her my regards!
Let's meet again someday, Namizou!
Set sail!
No one truly knows what happens in this mysterious sea, the Florian Triangle...
They're gone...
Seems like it.
Now that that's over, let's set sail tomorrow!
Yeah!
Every year, over 100 ships vanish in the mist.
This started long before the enormous pirate ship, Thriller Bark, started hiding in the mist ten years ago.
It is a deep, ancient mystery...
It is lucky that the mist is as thick as ever this day...
For that strange face in the sea is concealed by its thick white veil...
Luffy...
Is this really okay with you?
Huh?
Ah, about Ace's paper, huh?
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Luffy-san, I would have no objections if you wished to take a detour!
Time is of no great importance to Laboon and myself!
To "live" and "meet once more"... That is all that matters!
Luffy, we're all totally fine if you want to take a detour!
It's fine, it's fine!
Yeah! Let's go see your whale of a brother!
No, it's fine, really!
Even if he was in some kind of trouble, he wouldn't want me to worry...
Ace hates being made to look weak!
If we went to help him, he'd just get pissed off.
If we do meet up, it'll be as enemy pirates!
Ace has his own adventure.
That "Vivre Card" apparently doesn't just shrink when the owner's in bad condition...
It goes back to how it was once they recover.
Yeah! If we meet, it'll be at that time.
That's why Ace gave me this paper, right?
Oh, and Zoro!
You were asleep all along, so we haven't done this yet!
Well, let's do it properly then!
To celebrate the recruitment of our new companion, the musician Brook...
Cheers!
Most obliged!
Alright! Pull in the sails! We'll launch our way out of here with the Coup de Burst!
Coup de Burst!
What is this?!
Holy Land, Mariejoa
Don't be ridiculous!
Bartholomew Kuma, are you telling me that they managed to escape from your powers?!
I want a better explanation than that! I'm the one who has to report this to the higher-ups!
Just what I expected from my grandson!
Garp, be quiet!
You were given a special Government order to eliminate the whole crew,
yet you couldn't even bring back Straw Hat Luffy's head? This is a disgrace!
Don't worry about that, Sengoku!
Luffy isn't the kind of guy who would go around bragging about defeating Moriah anyway!
Hmph!
Kuma, I hope you didn't take pity on those pirates just because they were injured.
Because you've failed to take this seriously, this game of cat-and-mouse will have no end.
If they continue blindly following the Log, as they are now, they will draw ever closer to the Navy HQ.
Oh, yeah, by the way... I brought the new tea!
Get out the crackers!
Garp, will you be quiet?!
A few days later
Grand Line
Thousand Sunny
Serpent currents!
Serpent... currents?
Everyone, be careful!
Let's go, everyone!
That's...
Coup de Burst!
We're here...
We've finally made it this far!
It feels kind of nostalgic...
I can't see the top! It's huge!
So this is the Red Line?
I wonder if we've matured since then?
I kinda feel like crying!
A lot of stuff has happened, huh?
Anyways, now we're halfway there!
The Twin Capes on the other side of the world, where we met Laboon, is connected to this spot!
Current location
It's great that we've all made it this far, huh?
I was told I came over Reverse Mountain from South Blue when I was just a kid...
But I guess that's a 30 year old tale.
I came to this sea from West Blue, five years ago.
When we've crossed the other half of the world, and see this wall again...
At that time...
I'll be the Pirate King!
But we've got to be careful now.
This place is close to the "Holy Land" of the World Government and the Navy HQ, Mariejoa.
This "surprise-pool" is the best!
I'm too weak.
I have to become stronger!
I'm still far too weak!
I'm still...!
How is it, Robin, Brook, Luffy?
No use. It's completely black.
It's totally black out there!
Hey, I think I saw something there!
Was that the eyeball of a monster?
A-a monster?
W-We are going to die!
Although I am already dead!
Oh, by the way, Nami-san? I have a question...
What panties are you wearing today?
Shut up! Take this seriously!
Scary...!
He's a plucky guy, huh?
Hey, you guys! The Shark Submerge can't go any deeper than 5,000 metres, so be careful!
Hmm? The hull seems to be creaking.
Yes, it's because...
we're deeper than 5,000 metres right now.
Ah, that means...
But that is terrible! We are going to be crushed by the water-pressure!
Oh! The monster from earlier! It's still here!
What a big mouth it has.
Watch out!
It's gonna eat us!
Here it comes again!
This sounds pretty bad...
I don't want to ride the Shark Submerge...
Me neither.
Nami-swan!
The "Horror-Nashi Tarte" from Thriller Bark is done!
Oh, it looks good!
But this is a problem...
It tastes great!
It's good!
It's the same problem we had with Sky Island.
That's right...
We know the direction we have to take,
but we have no idea how we're gonna get there.
How are we gonna reach Fishman Island?
We're back!
That was fun!
Welcome back! Good work!
It's no use!
We can't see anything on the bottom of the sea at all. Is Fishman Island really there?
That was my first time riding a submarine.
If we'd have gone further down, the pressure would have killed us.
The Log Pose is certainly pointing straight down, but...
This is no good... I should have gotten some more info from Lola and the others.
It's that thing from earlier!
It followed us!
Don't think you can beat me when we're above the water!
Rubber...
Rifle!
Somehow, he didn't seem all that huge.
Because we dealt with Oars! Seems like we're fine.
Something came out.
A fish?
A person?!
No, that is wrong...
That's a...
C-Could it be?!
Ah! I crushed a human!
I'm so sorry! Are you OK?
Oh, don't worry about it~!
Anyway, who are...
Please pull yourself together! Are you OK?
That's...
I can't believe I did something like that! Please pull yourself together!
A fin...
Could it really be...?
A mermaid?!
What a shock! There are so many humans here!
W-What?
W-We're surprised too!
Camie
Kissing Gourami
Mermaid
(Designer Apprentice,
Takoyaki Shop Employee)
I thought I was going to be digested. Thank you for saving me.
I keep getting swallowed by monsters.
This was probably the 20th time.
You get eaten too much!
I have to repay you somehow.
Oh, I know! Would you like some takoyaki?
Takoyaki?! That's my favorite food!
Really?! Then that'll be 500 belly per person!
Hey, you're selling them?!
I screwed up!
Mermaid~! Mermaid~!
Mermaids, the dream of all mankind! Mermaids, the jewels of the ocean!
Yes, I've finally gotten to meet one of them!
She's so cute~!
This is the first time I've ever met one!
Camie, was it?
It's not the first time.
You met old lady Kokoro, didn't you?
Thriller Bark? No, that wasn't scary. Not scary at all.
The scariest thing we've encountered so far was...
Uh, that's right, Sanji! Let's just pretend that never happened!
This is the first mermaid we've ever met!
You guys are so rude!
Huh? Old lady Kokoro was a mermaid?
But she could walk, couldn't she?
I see... You didn't know, huh?
Well, it happened while you were fighting that Lucci fellow after all.
Imagining old lady Kokoro as a mermaid is really gross for some reason.
You are too freaking blunt!
Geez, when it comes to this guy's expectations of mermaids...
But she seems like a cute mermaid, doesn't she?
This is my first encounter with a mermaid too.
Excuse me, would you please lend me some money?
Why would she?!
A skeleton!
See?! How are you gonna make it up if you scare her?! Get lost!
I can open my head as well. Isn't that funny?
Why you...!
That's so funny!
She sure got over that quickly.
By the way, can you poop?
What are you trying to ask, damn you?!
Ah, well, I...
Don't answer!
She does not poop!
Camie? Camie? This is just weird...
Aren't you missing someone?
Who's the one left out of this fun group?
Answer: Me.
That's right. I was wondering about this...
Hey, Camie, what's this?
This talking glove-thingy...
Oh, sorry. I completely forgot.
He's my pet, Pappag.
He's a starfish, and he's my master.
Nice to meet you!
Can starfish talk?
Isn't it strange for her pet to be her master?
Well, I was taken in, and with reason.
Camie always feeds me clams
So she feeds you?
Am I a person? I'm a starfish, yet I'm not a human.
Am I not a person? I'm not a person, but I am a starfish.
Are you busy? No, it's fine.
We've got enough hands around here.
Yay, thank you!
This is where you're supposed to laugh!
So, this T-shirt is of the "Criminal" brand, and it's really popular on Fishman Island these days.
Oh?
That's pretty cool.
Pappug designed it!
I want to become a designer one day too!
You will! You'll definitely make it, Camie!
Thank you, Sanji!
Nobody listens to me...
Oh yeah, you. How can you talk?
I'm glad you asked!
Back when I was a kid, I always thought I was a human.
By the time I found out that I was actually a starfish, I was already speaking the human language!
Does it really work like that?
Ah, the world works in strange and frightening ways. That's just how the world is!
Pappag
The starfish
(Criminal brand
designer)
Anyway, I'm Pappag the starfish!
Up-and-coming designer.
Thanks for saving me!
What a relief! We were having trouble figuring out what to do. I want to ask you something...
Hey, Nami! The takoyaki comes first!
Ah, that's right! The takoyaki to show my gratitude!
Well, I've got to meet up with Hacchin somewhere.
Hacchin?
Hello, Hacchin? This is Camie!
Sorry I got kinda lost. Where are you right now?
Oh, that voice must be Camie, right?
Hacchin?
Do you know who you're talking to?
This ain't Hacchin, y'know!
You're not Hacchin?!
This is Macro! From the simple-minded Macro Crew! Wait, I shouldn't say that myself...
Seems like trouble.
Why do you have Hacchin's Transponder Snail?
'Cause we beat up Hachi! Isn't it obvious?!
Liar! There is no way Hacchin would lose to you guys!
Yeah, you have a point. Usually, we'd be no match for him,
but this time, we had the Flying Fish Riders on our side!
The Flying Fish Riders?!
Camie, are you still alright? Thank goodness.
Hacchin! Did they really beat you?
I let my guard down.
Don't come here! I'll take out these guys and come straight back! It'll be fine!
Y'know, Camie, we're just about to sell this guy.
Octopus Fishmen are pretty rare, so he should fetch us quite the price.
Feel free to come and save him!
We're at the Sabaody Archipelago, in the waters five kilometres east of grove 44.
This is where the Flying Fish Riders' base is!
No! Camie, don't come here!
Shut up, you damn octopus!
See ya!
Hacchin...
So what about the takoyaki?
This isn't the time for that!
Wait... The voice of that Hacchin guy we just heard on the Transponder-Snail. It seemed kinda familiar...
It's just my imagination, right? There's no way...
Sorry, Luffy-chin. Can we do takoyaki later?
I've got to go save my friend!
Huh?
Hey!
Wait, Camie.
I shouldn't be meddling here, but if you want to save your friend, then we'll help you!
No, that's wrong. I mean, they'll help you!
Why, you...!
And in exchange, how about you help us get to Fishman Island?
Really, Nami-chin?
You're gonna help me save Hacchin, Luffy-chin?
Well, I'm fine with it. But who is this Hacchin anyway?
He runs the Takoyaki store I work at.
Our takoyaki is the best in the world!
That's important!
Men! Even if it costs you your lives, we're gonna save the takoyaki!
Yeah!
They say it's okay. So, do you know where they are?
Yeah, let's see...
Grove 44 is an island at the very eastern edge of the archipelago.
5 kilometres west from there. I guess the Flying Fish Riders' base would be about here.
Seeing how we're about here right now...
If we head straight for the Sabaody Archipelago from here, we should pass it on the way.
So, let's head west!
Afterwards we can ask the fish, and figure it out.
Yeah, that's right. Let's hurry and go!
Hey!
Wow! The fish are sticking their heads out!
We want you to lead the way!
They say they're afraid of the Flying Fish and won't take us all the way, but will show us the direction.
Incredible! You can talk to fish?
I had no idea mermaids could do that!
Camie, if you were around, we could eat as much fish as we wanted!
Watch your mouth. I'll beat you senseless.
But how do we follow the fish in the sea anyway?
Well, just take a look!
Awesome!
They can do this? I don't believe it!
The fish are drawing an arrow on the sea!
Fantastic! We just have to follow this, right?
You're awesome, Camie!
No, I have a long way to go.
No, this is really impressive!
Alright! Then, I'll take the helm!
Turn it around to 4 o'clock.
Right!
Zoro!
Are we already setting off? Does it look like we can make it to Fishman Island?
Forget that, and look here. It's Camie the mermaid! She's real! Awesome, right?
Hello!
A mermaid?
First time I've seen one.
He erased it! He just... erased his memory!
But I'm worried.
Hacchin sounded like he had trouble talking. I'm sure they've done something awful to him.
Well, he's tough, so it should be alright.
Anyway, you guys were pretty quick to offer your help, but are you sure you can handle this?
Yeah! We're strong.
I should warn you, there's not just one gang of kidnappers around here.
Human trading is big business on Sabaody Archipelago.
Selling human lives? That's horrible!
And seeing how mermaids are particularly valuable,
the Macro crew, a gang of three fishmen, have been after Camie for a while now.
Hachi from the Takoyaki shop probably thought we were kidnapped by the Macro Crew
and went after them, since we'd been missing for a while after we were eaten by that monster.
That's probably it.
Hacchin is a kind, straight-forward person after all.
It's my fault.
Hearing about this octopus named Hachi,
I can't help but think of that stupid fishman.
If it's really him, then we're not gonna help.
Well, there's no way...
Usually, Hachi could beat those guys easily...
But who'd have thought the Flying Fish Riders would help them?
Who're they?
Another kidnapping gang who started causing a lot of trouble around these parts recently.
They say that if they target you, you're doomed.
Their boss, Duval, is a guy with an iron mask.
Nobody knows what he really looks like.
It seems like they're looking for someone.
They check every single ship that passes this area.
Well, anyway, there's no need for you to worry, Camie. We'll definitely save the takoyaki!
It's the takoyaki seller!
Thank you, Luffy-chin!
Well then, Brook! Play a song to get us in the mood!
With pleasure!
Huh? Is that...?
Hey! We're in trouble!
What's wrong, Camie?
The fish said, "We're sorry, but we can't take you any further."
They're here! The Flying Fish Riders!
Where? I can't see anything!
Wrong! They're not in the sea, but in the air!
The fish are flying!
So cool!
Is this the time to be impressed?!
Damn, they're gonna attack us!
So the "Flying Fish" really can fly?!
Hey, did you see that?!
I saw it! No doubt, that's the Straw Hat Pirates!
Contact him right now!
Understood.
We only came here to find a single mermaid, but this must be our lucky day!
Master Duval is gonna be overjoyed!
Here they come again!
Don't come any closer!
Bombs, huh?
Damn those guys!
Rubber...
72 Pound Canon!
Pistol!
That was close.
Be careful! Once the flying fish jump out of the water, they can stay in the air for five minutes!
Flying Fish Riders'
Hideout
Hey, Macro.
Yes, Duval, my lord.
It seems that the mermaid you were luring to the base is on a pirate ship right now.
Huh? Camie is on a pirate ship?!
I'm sick of waiting... I really was sick of waiting!
That pirate ship is the one I've been waiting for!
I'll kill him!
That man who screwed up my life!