Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
Lance
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Translation
Funimation
Raws
df68
Captain Kuro
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Don't call it assassination, Jango.
That has a bad ring to it.
Oh, right. Accident. It's an accident.
Hey, what're those guys talking about?
D-Don't look at me!
That's what I'd like to know!
We can't simply kill her.
Miss Kaya must perish
in an unfortunate accident.
Don't mess that up!
So basically, on your signal,
the men and I storm
the village and kill the girl.
And then you'll get her inheritance...
You fool! You don't
understand a thing!
How would I, an outsider,
inherit Kaya's estate?!
You'll work hard to?
Working hard won't amount to squat.
Listen, this is the most important part!
Before you kill her, you'll use hypnosis
to make Kaya write her will...
to say: "I leave my entire fortune
to my butler, Klahadore!"
Only then will I inherit
her enormous fortune...
in a completely ordinary manner.
I've spent three long years gaining
the trust of everyone around me,
so that it would be unsurprising
for her to leave her inheritance to me.
Three years as a butler for that, huh?
But you sure scared us back then,
Captain Kuro.
Three years ago, you suddenly said
you were giving up life as a pirate.
In no time flat, you set up
a subordinate to be your double,
then let the world see
Captain Kuro get executed.
So that was the beginning of this plan.
You truly are Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans.
Don't call me that.
I abandoned that name
three years ago.
I now want to obtain
great sums of money
without the government on my back.
In other words, I'm a pacifist.
Some pacifist you are!
killing off an entire rich family
for this "peace" of yours.
Hold on, now.
The father's death was real.
I hadn't planned on that.
Well, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Just hurry and give the signal.
We've been waiting in the waters
for almost a whole week now.
The men are starting
to grow impatient.
This is bad!
We heard something really bad!
Hey, what's going on?
That sounds kind of bad.
Weren't you listening this
whole time?! This is seriously bad!
They're the real deal!
Captain Kuro is said to be the smartest
and most brutal pirate of all!
Rumor had it, the Marines caught
and executed him three years ago...
but Captain Kuro is alive!
As Klahadore, the butler!
He's been after Kaya's fortune
for these past three years!
They're gonna attack the village!
Kaya's in danger, too!
Bad!
This is seriously bad!
Hey, don't stand up! They'll see you!
Hey, you guys! Don't attack that girl!
Who're you?!
You idiot! They spotted you!
Hurry and hide before they kill you!
Oh...
If it isn't Usopp.
They spotted me, too!
Did you... hear anything?
N-No! Whatever do you mean?!
We just got here, so of course
we didn't hear anything!
We heard everything!
Hey, you!
Oh, all right.
Hey, you guys!
Watch this ring closely!
What's that?
Th-This is bad! It's a throwing
weapon! Dodge it!
At the count of "one, two, Jango,"
you will get sleepy.
Ready?
One, two...
Hide! He's gonna kill us!
...Jango!
Hey, wake up, Jango!
Have you still not fixed
that habit yet?!
H-Hey, what're you doing?!
You're gonna fall!
Hmm, head-first...
I didn't mean to kill him,
but he couldn't have
survived from that height...
Damn it!
He killed him!
That bastard! Damn it!
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
No need.
No matter what he does,
it won't matter.
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak.
Tear up the villagers' homes,
and make certain Miss Kaya's
murder looks like an accident!
Tomorrow!
You heard me, Usopp.
There's nothing you can do
to stop my plan.
Damn it!
You sure about him?
Of course. My plans are flawless.
This is bad, this is bad, this is bad!
Everyone in this village, who I
grew up with, is going to be killed!
Kaya's going to be killed!
Even though I love them all!
Who are you?!
I'm Usopp!
A brave warrior of the sea!
I hear you've been unhappy lately!
I'll cheer you up with a story!
Mind your own business!
Please leave! I'll call for someone!
And then? What happened after that?!
I fought, of course! Bravely, at that!
Damn it!
– Captain!
Huh?
Wasn't Luffy with him?
– Captain!
Where's Luffy...?
Is he still mad about
his dad being insulted?
Who knows.
No, that look was different!
Yeah, something must've happened!
Why do you suppose he
looked so desperate?!
Hey, how do we get
to this shore of yours?
Doesn't this smell like trouble?!
Yeah, something must've
happened at the shore!
I think this calls for the Usopp Pirates!
Alright, already!
How do we get there?!
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are going to attack!
Tomorrow morning, pirates are
going to attack this village!
Everyone, run away!
Alright, Usopp! Enough is enough!
You're gonna pay once and for all!
N-No, it's not like that!
It's the truth this time!
Shut up! All you ever do
is spout huge lies!
If you were as honest as
Klahadore, then we'd believe you!
No matter what he does,
it won't matter.
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
Damn it!
So he ignored me because
nobody would believe me anyway?!
Are these to your liking?
They're the ones you custom-ordered
from the eyewear shop...
in the next town over.
Yes, they're perfect!
I'm sorry for asking you
to go all the way there.
It's a present, isn't it?
Yes.
Tomorrow will be three years, since the day
Klahadore came to this mansion.
He's always taken
good care of me, so...
Klahadore will be delighted!
Yes!
Please hear me out, everyone!
Pirates really are going to
attack tomorrow morning!
If we believed every
story you ever told,
we'd have fled the village
hundreds of times by now!
Please, believe me!
We gotta get out of here!
They really are going to kill everyone!
I swear it's the truth this time!
And we're gonna get you this time!
Dammit!
Get him! Don't let him escape!
Thank you for coming, men.
It's truly been three long years.
Once this plan succeeds,
I intend to give you all
plenty of the take.
At dawn tomorrow,
destroy the village
to your hearts' content!
– What?! They're going to kill Miss Kaya?!
– Are they really going to attack the village?!
Yeah, that's what they said.
No question about it.
So what were you
sleeping down here for?
That's the thing!
I thought I was up on the cliff...
So how'd I get down here?
I knew it, Klahadore's a bad guy!
No wonder he seems so creepy!
So that's why our captain ran
to the village with that intense look!
That's great, then!
Now they'll know and can
run away beforehand!
Talk about stupid bad guys!
Yeah, that's right!
We gotta run away, too!
Yeah, we better grab
all our prized possessions...
– ...and hurry!
Oh no!
What is it?
We need to stock up on food before
the meat shop guy runs away!
That's not the issue at hand here.
Usopp!
Thank goodness!
I thought you might
never come back...
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
Um...
What are you talking about?
You've been tricked!
Your butler is really a pirate!
Hold on...
What kind of joke is this?
It's no joke! I heard it
with my own ears!
Klahadore's really a pirate...
who weaseled his way into your
mansion so he could get your fortune!
He's been pretending to be a butler
for three years straight,
just so he could rob you!
What are you talking about, Usopp?
He said his crew's gonna storm in
and kill you at dawn tomorrow!
I admit, he did say too much earlier.
But lying like this...
It's not like you, Usopp!
No, it's not a lie...
It's the truth...
It's the truth!
Is something the matter, Miss?!
You gotta escape, Kaya!
Let go of her!
Just trust me!
You gotta get out of this village...
before that butler gets back!
Stop!
Come on!
This'll all make sense come tomorrow!
But you gotta escape for now!
Please, listen to me!
You're pathetic.
Get away from her!
No!
Please, catch him!
He roughed up the lady of the house!
– There he is! Get him!
Usopp...
Please pull yourself together, miss!
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
– Captain!
Oh! Hey, guys!
– Hey!
Y-You're alive?!
Alive?
Yeah, I just woke up!
This guy was asleep the whole time!
Anyways, Captain!
We heard everything!
Let's hurry and tell everyone
about the pirates!
Tell everyone?
You're pathetic.
Shut up! All you ever do
is spout huge lies!
I'm lying like usual, obviously!
That damn butler pissed me off,
so I made up a lie about
him being a pirate!
Oh, I see!
So the straw hat guy is in on it, too!
Hey, what's wrong?
I can't believe you'd do that, Captain.
Me neither!
Same here!
Even if that butler is a jerk,
I never thought you would lie
just to hurt someone!
We really respected you, too!
Let's go home!
Yeah, it's suppertime!
Wonder what we're having...
They were never going to
believe me from the start.
I was too optimistic.
Even so, the truth is the truth.
Yeah, they're definitely
gonna show up.
But everyone thinks its a lie.
They think tomorrow will be
just another normal, peaceful day...
That's why...
I'm going to stop the pirates at the beach
tomorrow and make sure this stays a lie!
That's the only logical thing
for a liar like me to do!
Even if I get shot in the arm...
or even if I'm driven off with brooms...
this is my village!
I love this village!
I want to protect everyone!
You're one hell of a nice guy,
pushing your crew away
and going into battle alone!
Just so you know, I have dibs
on all the pirates' treasure!
Alright! We'll help you out!
You guys...
are going to fight with me?!
Why?
There's a whole bunch
of bad guys, right?
"Scared" is written all over your face.
M-Me, scared?!
I'm perfectly okay with
lots of bad guys or whatever!
Because I'm Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
Dammit! Dammit!
What're you looking at?!
These are Klahadore's pirates
we're dealing with!
Of course I'm scared!
What's wrong with that?!
I don't want your pity!
Stop laughing, and leave! Leave!
We ain't laughing!
We're impressed. That's why
we want to help you!
As if we'd risk our lives out of pity!
Oh...
You guys...