Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Feeso
Grug
Pepperjack
Feeso
Grug
Pepperjack
Feeso
Grug
Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Zenef
Timing
Halee
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Luffy vs. Sanji
Fly away...
to the end of the New World!
Cannonball!
Mama, Mistress Smoothie of the
Three Sweet Commanders has arrived!
Whole Cake
Chateau
Okay.
Sweet Commander Katakuri
will also be here shortly!
Oh, it's been a while since
they all got together!
What about Cracker?
Is he home yet?
I bet he'll be back soon
with Straw Hat's head as a present!
I can't wait!
Hm? Is that...?
What happened?
What is it?!
Big Brother!
Big Brother Cracker!
This can't be happening!
He's one of our Three Sweet Commanders!
Who did this?! I'll kill the bastard!
Charlotte Mont d'Or
(19th Son of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Cheese
Charlotte Mont d'Or
(19th Son of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Cheese
Charlotte Opera
(Fifth Son of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Cream
Charlotte Opera
(Fifth Son of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Cream
Where did he fly from?!
I think he went to the woods
Charlotte Galette
(18th Daughter of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Butter
Charlotte Galette
(18th Daughter of the Charlotte Family)
Minister of Butter
to take care of Straw Hat Luffy last night.
That means...
Straw Hat Luffy must be somewhere nearby!
Put out an emergency alert!
Evacuate!
What happened?!
Sweet Commander Cracker was defeated!
What?!
The Seducing
Woods
Luffy! Are you okay?!
I ate a lifetime's worth of biscuits...
But you shrunk back down a lot.
Gear Fourth takes so much energy.
Pound!
Where were you?!
Well, I'm sorry for running away.
I thought you were going to lose.
You're being pretty honest!
Because that guy was
one of the Three Sweet Commanders...
Well...
Anyway, we won!
We did it! We did it!
Yay! Yay!
Lighten up!
We beat one of the emperor's top officers!
I... can't even move...
What have we done...
We helped them defeat Minister Cracker...
Everyone knows that we homies
cannot resist the power of Mama's vivre card!
That is why even Mama's
children aren't allowed to carry one!
Why do you have one?!
Is that true?
So, this thing is pretty valuable.
But you're in big trouble.
Why?
When Sweet Commander Snack was defeated,
the vengeful Cracker's
fleet blackened the sea...
and the angry Linlin created a storm.
I heard it sank the enemy ship
in the blink of an eye!
Storm?
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
Weather?
On her left hand, Zeus, a thundercloud!
On her right hand, Prometheus, a sun!
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
Before she hears about this,
you'd better run!
I don't care if she gets mad!
What?!
I'm the one who wants to get mad!
First of all, that idiot Sanji...
"To my buds, I've gotta see a woman.
I'll be back. –Sanji"
He left so suddenly, leaving behind a note!
All without telling us why!
This is my problem.
I will definitely return.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Thanks to Pudding's map,
we made it this far,
but Pekoms went missing.
And although Pudding said
that she'd bring Sanji,
no one was there
at the rendezvous point.
We wasted a lot of time
while we were lost in the forest!
When they get married,
Sanji will Big Mom's subordinate, right?!
We gotta get moving!
Yeah! When is the wedding?
Cracker said that today the Vinsmokes will be
at the castle where the wedding will take place.
What time is it now? We've gotta stop them!
A-Are you serious?
If you don't run away, you'll really...
I'm not gonna run away!
Hey, tree!
You know where the castle is, don't you?!
Well...
Carry me to the castle!
No way–
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
Nami, can you hear me?!
Chopper!
How are you guys?
We're okay! If things go well,
we'll see you guys and Brook's group–
What?
That doesn't look okay! Chopper?
Either way, we can't be saved from the outside!
Just keep–
Chopper?!
Nami, don't worry! We're fine–
How can I not worry?
Right, we're going to the castle
to find Sanji-kun !
Okay!
Once you rescue Sanji,
let us know through this mirror aga–
It broke!
Hey, Chopper?! Carrot?!
It turned into a normal mirror.
Are they okay?
Has he gotten smaller than before?!
What?
What's going on?!
Whoa...
He's almost back to normal!
Is that humanly possible?!
Meat...
Meat?!
Hey, young girl.
You're lucky.
Why?
There they are.
That's Germa 66.
Can you see Sanji?
Is that it?!
Hey, Sanji!
Your Majesty,
something is charging towards us.
It's been a while!
What?! That idiot made it this far
into Big Mom's territory?!
What is the big tree behind him?!
It's running!
Hey!
Sanji-kun !
I'm glad that we made it in time!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Why are they... here?
Is that Straw Hat Luffy?
Hey! We're here to pick you up!
Sanji!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
Let's go, Sanji!
You said in the note you'd be back,
but I didn't wanna wait.
Banquet!
I was gonna come by myself, but...
You said your hands are important to you.
If you try to escape this island,
your hands will be blown off!
If someone declines Mama's invitation...
So, Zoro and the others
must've gotten to Wano.
...want us to chop his head off.
That's why Nami, Chopper, Brook and I
came to pick you up. And...
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed.
...if you ever fail at being a proper man,
I'll slit my own throat!
Sanji, I'm hungry!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
That's how a parent owns up to their mistake!
I do not want anyone to learn of my shame.
Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't catch a cold.
You see, I had no choice, so...
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun ?!
Begone from my sight,
you miserable, lowlife pirate!
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
I'm a prince...
of Germa!
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
I thought that it would drive you to grief.
The difference between our standings
couldn't be clearer.
If I stay here, I can spend money
and use soldiers and servants as I like.
Going back to that crappy ship
with you and your friends...
or staying here,
marrying Big Mom's beautiful daughter.
It's pretty obvious which is a happier life.
Don't take the note seriously.
I won't go back with you!
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Get out of here...
I've already forgotten your name.
Screw that! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
Sit back!
I'll...
send them away!
What do you mean by sending us away, Sanji?
Get packing.
There is no other meaning.
I don't know what made you come,
but I appreciate
that you took the trouble.
Having said that, if you were really thinking about me,
you should've done just the opposite.
Rather than being with you guys
who are poor and weak,
it'd be better to be part of
the rich and powerful Big Mom Pirates.
I'll be happier.
To be honest, I'm not so sure
about you becoming the pirate king.
It's only human nature
to jump on the bandwagon.
Stop joking, Sanji-kun !
What are you talking about?!
Then, all this time,
you've been fooling me.
Yeah, that's right.
I've actually been looking down on you.
What is that glow? A flame?!
This ought to be fun to watch.
I bet you didn't see it coming,
so it's hard to accept.
I'll prove it to you. Get ready.
Diable Jambe...
No, Sanji-kun !
Joue Shot!
Luffy! You're bleeding!
Sanji-kun, did you really...
Get ready to fight.
Use your haki or you're gonna die.
I just wanna talk to you.
Why do I need haki?
I'm...
not gonna fight you!
Then...
go away!
I'm not gonna do that either!
You've always...
been selfish!
Hey you, cook!
Join my crew!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Please stop, Sanji-kun !
We just came to pick you up!
Luffy has...
fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
So his body is–
Cut it out, Nami!
Stay out of this!
This is...
a duel!
You call this a duel?!
Sanji-kun !
Get out of my sight now!
Luffy!
Go away!
Get out of my face...
now!
I refuse!
Luffy!
Sanji-kun !
Here we go!
Sanji-kun... Please stop...
That's enough! Stop, Sanji-kun !
We'll leave!
I won't!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Concassé!
Luffy! Luffy!
What strength...
After all, he's a Vinsmoke.
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Hey! Stay with me!
Luffy! Luffy!
Hey, Sanji!
Goodbye!
Sorry...
we should never have done this!
Oh! A bitchy girl! How hot!
The superfluous ties
have finally been severed.
Thanks for waiting.
– Let's go.
– Yes, sir.
Luffy!
Wait!
Sanji!
"Lowlife pirate"?!
I know you don't
really want to say these things!
Stop lying!
Did you think that you could
send me away that easily?!
Screw that!
No matter how many times you kick me,
you're the one...
who gets hurt!
Luffy! Why?!
Whatever the reason is, he can't do this–
Shut up!
Should we stop, Sanji?
Keep going.
Hey...
have you heard of the All Blue?!
That sea itself is a miracle!
In that sea...
Our journey...
isn't over yet!
I'll be waiting right here!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
starving to death!
You're the cook of my ship!
He was making food for rats again!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Even if I get hungry
or spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become king of the pirates!