Team One Pace
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Feeso
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Graphics
Datenshi
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
♪ Ship! Ship! Ship! Ship! ♪
0 and 4
By the way, have you ever read the WEN?
The WEN, you know?
The World Economy Newspaper?
You know it, don't you?
There was this comic strip in the WEN!
A giant dreamlike robot was featured in it!
Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
I've been constantly reading it!
Sora, a hero who can walk on water,
accompanied by a
transforming robot and a seagull,
fights the evil armies of Germa 66.
It's a story of a marine hero!
It has fans all over the world!
I heard it's based on true
stories of Navy heroes.
"Navy"
So it's sort of educational
material to brainwash children!
To teach them that "the Navy is
always right and strong"!
But that's not what I like about it!
It's Germa! Germa 66!
Their evil army always corners Sora
by all possible means!
They're evil heroes!
Yes, they get defeated for the
sake of the story every time,
but I've always supported them
with a white-knuckled intensity!
I supported you guys!
Don't include me!
I have nothing to do with them!
Don't say such a thing!
I'm kind of happy to see you in person, actually!
Why don't you tell that to them?
Hey, open!
♪ Door! ♪
Listen...
Stop following me!
I thought this was my room!
This room belongs to me, too!
Let me out! Dammit!
Why are you treating me so poorly?!
I'm a genius scientist!
Haven't you given up yet?!
We were only told to capture you, Caesar!
But he is the precious groom who will
connect the Vinsmoke family
and us, the Charlotte family!
You two are different in value.
I'm not gonna get married.
Just get out.
"Get out"?!
He's just being mean to Vito!
Gotti "the Hitman"
The Fire Tank Pirates
I can't stand it! Apologize to him!
Gotti! Whoa, wait! Wait!
He hasn't been that mean to me!
I'm okay. Thanks. We were
just messing around.
I wasn't.
Gotti. I want both you and Vito out!
Oh, you said it again!
You're a dead man!
No, Gotti!
Say whatever you like!
But I can't tolerate anyone
who insults my friends!
I said "Wait"! Please don't do it!
You don't have to tolerate me.
It's not like I wanna be your friend.
Son of a...
Gotti!
What are you doing?!
Ma'am!
Do you know that he's Vinsmoke's son?!
If you lay so much as a finger on him,
Father's head will roll!
Don't you get it?! Huh?!
Do you want me to chop
your head off first, you dummy?!
Ouch! I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
Hey, you...
Ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
No food for you today as punishment!
No, please, ma'am!
Sorry to bother you.
Let me hear about Germa some other time...
Nope.
Well...
She resembles her...
A Few Days Later...
I can't take it anymore... I'm gonna die...
On the
Thousand Sunny
It's hot... I'm gonna die...
(I'm drying up...)
(Sanji, food... ice cream...)
I can't stand the heat...
I wish I could take off this fur skin...
We're like you...
We Minks have low tolerance for heat.
It's really hot.
I'm gonna become a mummy...
A mummy...
A mummy?
A mummy! Nami-san, if I become a mummy,
I'd be a little more alive, right?
I don't care!
In that case, may I see your panties?
I have no energy even to smack you.
Nami, I'm so hungry and it's hot...
I need nutrition...
We're out of food and we couldn't fish
because it'd been stormy for days
and finally it's clear.
Catch some fish somehow
before the weather changes!
We're all gonna starve to death
before we get there!
Food...
We wanna do so, but Nami...
The water is boiling because it's too hot!
What?!
There won't be any fish around then.
What should we do?!
Emergency food...
Don't look at me!
Luffy! You got a bite!
There's a fish! It's huge!
– Pull it up, Luffy!
– Luffy-san, go...
You can do it, Luffy!
Food...
Food!
He did it!
Luffy!
It's very big!
Let's eat!
I did it!
Its color doesn't seem right.
Is it okay to eat?
What are you saying?!
There's no such thing as an inedible fish!
Luffy! Wait a sec!
I'll go check real quick!
What?
Where's the encyclopedia of fish?!
Sanji's bookshelf is full of nudity!
Found it!
Alright.
No, this is not it.
Here it is!
Luffy! Watch out for its skin!
The skin of that fish is extremely poisonous!
Look! I found Sanji's note!
The skin tastes good!
Luffy! Wait! I'll grill it for you!
Here, try it, Carrot.
The skin's so slimy...
Luffy!
– Shall we eat too?
– Yes!
It's delicious! It's so delicious, Nami!
– Yes, it even makes me cry!
– I'm so happy to be alive! Grr!
It's so good!
I just cooked it like it
said in Sanji-kun's note.
Chopper, you need energy too, first.
Eat it.
Luffy's gonna... d-die!
I-It's cold...
Crying isn't gonna help!
Here! To take care of Luffy,
you have to gain energy, Chopper!
Now, eat!
Okay!
But even if I wanna treat him,
we're short of antidotal herbs!
Yum!
We gotta find an island, Nami!
We're lacking herbs!
Yum!
Food...
But it's not that easy to find an island...
Sanji-kun's encyclopedia says
it's extremely poisonous
and kills you instantly if
you eat the skin, right?
Yeah.
Yum!
But he's still alive!
Doesn't that mean he has strong antibodies?
He has one of the best vital powers
of all humankind!
But he's in very bad shape!
Yum!
Luffy, are you okay?
The river is... beautiful...
He's seeing the River Styx!
We're about to reach Mama's territory.
There are some islands in the area
around Whole Cake Island.
I'd say Black Leg and the others
have passed through those islands
and reached Whole Cake Island by now.
Don't lower your guard, guys...
I'll stand guard!
I was gonna stop by at the first island.
Let's get an antidote there.
Okay.
What? This time, it's snow?
It's beautiful!
It's not snow! Are those clouds of sugar?!
That's right.
And it's a cotton candy flurry that's falling.
What?! Cotton candy?!
Nice! Nice!
Sweet...
Territorial
Sea Slug
Oh? Who is it?
Your transponder snail is
receiving warning signals.
That means we're
in Big Mom's territory for sure.
Cotton candy!
Guys! Hide or disguise yourselves!
So sweet!
Are you listening?!
I see something, Pekoms!
It's a ship! A ship is coming towards us!
What?! Are they here already?!
What do you mean?!
– That's probably a tarte, one of our scout ships.
– What?!
– I can't see it clearly because of the fog.
– What should we do?
– I'll handle it somehow, so all of you, go hide!
– Got it!
– Oh, no! Luffy is looking really sick!
– What?!
The poison must've spread
into his system even more!
It's dangerous! We gotta treat him ASAP!
Don't they have an antidote
on that scout ship?!
– I'll ask them for you! Hurry up and hide!
– Okay!
Chopper-san, hurry up!
What?!
Luffy...
Is that a transponder snail?
It's huge!
There is a number.
Sixty-six?
This is Germa.
Is that the Straw Hats' ship?
That's Germa 66's ship!
Germa 66...
The organization led by Sanji-kun's father...
Why are you here, Straw Hats?!
We're gonna collide!
Guys, furl the sail!
Luffy, I'll be back.
We managed to avoid the crash...
Sanji!
Oh, that twirly eyebrow! It's Sanji-san !
What? Sanji? Is that Sanji?!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun !
Great!
I didn't expect to see you this soon!
How lucky we are...
Hey, Sanji! We have a problem!
Luffy got poisoned by eating fish and is dying!
Is there any antidote on that ship?!
Sanji!
Stop calling me "Sanji"!
You got the wrong person!
Well, of course I look like him.
My name is Yonji!
Vinsmoke "Winch Green" Yonji
Germa 66
Yonji?!
Not "San(three)-ji" but "Yon(four)-ji"?!
He resembles him
and has twirly eyebrows but he's not him?!
My relationship with your friend Sanji
is a secret of secrets.
It's absolutely confidential!
He's definitely his younger brother...
So he also had a younger brother...
What?! How can you tell
that's his younger brother?!
Cutie! Cute, so cute...
Are you really not Sanji?!
Your Highness.
I don't think they are transporting
Prince Sanji on that ship.
So I guess we missed each other.
You're right. Let's go back.
It was a wasted trip.
Wait, Sanji!
I'm Yonji!
Oh, Luffy...
A rash is breaking out all over his body!
He's losing his resistance!
This poison is so severe!
Luffy may have strong antibodies, but it's...
Luffy, stay with us!
Hey, it's just fish poison!
I thought you were gonna be the pirate king!
Luffy! Don't die!
Luffy-san !
Hey, please!
I bet you have antidotes!
We used all we got,
but he still needs more!
Hey!
If you're Sanji-san's brother,
please save Luffy-san !
I'm sorry.
I have no interest in saving people.
Or do you wanna try and
rob the medicine from us?
Like pirates?
What a jerk!
He's totally different from Sanji-kun !
Even though he likes girls too!
He's not kind at all!
Just say the word if you want me to kill him!
Yonji.
Stop being so stingy!
Your Highness!
What's going on?!
Luffy!
Oh, Lady Reiju!
– Luffy-san !
– No!
An invader!
Who are you?!
Hello. I'm sorry.
My young brother is a cold-blooded jackass.
Young brother?
Are you his sister?
Vinsmoke "Poison Pink" Reiju
Germa 66
Her eyebrows are twirly too!
She's gorgeous!
Reiju!
Is he flying?!
You bitch!
How could you humiliate me?!
Shut up!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
What? Is he hovering in the air?
It's science!
What?!
Germa 66 is a group of fighters
who have honed themselves with science.
They are a scientific
fighting squad, if you will.
And Mama is...
looking to get that technology!
Pekoms-san, if I'm correct,
Vinsmoke was...
the name of a royal family, wasn't it?
If I remember right, it was a family that
conquered the North Blue
by force of arms long ago!
By "royal family,"
you mean like Vivi and Neptune?!
What? Are they such a prominent family?
That's right. They were synonymous
with "evil" in a past age.
That's why they were used as
models for the comic strip.
Skeleton-san,
you have so much historical knowledge.
I've lived a long time...
I'm dead now though.
But it's not just a story from the past.
We're still a royal family.
Germa is a country without soil.
We have no land to govern,
but we're given the right to attend the Reverie.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
If that is so, may I see your panties?
Stop it!
Okay, now, can I have it?
Looks like he ate an armored stonefish
from the Boiling Sea, didn't he?
What? How did you know?
The way this poison works is unique.
He must be greedy.
It could even kill a giant instantly.
What?! Oh, no!
Then, there's no way to save Luffy...
I shouldn't be a ship's doctor anymore!
But this boy is lucky.
Because this poison is...
one of my favorite things!
W-What are you gonna do?
Let's have it!
What?! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
If you suck up poison like that, you're gonna die!
Oh! I'm jealous! Smooch!
I wish I could change places with him!
Even though my lips...
are gone!
The rash is transferring to her body!
What?!
The rash on Luffy's body is all gone!
You've sucked it all out?! Are you alright?!
Yes, of course. I'm Poison Pink.
Poison...
...Pink?
It was delicious!
What?! What happened?!
Luffy! Luffy!
– I'm so relieved!
– Are you all right?!
What a relief!
Luffy!
Oh? Did I fall asleep while eating fish?
The skin was so good! Is there any left?
– No! Don't you remember?!
– Nope.
Sanji!
She's a woman!
Oh, right. Who is this?
Luffy-san, she saved your life!
What? Thank you for... what again?
So that's Straw Hat Luffy...
Oh! You're Sanji's sister!
Yes.
Sanji is one of us, the Vinsmoke family.
Our father parted from Sanji
when he was a little kid
and has been looking for him.
When Sanji's wanted poster
was circulated two years ago,
our father immediately asked
Navy Headquarters to pursue him.
But they found the wrong man—
someone named Duval.
Duval!
He's the guy from the Flying Fish Riders
who we met before Sabaody...
Oh, I remember!
Sanji-san was mad about it too.
It was only recently
that the government called us saying
that they finally captured an image
of Black Leg Sanji amid the chaos
evoked by the Straw Hats' comeback.
Our father raised the bounty right away
and made them change "DEAD OR ALIVE"...
... to "ONLY ALIVE."
That's why only Sanji-kun's poster was
changed a little bit.
Where is Sanji now?
I don't know.
Maybe he's with Big Mom or with our father.
We came to greet him,
but I think we missed each other.
Well, if he can attend the tea party,
that's all that matters.
And I got to see you guys, too.
Thank you for looking after my brother
all this time.
Sanji's sister!
Thank you for saving my life.
But...
I still want Sanji back! He's my friend!
I'm gonna take back Sanji at any cost!
See? She saved our enemy's life.
Hey, you!
You're Pekoms from the Big Mom Pirates, right?
Why are you with the Straw Hats?
I have my own reason!
Why do I have to explain it to you guys?!
There's no bond between us yet!
You're right!
I'll pretend that I didn't
see anything for now.
Yeah, we don't wanna cause trouble and
break off our brother's marriage.
We'd best all tread lightly.
That'd be smart!
Weigh anchor! Let's go back.
Well, good luck.
They didn't get into a fight with Germa,
it seems.
Yes, I'm sure that's their ship.
Straw Hat Luffy is on board, too.
What do you wanna do...
Jinbe?