Team One Pace
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Graphics
Datenshi
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Luffy vs. Commander Cracker
Hmph! What an insolent brat!
Look at this sword! Isn't it something?
It's called Pretzel!
It's a one-of-a-kind sword!
I'll teach you a lesson
about the roughness of the New World!
What?! A one-of-a-kind sword?!
But you've got six!
Let's run for now, Luffy!
No way!
Gear Third!
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
You fools have got nowhere to run!
Damn!
Pretzel Roll!
That's my brother!
Luffy...
Oh, no!
They're members of an emperor's crew!
We underestimated them!
Even Luffy's having a hard time
with her underling!
Luffy! Run!
W-What the...?
Stop there! I'll deal with you two!
Me too!
I know how you feel.
You just got scared, didn't you?
The Worst Generation?
What's so "worst" about it?!
After being puffed up
in the first half of the Grand Line,
lots of crews have come here and been certain
that their captain would be pirate king,
only to be disappointed by the result.
I've witnessed it firsthand!
In the past two years, many of them have come wandering into Mama's territory.
"Captain" Kid.
"Roar of the Sea" Apoo.
"Gang" Bege.
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
Aside from Bege, who wisely realized he was out of his depth and joined our crew,
the rest were all tossed out, without ever getting to see or speak to Mama!
The only one to make any progress was...
Mad Monk Urouge!
He was impudent enough to defeat
one of the Sweet Commanders!
They were the Four Sweet Commanders
until not so long ago.
But that's as far as he got.
Mama was furious,
and sent Cracker to crush him!
He had nowhere to run!
I bet he's dead in a ditch right now!
She disappeared!
Listen!
This is your brick wall in the New World.
Trying to fight the Four Emperors? You must be dreaming!
You'll never even see Mama!
Infiltrate the tea party?
Stop the wedding?
Taking your crewmate back?!
All of that is a dream!
You have no hope of even catching sight of Mama's face! You will die in this forest!
M-My Tact...
Now, come to the Mirro-world!
Let go of me!
Come on! Come on! Come to me!
I'll have plenty of time to cut up your face and body in here!
Pound-chan !
Just give up!
Let go of her, Brûlée!
Thank you!
Father Pound!
No, it's just Pound, now!
What you've just done is treason against Mama!
You're a dead man! No one will save you now!
Thunderbolt...
Tempo!
Brûlée will come back.
She can show up in any place that has a mirror.
I'm sorry. You did it to help me!
I was targeted to be killed anyway.
By my ex-wife.
By the way, are you Lola's friend?
Uh-huh.
I see. It's no mistake!
Lola's mama is Big Mom.
The fact that those trees in the forest
are afraid of this vivre card proves it.
I'll make good use of it, Lola!
Oh, no! We'll get involved!
Hey! Don't get so spread apart that you forget your Seducing Woods duties!
There must never be an exit to the woods!
O-Okay!
Block his way!
Gum-Gum...
Hawk Gatling!
Hard Biscuit!
Damn!
His Armament is too hard!
If you consider Vinsmoke Sanji to be a friend,
then leave him alone.
He's a prince of a mighty kingdom.
His status is far greater than yours!
He will have a proud wife and live here...
with his every desire catered to!
You selfishly claim you will take back your friend,
rather than allowing him to be happy?
When his annoying former captain finds him,
that proud prince will no doubt say...
"Begone from my sight,
you miserable, lowlife pirate!"
Muscle Balloon!
Gear Fourth!
Boundman!
Muscle Balloon is a good name.
But what can a balloon do?
Let me say it one more time!
Begone from my sight, you miserable, lowlife pirate!
Gum-Gum...
Kong...
Hard Biscuit!
Gun!
Minister Cracker!
Don't insult Sanji!
Even if he's happy
and doesn't want to come back,
he'd never talk to us like that!
I'm gonna go see Sanji!
Gum-Gum...
Don't push your luck!
Pretzel...
Kong Gun!
Roll!
Minister Cracker!
What?!
You did a good job breaking...
my armor!
Who are you?!
Who am I?
I'm pretty sure I already introduced myself as Sweet Commander Cracker.
"Thousand Arms" Cracker
I really liked that armor...
Armor?
No way! He coughed up blood!
– That was jam!
– Jam?!
Since I'm a craftsman at heart,
I also make sure that it tastes good.
I'm a biscuit man
with the powers of the Bis-Bis Fruit!
I can produce and manipulate an infinite number of biscuits!
To shape them into anything...
Crush Biscuit!
And if I craft it carefully...
Look! It's the face of a hardened warrior!
The form that biscuits have taken
has changed throughout history, depending on the baker.
Very few people have forced me to reveal my true identity.
Just look at the picture on my wanted poster, which was issued by the World Government.
It's not me. It's my armor!
I despise pain. I can't even
stand the prick of a needle!
And that's why I use my armor to fight.
When I clap my hands, they multiply.
That is the power and beauty of my biscuits!
I have unlimited power at my disposal!
You had to give your all to defeat...
a biscuit soldier that I can remake over and over.
Do you understand now why you will never see
Vinsmoke Sanji again?
I will definitely return.
I'm gonna see Sanji!
Learning that there are people you can't beat
no matter the effort you put in
is a mark of true growth, brat!
I'll teach you a lesson!
– We can't do it!
– We have no chance!
Run!
I guess we'll be safe here.
We're no match for him!
I'm here.
When did she get there?!
If you close your mouth,
you'll be sealing your doom.
Even if all of you shriveled up
and withered away, I wouldn't care at all!
What?!
You're a horrible person.
Sweet Commander Cracker,
or his mother, Emperor Big Mom.
Which is scarier?
You're scarier than both of them!
Brûlée's Mirro-world
I see! I get the picture!
Listen, Carrot!
I have a great idea,
so from now on, please call me Big Bro Chopper!
Uh-huh, okay.
Good!
And what is your idea, Chobro?!
Chobro?!
That's right!
Short for Big Bro Chopper, Chobro!
Well, okay.
It seems like this world of mirrors
is connected to all of the mirrors
on Whole Cake Island!
Yes, I think you're right.
Instead of escaping from here,
we should take advantage of Brûlée's ability!
How?
We can look for Sanji through these mirrors!
You're right! That's my Chobro!
Your compliment doesn't
make me happy, you jerk!
The Capital (Sweet City)
Whole Cake Island
Secret Song: Whirlwind Slash!
– That went well.
– Mm-hm.
After it's done patrolling, the biscuit soldier will return to the castle storage room.
We'll wait until then to make a move.
I'll beat you up and go see Sanji!
Gum-Gum...
Kong...
Organ!
Advance!
Honey Pretzel!
♪ It's morning! It's morning! ♪
Good morning!
Today, the Vinsmoke family will be coming to the castle,
♪ Good morning! ♪
Whole Cake Chateau
♪ It's morning! It's morning! ♪
and we'll hold an engagement ceremony, Mama.
♪ It's a new morning again! ♪
What about the wedding cake?
That comes tomorrow.
It's been one night.
How are the mold spores holding up?
This is their last chance
to make contact with their friend.
Oh, please! How could you say that
after you sent Minister Cracker?
It's true that once Black Leg enters the castle,
their chances of contact are essentially zero!
After all, both the tea party and the wedding
will be held in the castle.
So they're all talk? Just like the others?
Some of the Vinsmoke sons
aren't here yet, right?
Oh, actually,
The Kingdom of Germa
I just received word that they have landed at the port.
Good. They're here.
My beloved sons!
I can't wait to see them face off with Sanji.
Welcome back!
Vinsmoke "Sparking Red" Ichiji
Eldest Son of the Vinsmoke Family
Vinsmoke "Electric Blue" Niji
Second Son of the Vinsmoke Family
– Prince Ichiji! Prince Niji!
– Nice to see you back from your long trip!
I can't believe that you ended the
long war on Broc Coli.
Why isn't he coming out to greet us?
Give it a rest, Niji.